[
  {
    "question": "hi, how are you doing?",
    "answer": "i'm fine. how about yourself?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm fine. how about yourself?",
    "answer": "i'm pretty good. thanks for asking."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm pretty good. thanks for asking.",
    "answer": "no problem. so how have you been?"
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem. so how have you been?",
    "answer": "i've been great. what about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been great. what about you?",
    "answer": "i've been good. i'm in school right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been good. i'm in school right now.",
    "answer": "what school do you go to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what school do you go to?",
    "answer": "i go to pcc."
  },
  {
    "question": "i go to pcc.",
    "answer": "do you like it there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you like it there?",
    "answer": "it's okay. it's a really big campus."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's okay. it's a really big campus.",
    "answer": "good luck with school."
  },
  {
    "question": "good luck with school.",
    "answer": "thank you very much."
  },
  {
    "question": "how's it going?",
    "answer": "i'm doing well. how about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm doing well. how about you?",
    "answer": "never better, thanks."
  },
  {
    "question": "never better, thanks.",
    "answer": "so how have you been lately?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so how have you been lately?",
    "answer": "i've actually been pretty good. you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i've actually been pretty good. you?",
    "answer": "i'm actually in school right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm actually in school right now.",
    "answer": "which school do you attend?"
  },
  {
    "question": "which school do you attend?",
    "answer": "i'm attending pcc right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm attending pcc right now.",
    "answer": "are you enjoying it there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you enjoying it there?",
    "answer": "it's not bad. there are a lot of people there."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not bad. there are a lot of people there.",
    "answer": "good luck with that."
  },
  {
    "question": "good luck with that.",
    "answer": "thanks."
  },
  {
    "question": "how are you doing today?",
    "answer": "i'm doing great. what about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm doing great. what about you?",
    "answer": "i'm absolutely lovely, thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm absolutely lovely, thank you.",
    "answer": "everything's been good with you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "everything's been good with you?",
    "answer": "i haven't been better. how about yourself?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't been better. how about yourself?",
    "answer": "i started school recently."
  },
  {
    "question": "i started school recently.",
    "answer": "where are you going to school?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where are you going to school?",
    "answer": "i'm going to pcc."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to pcc.",
    "answer": "how do you like it so far?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you like it so far?",
    "answer": "i like it so far. my classes are pretty good right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like it so far. my classes are pretty good right now.",
    "answer": "i wish you luck."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's an ugly day today.",
    "answer": "i know. i think it may rain."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know. i think it may rain.",
    "answer": "it's the middle of summer, it shouldn't rain today."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the middle of summer, it shouldn't rain today.",
    "answer": "that would be weird."
  },
  {
    "question": "that would be weird.",
    "answer": "yeah, especially since it's ninety degrees outside."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, especially since it's ninety degrees outside.",
    "answer": "i know, it would be horrible if it rained and it was hot outside."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know, it would be horrible if it rained and it was hot outside.",
    "answer": "yes, it would be."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it would be.",
    "answer": "i really wish it wasn't so hot every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really wish it wasn't so hot every day.",
    "answer": "me too. i can't wait until winter."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. i can't wait until winter.",
    "answer": "i like winter too, but sometimes it gets too cold."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like winter too, but sometimes it gets too cold.",
    "answer": "i'd rather be cold than hot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd rather be cold than hot.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "it doesn't look very nice outside today.",
    "answer": "you're right. i think it's going to rain later."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. i think it's going to rain later.",
    "answer": "in the middle of the summer, it shouldn't be raining."
  },
  {
    "question": "in the middle of the summer, it shouldn't be raining.",
    "answer": "that wouldn't seem right."
  },
  {
    "question": "that wouldn't seem right.",
    "answer": "considering that it's over ninety degrees outside, that would be weird."
  },
  {
    "question": "considering that it's over ninety degrees outside, that would be weird.",
    "answer": "exactly, it wouldn't be nice if it started raining. it's too hot."
  },
  {
    "question": "exactly, it wouldn't be nice if it started raining. it's too hot.",
    "answer": "i know, you're absolutely right."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know, you're absolutely right.",
    "answer": "i wish it would cool off one day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish it would cool off one day.",
    "answer": "that's how i feel, i want winter to come soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's how i feel, i want winter to come soon.",
    "answer": "i enjoy the winter, but it gets really cold sometimes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy the winter, but it gets really cold sometimes.",
    "answer": "i know what you mean, but i'd rather be cold than hot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know what you mean, but i'd rather be cold than hot.",
    "answer": "that's exactly how i feel."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish it was a nicer day today.",
    "answer": "that is true. i hope it doesn't rain."
  },
  {
    "question": "that is true. i hope it doesn't rain.",
    "answer": "it wouldn't rain in the middle of the summer."
  },
  {
    "question": "it wouldn't rain in the middle of the summer.",
    "answer": "it wouldn't seem right if it started raining right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "it wouldn't seem right if it started raining right now.",
    "answer": "it would be weird if it started raining in ninety degree weather."
  },
  {
    "question": "it would be weird if it started raining in ninety degree weather.",
    "answer": "any rain right now would be pointless."
  },
  {
    "question": "any rain right now would be pointless.",
    "answer": "that's right, it really would be."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's right, it really would be.",
    "answer": "i want it to cool down some."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want it to cool down some.",
    "answer": "i know what you mean, i can't wait until it's winter."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know what you mean, i can't wait until it's winter.",
    "answer": "winter is great. i wish it didn't get so cold sometimes though."
  },
  {
    "question": "winter is great. i wish it didn't get so cold sometimes though.",
    "answer": "i would rather deal with the winter than the summer."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's such a nice day.",
    "answer": "yes, it is."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it is.",
    "answer": "it looks like it may rain soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "it looks like it may rain soon.",
    "answer": "yes, and i hope that it does."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and i hope that it does.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "i really love how rain clears the air."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really love how rain clears the air.",
    "answer": "me too. it always smells so fresh after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. it always smells so fresh after it rains.",
    "answer": "yes, but i love the night air after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i love the night air after it rains.",
    "answer": "really? why is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really? why is it?",
    "answer": "because you can see the stars perfectly."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you can see the stars perfectly.",
    "answer": "i really hope it rains today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really hope it rains today.",
    "answer": "yeah, me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "isn't it a nice day?",
    "answer": "it really is."
  },
  {
    "question": "it really is.",
    "answer": "it seems that it may rain today."
  },
  {
    "question": "it seems that it may rain today.",
    "answer": "hopefully it will."
  },
  {
    "question": "hopefully it will.",
    "answer": "how come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how come?",
    "answer": "i like how clear the sky gets after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like how clear the sky gets after it rains.",
    "answer": "i feel the same way. it smells so good after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel the same way. it smells so good after it rains.",
    "answer": "i especially love the night air when it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "i especially love the night air when it rains.",
    "answer": "really? why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really? why?",
    "answer": "the stars look so much closer after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "the stars look so much closer after it rains.",
    "answer": "i really want it to rain today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really want it to rain today.",
    "answer": "yeah, so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't you think it's nice out?",
    "answer": "yes, i think so too."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i think so too.",
    "answer": "i think that it's going to rain."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that it's going to rain.",
    "answer": "i hope that it does rain."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope that it does rain.",
    "answer": "you like the rain?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you like the rain?",
    "answer": "the sky looks so clean after it rains. i love it."
  },
  {
    "question": "the sky looks so clean after it rains. i love it.",
    "answer": "i understand. rain does make it smell cleaner."
  },
  {
    "question": "i understand. rain does make it smell cleaner.",
    "answer": "i love most how it is at night after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love most how it is at night after it rains.",
    "answer": "how come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how come?",
    "answer": "you can see the stars so much more clearly after it rains."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can see the stars so much more clearly after it rains.",
    "answer": "i would love for it to rain today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really want to go to the beach this weekend.",
    "answer": "that sounds like fun. what's the weather going to be like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like fun. what's the weather going to be like?",
    "answer": "i heard that it's going to be warm this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i heard that it's going to be warm this weekend.",
    "answer": "is it going to be perfect beach weather?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it going to be perfect beach weather?",
    "answer": "i believe so."
  },
  {
    "question": "i believe so.",
    "answer": "good. i hope it doesn't cool off this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "good. i hope it doesn't cool off this weekend.",
    "answer": "i know. i really want to go to the beach."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know. i really want to go to the beach.",
    "answer": "but you know that california weather is really unpredictable."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you know that california weather is really unpredictable.",
    "answer": "you're right. one minute it's hot, and then the next minute it's cold."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. one minute it's hot, and then the next minute it's cold.",
    "answer": "i really wish the weather would just stay the same."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really wish the weather would just stay the same.",
    "answer": "i do too. that way we can have our activities planned ahead of time."
  },
  {
    "question": "i do too. that way we can have our activities planned ahead of time.",
    "answer": "yeah, that would make things a lot easier."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would like to take a trip to the beach this weekend.",
    "answer": "a trip to the beach would be fun. how is the weather going to be?"
  },
  {
    "question": "a trip to the beach would be fun. how is the weather going to be?",
    "answer": "the forecast says that it will be warm on the weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "the forecast says that it will be warm on the weekend.",
    "answer": "so do you think it'll be perfect weather for the beach?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so do you think it'll be perfect weather for the beach?",
    "answer": "it sounds like it will be."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sounds like it will be.",
    "answer": "i really hope it doesn't get cold."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really hope it doesn't get cold.",
    "answer": "that would ruin things, i want to go so badly."
  },
  {
    "question": "that would ruin things, i want to go so badly.",
    "answer": "the weather in california is unpredictable, so you never know."
  },
  {
    "question": "the weather in california is unpredictable, so you never know.",
    "answer": "that is true. the weather is constantly changing."
  },
  {
    "question": "that is true. the weather is constantly changing.",
    "answer": "it would be nice if the weather would never change."
  },
  {
    "question": "it would be nice if the weather would never change.",
    "answer": "that would be great, then we could plan things sooner."
  },
  {
    "question": "that would be great, then we could plan things sooner.",
    "answer": "true. predictable weather would make life easier."
  },
  {
    "question": "it would be nice to go to the beach sometime this weekend.",
    "answer": "what's the weather going to be like? i may want to go too."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the weather going to be like? i may want to go too.",
    "answer": "the weather this weekend is supposed to be warm."
  },
  {
    "question": "the weather this weekend is supposed to be warm.",
    "answer": "will it be good beach weather?"
  },
  {
    "question": "will it be good beach weather?",
    "answer": "i think it will be."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it will be.",
    "answer": "it wouldn't be good if it got cold this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "it wouldn't be good if it got cold this weekend.",
    "answer": "i want this trip to be perfect, i hope it stays warm."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want this trip to be perfect, i hope it stays warm.",
    "answer": "this california weather is so uncertain, it's impossible to know what'll happen."
  },
  {
    "question": "this california weather is so uncertain, it's impossible to know what'll happen.",
    "answer": "i know. every day the weather seems different."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know. every day the weather seems different.",
    "answer": "i would love it if it wasn't always so unpredictable."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would love it if it wasn't always so unpredictable.",
    "answer": "that would make it easier for us to make plans."
  },
  {
    "question": "hello, may i speak to alice please?",
    "answer": "this is she. how's it going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is she. how's it going?",
    "answer": "i've been trying to call you all day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been trying to call you all day.",
    "answer": "sorry about that. i was cleaning up."
  },
  {
    "question": "sorry about that. i was cleaning up.",
    "answer": "it's okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's okay.",
    "answer": "so what were you calling me about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what were you calling me about?",
    "answer": "oh, i just wanted to see if you wanted to hang out tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, i just wanted to see if you wanted to hang out tomorrow.",
    "answer": "sure, what did you want to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure, what did you want to do?",
    "answer": "maybe we can go see a movie or something."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe we can go see a movie or something.",
    "answer": "that sounds like fun. let's do it."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like fun. let's do it.",
    "answer": "i'll see you tomorrow then."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll see you tomorrow then.",
    "answer": "see you then. goodbye."
  },
  {
    "question": "hi, how are you. is alice there?",
    "answer": "speaking. what's up?"
  },
  {
    "question": "speaking. what's up?",
    "answer": "why haven't you answered the phone?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why haven't you answered the phone?",
    "answer": "my bad, i had chores to do."
  },
  {
    "question": "my bad, i had chores to do.",
    "answer": "that's all right."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's all right.",
    "answer": "what was the reason for your call?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the reason for your call?",
    "answer": "i want to do something tomorrow with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to do something tomorrow with you.",
    "answer": "sounds good. what did you have in mind?"
  },
  {
    "question": "sounds good. what did you have in mind?",
    "answer": "i was thinking about seeing a movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was thinking about seeing a movie.",
    "answer": "okay, let's go see a movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, let's go see a movie.",
    "answer": "until then."
  },
  {
    "question": "until then.",
    "answer": "talk to you later."
  },
  {
    "question": "is alice available?",
    "answer": "you're talking to her."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're talking to her.",
    "answer": "i've called you a hundred times today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've called you a hundred times today.",
    "answer": "i was busy doing something. i apologize."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was busy doing something. i apologize.",
    "answer": "no problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem.",
    "answer": "did you need something?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you need something?",
    "answer": "do you want to do something tomorrow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you want to do something tomorrow?",
    "answer": "is there somewhere special you wanted to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is there somewhere special you wanted to go?",
    "answer": "how about a movie?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about a movie?",
    "answer": "a movie sounds good."
  },
  {
    "question": "a movie sounds good.",
    "answer": "call me tomorrow then."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you seen the new girl in school?",
    "answer": "no, i haven't."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i haven't.",
    "answer": "she's really pretty."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's really pretty.",
    "answer": "describe her to me."
  },
  {
    "question": "describe her to me.",
    "answer": "she's not too tall."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's not too tall.",
    "answer": "well, how tall is she?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, how tall is she?",
    "answer": "she's about five feet even."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's about five feet even.",
    "answer": "what does she look like, though?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does she look like, though?",
    "answer": "she has pretty light brown eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "she has pretty light brown eyes.",
    "answer": "i may know which girl you're talking about."
  },
  {
    "question": "i may know which girl you're talking about.",
    "answer": "so you have seen her around?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so you have seen her around?",
    "answer": "yes, i have."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's a new girl in school, have you seen her yet?",
    "answer": "i haven't seen her yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't seen her yet.",
    "answer": "i think that she is very pretty."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that she is very pretty.",
    "answer": "tell me how she looks."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me how she looks.",
    "answer": "she's kind of short."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's kind of short.",
    "answer": "what height is she?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what height is she?",
    "answer": "she's probably about five feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's probably about five feet.",
    "answer": "that's nice, but tell me what she looks like."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's nice, but tell me what she looks like.",
    "answer": "the first thing i noticed was her beautiful brown eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "the first thing i noticed was her beautiful brown eyes.",
    "answer": "i think i might've bumped into her before."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i might've bumped into her before.",
    "answer": "are you telling me that you've seen her before?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you telling me that you've seen her before?",
    "answer": "i believe so."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you met the new girl?",
    "answer": "no. have you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "no. have you?",
    "answer": "she's one of the prettiest girls at the school."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's one of the prettiest girls at the school.",
    "answer": "what does she look like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does she look like?",
    "answer": "well, she's quite short."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, she's quite short.",
    "answer": "how tall would you say that she is?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how tall would you say that she is?",
    "answer": "i would say she's only five feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would say she's only five feet.",
    "answer": "what about her facial features?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about her facial features?",
    "answer": "she has light brown eyes, absolutely beautiful."
  },
  {
    "question": "she has light brown eyes, absolutely beautiful.",
    "answer": "i think i know who you're talking about."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i know who you're talking about.",
    "answer": "have you seen her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why weren't you at school yesterday?",
    "answer": "i wasn't really feeling well."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wasn't really feeling well.",
    "answer": "what was wrong with you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was wrong with you?",
    "answer": "my stomach was upset."
  },
  {
    "question": "my stomach was upset.",
    "answer": "do you feel better now?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you feel better now?",
    "answer": "i don't really feel too well yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't really feel too well yet.",
    "answer": "do you want anything to make you feel better?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you want anything to make you feel better?",
    "answer": "no, thanks. i already took some medicine."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, thanks. i already took some medicine.",
    "answer": "i hope you feel better."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope you feel better.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "what reason do you have for missing school?",
    "answer": "i was sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was sick.",
    "answer": "how were you sick?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how were you sick?",
    "answer": "i had a stomachache."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had a stomachache.",
    "answer": "did it get any better?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did it get any better?",
    "answer": "i'm still feeling under the weather."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm still feeling under the weather.",
    "answer": "would you like anything for your stomach?"
  },
  {
    "question": "would you like anything for your stomach?",
    "answer": "i took something earlier."
  },
  {
    "question": "i took something earlier.",
    "answer": "get better."
  },
  {
    "question": "get better.",
    "answer": "thanks a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "why didn't you go to school yesterday?",
    "answer": "i stayed home because i wasn't feeling well."
  },
  {
    "question": "i stayed home because i wasn't feeling well.",
    "answer": "what was your problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was your problem?",
    "answer": "my stomach was bothering me."
  },
  {
    "question": "my stomach was bothering me.",
    "answer": "are you feeling any better?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you feeling any better?",
    "answer": "i'm still feeling a little sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm still feeling a little sick.",
    "answer": "i'm going to the store, would you like any pepto bismol?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to the store, would you like any pepto bismol?",
    "answer": "that's okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's okay.",
    "answer": "i hope you feel better."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear the good news?",
    "answer": "no, i haven't."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i haven't.",
    "answer": "i got a promotion at my job."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a promotion at my job.",
    "answer": "did you really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you really?",
    "answer": "seriously, i am so excited."
  },
  {
    "question": "seriously, i am so excited.",
    "answer": "well, congratulations."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, congratulations.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "i'm so happy for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm so happy for you.",
    "answer": "really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really?",
    "answer": "yes. you really deserved this."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. you really deserved this.",
    "answer": "you think so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you think so?",
    "answer": "yes. good for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard my good news?",
    "answer": "you haven't told me anything yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "you haven't told me anything yet.",
    "answer": "i got a promotion at work earlier this week."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a promotion at work earlier this week.",
    "answer": "is that right?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right?",
    "answer": "it's the truth. i am really happy."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the truth. i am really happy.",
    "answer": "congratulations on your promotion."
  },
  {
    "question": "congratulations on your promotion.",
    "answer": "thank you very much."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you very much.",
    "answer": "i am really excited for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i am really excited for you.",
    "answer": "are you really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you really?",
    "answer": "i'm serious. you deserved this promotion."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm serious. you deserved this promotion.",
    "answer": "is that what you really think?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that what you really think?",
    "answer": "yes, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't told you what happened yet, have i?",
    "answer": "i haven't heard anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't heard anything.",
    "answer": "my boss offered me a promotion, and i took it."
  },
  {
    "question": "my boss offered me a promotion, and i took it.",
    "answer": "are you serious?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you serious?",
    "answer": "yes, i am really excited."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i am really excited.",
    "answer": "that's great. congratulations."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's great. congratulations.",
    "answer": "i appreciate that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i appreciate that.",
    "answer": "you have no idea how happy i am for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "you have no idea how happy i am for you.",
    "answer": "for real?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you look really nice today.",
    "answer": "thank you. i just got this outfit the other day."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. i just got this outfit the other day.",
    "answer": "really, where did you get it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really, where did you get it?",
    "answer": "i got it from macy's."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got it from macy's.",
    "answer": "it's really nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's really nice.",
    "answer": "thanks again. you look nice today, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks again. you look nice today, too.",
    "answer": "thank you. i just got these shoes today."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. i just got these shoes today.",
    "answer": "really? what kind of shoes are they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really? what kind of shoes are they?",
    "answer": "these are called all star chuck taylors."
  },
  {
    "question": "these are called all star chuck taylors.",
    "answer": "i really like those. how much did they cost?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i really like those. how much did they cost?",
    "answer": "they were about forty dollars."
  },
  {
    "question": "they were about forty dollars.",
    "answer": "i think i'm going to go buy myself a pair."
  },
  {
    "question": "i absolutely love what you're wearing today.",
    "answer": "you do? i just bought this outfit a couple days ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "you do? i just bought this outfit a couple days ago.",
    "answer": "seriously, it looks really nice on you. where did you buy it from?"
  },
  {
    "question": "seriously, it looks really nice on you. where did you buy it from?",
    "answer": "i bought it from the macy's at the santa anita mall."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought it from the macy's at the santa anita mall.",
    "answer": "i really like that outfit."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really like that outfit.",
    "answer": "thanks. i think you look nice today, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks. i think you look nice today, too.",
    "answer": "thank you. i just bought these new shoes earlier today."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. i just bought these new shoes earlier today.",
    "answer": "those are nice. what are they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "those are nice. what are they?",
    "answer": "these are some chucks."
  },
  {
    "question": "these are some chucks.",
    "answer": "those are great. how much were they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "those are great. how much were they?",
    "answer": "i got them for forty."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got them for forty.",
    "answer": "i think i might go and find me my own pair of chucks."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that you look very cute today.",
    "answer": "is that right? this is a brand new outfit."
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right? this is a brand new outfit.",
    "answer": "what store did you get it from?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what store did you get it from?",
    "answer": "i went to macy's and picked it out."
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to macy's and picked it out.",
    "answer": "i love your outfit right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love your outfit right now.",
    "answer": "well, i think you look nice today too."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i think you look nice today too.",
    "answer": "thanks. i found these new shoes earlier at the store."
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks. i found these new shoes earlier at the store.",
    "answer": "i think that those are some really nice shoes. what kind are they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that those are some really nice shoes. what kind are they?",
    "answer": "these are chucks."
  },
  {
    "question": "these are chucks.",
    "answer": "your shoes look really nice. how much did you get them for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "your shoes look really nice. how much did you get them for?",
    "answer": "they only cost me about forty dollars."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me, what do you enjoy doing in your spare time?",
    "answer": "i enjoy drawing and painting."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy drawing and painting.",
    "answer": "you know how to draw and paint?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you know how to draw and paint?",
    "answer": "yes, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i do.",
    "answer": "when did you learn how to do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when did you learn how to do that?",
    "answer": "i learned back in high school."
  },
  {
    "question": "i learned back in high school.",
    "answer": "oh, so you took an art class?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, so you took an art class?",
    "answer": "yeah, i loved that class."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, i loved that class.",
    "answer": "i see that you're pretty talented."
  },
  {
    "question": "i see that you're pretty talented.",
    "answer": "thank you very much."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you very much.",
    "answer": "i wish i had a talent like that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i had a talent like that.",
    "answer": "i'm sure you have a talent. it's just hidden."
  },
  {
    "question": "what kinds of things do you like to do?",
    "answer": "i've always liked to draw and paint."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've always liked to draw and paint.",
    "answer": "i didn't know you knew how to draw and paint."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't know you knew how to draw and paint.",
    "answer": "i do it every once in a while."
  },
  {
    "question": "i do it every once in a while.",
    "answer": "how long have you known how to do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how long have you known how to do that?",
    "answer": "i first learned how to do it in high school."
  },
  {
    "question": "i first learned how to do it in high school.",
    "answer": "did you take some sort of art class or something?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you take some sort of art class or something?",
    "answer": "that was my favorite class."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was my favorite class.",
    "answer": "you have got to be talented."
  },
  {
    "question": "you have got to be talented.",
    "answer": "thanks."
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks.",
    "answer": "if only i was talented."
  },
  {
    "question": "if only i was talented.",
    "answer": "you have a talent. you just don't know what it is yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "are there any hobbies you do?",
    "answer": "when i have time, i sometimes draw and paint."
  },
  {
    "question": "when i have time, i sometimes draw and paint.",
    "answer": "oh, you actually do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, you actually do that?",
    "answer": "every so often, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "every so often, i do.",
    "answer": "did you always know how to draw and paint?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you always know how to draw and paint?",
    "answer": "i was taught in high school how to draw and paint."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was taught in high school how to draw and paint.",
    "answer": "you had an art class?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you had an art class?",
    "answer": "exactly, it was my favorite class."
  },
  {
    "question": "exactly, it was my favorite class.",
    "answer": "well, it's good that you're so talented."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's good that you're so talented.",
    "answer": "i appreciate that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i appreciate that.",
    "answer": "talent is a great thing, i wish i had one."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's your favorite movie?",
    "answer": "my favorite movie is superbad."
  },
  {
    "question": "my favorite movie is superbad.",
    "answer": "oh, why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, why is that?",
    "answer": "it's the funniest movie that i've ever seen."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the funniest movie that i've ever seen.",
    "answer": "that's true. it is a very funny movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's true. it is a very funny movie.",
    "answer": "you've seen it before?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you've seen it before?",
    "answer": "yes, i saw that movie the first day it came out in theaters."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i saw that movie the first day it came out in theaters.",
    "answer": "didn't you laugh through the whole movie? i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "didn't you laugh through the whole movie? i did.",
    "answer": "me too. that movie brought tears to my eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. that movie brought tears to my eyes.",
    "answer": "mine too."
  },
  {
    "question": "mine too.",
    "answer": "i have it on dvd at my house if you want to come over and watch it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have it on dvd at my house if you want to come over and watch it.",
    "answer": "sure, let's go."
  },
  {
    "question": "which movie is your favorite to watch?",
    "answer": "i have to say, my favorite movie is superbad."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to say, my favorite movie is superbad.",
    "answer": "is that right? why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right? why?",
    "answer": "honestly, it is one of the funniest movies i've seen in a long time."
  },
  {
    "question": "honestly, it is one of the funniest movies i've seen in a long time.",
    "answer": "you're right. that movie is hilarious."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. that movie is hilarious.",
    "answer": "i didn't think you saw that movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't think you saw that movie.",
    "answer": "i went to see it the day it came out."
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to see it the day it came out.",
    "answer": "i was laughing through the whole movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was laughing through the whole movie.",
    "answer": "i couldn't help laughing, either."
  },
  {
    "question": "i couldn't help laughing, either.",
    "answer": "same here."
  },
  {
    "question": "same here.",
    "answer": "i bought the movie. would you like to come to my house and watch it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought the movie. would you like to come to my house and watch it?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "out of every movie that you've seen, which one is your favorite?",
    "answer": "i'm going to have to say that superbad is the best movie ever."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to have to say that superbad is the best movie ever.",
    "answer": "you think so, how come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you think so, how come?",
    "answer": "well, superbad is super funny."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, superbad is super funny.",
    "answer": "you're not lying, i found that movie absolutely hilarious."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're not lying, i found that movie absolutely hilarious.",
    "answer": "i didn't know that you saw superbad before."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't know that you saw superbad before.",
    "answer": "i made sure to be in line to see it the first day it came out."
  },
  {
    "question": "i made sure to be in line to see it the first day it came out.",
    "answer": "i couldn't keep from laughing throughout the whole movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "i couldn't keep from laughing throughout the whole movie.",
    "answer": "i was laughing hysterically the whole time; my stomach muscles hurt afterwards."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was laughing hysterically the whole time; my stomach muscles hurt afterwards.",
    "answer": "that's exactly how i felt."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's exactly how i felt.",
    "answer": "i got the movie when it came out on dvd, do you want to come over?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what type of music do you like to listen to?",
    "answer": "i like listening to different kinds of music."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like listening to different kinds of music.",
    "answer": "like what, for instance?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what, for instance?",
    "answer": "i enjoy rock and r&b."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy rock and r&b.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "i like the different instruments that they use."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the different instruments that they use.",
    "answer": "that's a good reason to like something."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good reason to like something.",
    "answer": "yeah, i think so too."
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of music do you enjoy listening to?",
    "answer": "i enjoy listening to all kinds of music."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy listening to all kinds of music.",
    "answer": "what kind?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind?",
    "answer": "i like to listen to rock and r&b."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to listen to rock and r&b.",
    "answer": "why do you like that type of music?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you like that type of music?",
    "answer": "i like the kinds of instruments that they use."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the kinds of instruments that they use.",
    "answer": "i think that's an excellent reason to like something."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that's an excellent reason to like something.",
    "answer": "thanks, i feel the same way."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is your favorite kind of music?",
    "answer": "i listen to various types of music."
  },
  {
    "question": "i listen to various types of music.",
    "answer": "what genres?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what genres?",
    "answer": "i enjoy listening to both rock and r&b."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy listening to both rock and r&b.",
    "answer": "what interests you in that type of music?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what interests you in that type of music?",
    "answer": "i enjoy the different types of instruments that they use."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy the different types of instruments that they use.",
    "answer": "that is a perfect reason to like a certain kind of music."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you go to the basketball game on friday?",
    "answer": "no, i couldn't make it."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i couldn't make it.",
    "answer": "you missed a really good game."
  },
  {
    "question": "you missed a really good game.",
    "answer": "oh, really? who won?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, really? who won?",
    "answer": "our school did. they played really well."
  },
  {
    "question": "our school did. they played really well.",
    "answer": "too bad i was busy. i really wanted to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "too bad i was busy. i really wanted to go.",
    "answer": "yeah, you should have. it was really exciting."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, you should have. it was really exciting.",
    "answer": "so what was the score?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what was the score?",
    "answer": "the score was 101-98."
  },
  {
    "question": "the score was 101-98.",
    "answer": "man, that was a really close game."
  },
  {
    "question": "man, that was a really close game.",
    "answer": "that's what made it so great."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what made it so great.",
    "answer": "i'll make sure and make it to the next one."
  },
  {
    "question": "were you able to attend friday night's basketball game?",
    "answer": "i was unable to make it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was unable to make it.",
    "answer": "you should have been there. it was intense."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should have been there. it was intense.",
    "answer": "is that right. who ended up winning?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right. who ended up winning?",
    "answer": "our team was victorious."
  },
  {
    "question": "our team was victorious.",
    "answer": "i wish i was free that night. i'm kind of mad that i didn't go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i was free that night. i'm kind of mad that i didn't go.",
    "answer": "it was a great game."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was a great game.",
    "answer": "what was the score at the end of the game?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the score at the end of the game?",
    "answer": "our team won 101-98."
  },
  {
    "question": "our team won 101-98.",
    "answer": "sounds like it was a close game."
  },
  {
    "question": "sounds like it was a close game.",
    "answer": "that's the reason it was such a great game."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's the reason it was such a great game.",
    "answer": "the next game, i will definitely be there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was meaning to ask you if you saw the basketball game on friday.",
    "answer": "i wanted to go, but i couldn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wanted to go, but i couldn't.",
    "answer": "it was a great game."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was a great game.",
    "answer": "it's too bad that i couldn't make it. who won?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's too bad that i couldn't make it. who won?",
    "answer": "our team played hard and won."
  },
  {
    "question": "our team played hard and won.",
    "answer": "i really wish i went to the game."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really wish i went to the game.",
    "answer": "it was the best game ever."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was the best game ever.",
    "answer": "so tell me the final score."
  },
  {
    "question": "so tell me the final score.",
    "answer": "the other team lost by three points, 101-98."
  },
  {
    "question": "the other team lost by three points, 101-98.",
    "answer": "it must've been a close game."
  },
  {
    "question": "it must've been a close game.",
    "answer": "it really was. you should've gone."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you doing this weekend?",
    "answer": "i'm going to the movies with a friend. how about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to the movies with a friend. how about you?",
    "answer": "i'm not sure yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sure yet.",
    "answer": "well, did you want to go see a movie with me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, did you want to go see a movie with me?",
    "answer": "what movie are you going to see?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what movie are you going to see?",
    "answer": "i'm not sure yet. is there something you want to see?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sure yet. is there something you want to see?",
    "answer": "there's nothing i can think of."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's nothing i can think of.",
    "answer": "so, did you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so, did you want to go?",
    "answer": "no, thanks, maybe another time."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, thanks, maybe another time.",
    "answer": "okay, sounds good."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know what you're going to do this weekend?",
    "answer": "i am going to see a movie with a friend of mine. what about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i am going to see a movie with a friend of mine. what about you?",
    "answer": "i don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know.",
    "answer": "would you like to see a movie with me and my friend?"
  },
  {
    "question": "would you like to see a movie with me and my friend?",
    "answer": "do you know what movie you're going to watch?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know what movie you're going to watch?",
    "answer": "i don't know, but was there a certain movie you wanted to see?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know, but was there a certain movie you wanted to see?",
    "answer": "none that i can think of."
  },
  {
    "question": "none that i can think of.",
    "answer": "well, would you like to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, would you like to go?",
    "answer": "thank you for inviting me, but i think i'll pass."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you for inviting me, but i think i'll pass.",
    "answer": "all right. another time then."
  },
  {
    "question": "you have any ideas as to what you want to do this weekend?",
    "answer": "i'm going to the movie theater with my friend. what are you going to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to the movie theater with my friend. what are you going to do?",
    "answer": "i'm not quite sure yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not quite sure yet.",
    "answer": "how about you see a movie with me and my friend?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about you see a movie with me and my friend?",
    "answer": "what movie are you and your friend planning on watching?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what movie are you and your friend planning on watching?",
    "answer": "not sure. is there a movie out that catches your eye?"
  },
  {
    "question": "not sure. is there a movie out that catches your eye?",
    "answer": "no good movies come to mind."
  },
  {
    "question": "no good movies come to mind.",
    "answer": "have you decided whether or not you would like to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you decided whether or not you would like to go?",
    "answer": "no, thanks. maybe another time."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you go to school today?",
    "answer": "yeah, i went to school today. were you there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, i went to school today. were you there?",
    "answer": "no, i didn't go, i've been sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i didn't go, i've been sick.",
    "answer": "that sucks. did you want the assignments from english class?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that sucks. did you want the assignments from english class?",
    "answer": "that would be nice, thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "that would be nice, thank you.",
    "answer": "no problem, you're welcome."
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem, you're welcome.",
    "answer": "i will be glad to do the same for you when you're sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will be glad to do the same for you when you're sick.",
    "answer": "well, thank you. i hope to see you at school tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you attended school today?",
    "answer": "i attended school today. did you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i attended school today. did you?",
    "answer": "i wasn't able to attend school because i was feeling ill."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wasn't able to attend school because i was feeling ill.",
    "answer": "i'm sorry to hear that. would you like the assignments from english class?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sorry to hear that. would you like the assignments from english class?",
    "answer": "i would really appreciate that, thanks."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would really appreciate that, thanks.",
    "answer": "it's no trouble at all."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's no trouble at all.",
    "answer": "if you get sick, i'll return the favor."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you get sick, i'll return the favor.",
    "answer": "thanks. see you at school tomorrow if you feel better."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you gone to school today?",
    "answer": "i went to school today. did you go to school?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to school today. did you go to school?",
    "answer": "i couldn't go to school today, i was sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "i couldn't go to school today, i was sick.",
    "answer": "that's horrible. i'd be happy to give you the assignments from english class."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's horrible. i'd be happy to give you the assignments from english class.",
    "answer": "thank you very much, that's kind of you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you very much, that's kind of you.",
    "answer": "don't mention it."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't mention it.",
    "answer": "when you miss a day of school, i'll be happy to give you the english assignments."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear the news?",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "our cousin went into labor and had her baby last week."
  },
  {
    "question": "our cousin went into labor and had her baby last week.",
    "answer": "she did? why didn't anyone tell me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "she did? why didn't anyone tell me?",
    "answer": "i would've thought that somebody would have told you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would've thought that somebody would have told you.",
    "answer": "no, i had no idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i had no idea.",
    "answer": "well, she did, her baby was 8 pounds 6 ounces."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, she did, her baby was 8 pounds 6 ounces.",
    "answer": "oh my god, that's great!"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh my god, that's great!",
    "answer": "are you going to go and visit her and the baby?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to go and visit her and the baby?",
    "answer": "i think that i might."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that i might.",
    "answer": "good! i just thought i'd let you know."
  },
  {
    "question": "good! i just thought i'd let you know.",
    "answer": "thanks for telling me."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard what happened?",
    "answer": "heard what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "heard what?",
    "answer": "debrah already had her baby."
  },
  {
    "question": "debrah already had her baby.",
    "answer": "i didn't know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't know that.",
    "answer": "i thought you knew."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought you knew.",
    "answer": "i honestly didn't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i honestly didn't know.",
    "answer": "the baby was 8 pounds 6 ounces."
  },
  {
    "question": "the baby was 8 pounds 6 ounces.",
    "answer": "that's good to hear."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's good to hear.",
    "answer": "will you go and visit them?"
  },
  {
    "question": "will you go and visit them?",
    "answer": "of course i will."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course i will.",
    "answer": "i just wanted to give you the good news."
  },
  {
    "question": "i just wanted to give you the good news.",
    "answer": "thanks for letting me know."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard the news?",
    "answer": "i haven't heard anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't heard anything.",
    "answer": "debrah had her baby last week."
  },
  {
    "question": "debrah had her baby last week.",
    "answer": "nobody told me."
  },
  {
    "question": "nobody told me.",
    "answer": "i thought you heard."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought you heard.",
    "answer": "i really wasn't told anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really wasn't told anything.",
    "answer": "she was a cute 8 pounds 6 ounces."
  },
  {
    "question": "she was a cute 8 pounds 6 ounces.",
    "answer": "wow, how exciting."
  },
  {
    "question": "wow, how exciting.",
    "answer": "i know, you should really go and see her and the baby."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know, you should really go and see her and the baby.",
    "answer": "of course i will."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course i will.",
    "answer": "i just wanted to let you know what happened."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you go to school today?",
    "answer": "of course. did you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. did you?",
    "answer": "i didn't want to, so i didn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't want to, so i didn't.",
    "answer": "that's sad, but have you gone to the movies recently?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's sad, but have you gone to the movies recently?",
    "answer": "that's a switch."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a switch.",
    "answer": "i'm serious, have you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm serious, have you?",
    "answer": "no, i haven't. why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i haven't. why?",
    "answer": "i really want to go to the movies this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really want to go to the movies this weekend.",
    "answer": "so go then."
  },
  {
    "question": "so go then.",
    "answer": "i really don't want to go by myself."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really don't want to go by myself.",
    "answer": "well anyway, do you plan on going to school tomorrow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well anyway, do you plan on going to school tomorrow?",
    "answer": "no, i think i'm going to go to the movies."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you make it to school today?",
    "answer": "i always do. did you go to school today?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i always do. did you go to school today?",
    "answer": "no, i didn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i didn't.",
    "answer": "you should have, but have you seen any movies lately?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you should have, but have you seen any movies lately?",
    "answer": "that was an odd change of subject."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was an odd change of subject.",
    "answer": "maybe it was, but answer the question."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe it was, but answer the question.",
    "answer": "no, not recently."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, not recently.",
    "answer": "i want to go to see a movie this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to go to see a movie this weekend.",
    "answer": "what's stopping you then?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's stopping you then?",
    "answer": "i don't want to go alone."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want to go alone.",
    "answer": "so, will you be at school tomorrow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so, will you be at school tomorrow?",
    "answer": "no, i want to go to the movies instead."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you even bother to go to school today?",
    "answer": "yeah, i went. did you go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, i went. did you go?",
    "answer": "no, i didn't feel like it."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i didn't feel like it.",
    "answer": "that's nice, have you been to the movies lately?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's nice, have you been to the movies lately?",
    "answer": "no, but that was a random change of subject."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, but that was a random change of subject.",
    "answer": "it may have been random, but have you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it may have been random, but have you?",
    "answer": "i haven't lately."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't lately.",
    "answer": "i would love to catch a movie this weekend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would love to catch a movie this weekend.",
    "answer": "so then, why don't you just go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so then, why don't you just go?",
    "answer": "i don't want to see a movie by myself."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want to see a movie by myself.",
    "answer": "okay, so are you going to school tomorrow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks for coming to see me today.",
    "answer": "it's no problem. i was really missing you anyway."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's no problem. i was really missing you anyway.",
    "answer": "i missed you too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i missed you too.",
    "answer": "why haven't you tried to come see me then?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why haven't you tried to come see me then?",
    "answer": "i've been really busy."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been really busy.",
    "answer": "doing what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "doing what?",
    "answer": "working."
  },
  {
    "question": "working.",
    "answer": "i would've come to see you sooner, but i've been busy too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would've come to see you sooner, but i've been busy too.",
    "answer": "what have you been doing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what have you been doing?",
    "answer": "i've been working too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been working too.",
    "answer": "well regardless, i'm very happy that you came to see me."
  },
  {
    "question": "well regardless, i'm very happy that you came to see me.",
    "answer": "i am too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm really glad that you came to see me.",
    "answer": "i had to. i was missing you a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had to. i was missing you a lot.",
    "answer": "i was missing you too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was missing you too.",
    "answer": "so, why haven't you visited me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so, why haven't you visited me?",
    "answer": "i've actually been busy lately."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've actually been busy lately.",
    "answer": "what have you been doing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what have you been doing?",
    "answer": "i've just been working really hard."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've just been working really hard.",
    "answer": "i've also been busy."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've also been busy.",
    "answer": "tell me what you've been doing."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me what you've been doing.",
    "answer": "basically, i've been working too."
  },
  {
    "question": "basically, i've been working too.",
    "answer": "well whatever, i'm glad you came."
  },
  {
    "question": "well whatever, i'm glad you came.",
    "answer": "so am i."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm really happy that you came to visit me.",
    "answer": "i really missed you a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really missed you a lot.",
    "answer": "i've been missing you like crazy."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been missing you like crazy.",
    "answer": "i don't understand why you haven't come to visit me."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't understand why you haven't come to visit me.",
    "answer": "lately, i've been quite busy."
  },
  {
    "question": "lately, i've been quite busy.",
    "answer": "tell me what you've been up to."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me what you've been up to.",
    "answer": "i've really been working a lot lately."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've really been working a lot lately.",
    "answer": "i've been pretty busy myself."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been pretty busy myself.",
    "answer": "so what have you been up to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what have you been up to?",
    "answer": "i've just been working a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've just been working a lot.",
    "answer": "whatever the reason may be, i'm glad you visited me."
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, did you hear about jessica's party this weekend?",
    "answer": "yeah, but i'm still waiting for my invitation."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, but i'm still waiting for my invitation.",
    "answer": "oh really? she gave me mine earlier today."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh really? she gave me mine earlier today.",
    "answer": "well, she'll probably just give me my invitation later on today."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, she'll probably just give me my invitation later on today.",
    "answer": "yeah, so are you planning on going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, so are you planning on going?",
    "answer": "i think so. it sounds like it's going to be a lot of fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think so. it sounds like it's going to be a lot of fun.",
    "answer": "it really does, i can't wait."
  },
  {
    "question": "it really does, i can't wait.",
    "answer": "what time does the party start?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time does the party start?",
    "answer": "it starts at 8 o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "it starts at 8 o'clock.",
    "answer": "oh, well, how many people has she given invites to so far?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, well, how many people has she given invites to so far?",
    "answer": "i'm not sure, but i don't think she's given out that many."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sure, but i don't think she's given out that many.",
    "answer": "well, hopefully she'll give me my invite later on today."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard about jessica's party on saturday?",
    "answer": "i've heard about it, but i'm still waiting for my invitation."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've heard about it, but i'm still waiting for my invitation.",
    "answer": "really? i got mine from her this morning."
  },
  {
    "question": "really? i got mine from her this morning.",
    "answer": "i'm guessing that she's going to give me my invite today or tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm guessing that she's going to give me my invite today or tomorrow.",
    "answer": "you're probably right, do you intend on going to the party?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you're probably right, do you intend on going to the party?",
    "answer": "i want to. i heard it's going to be really fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to. i heard it's going to be really fun.",
    "answer": "i know, it does sound pretty awesome."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know, it does sound pretty awesome.",
    "answer": "well, when does the party start?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, when does the party start?",
    "answer": "it's supposed to start at about eight."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's supposed to start at about eight.",
    "answer": "how many invitations has she given out?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many invitations has she given out?",
    "answer": "i really don't know, but i don't think she gave out that many yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really don't know, but i don't think she gave out that many yet.",
    "answer": "i really want to go, so i hope that she gives me my invite soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "has anyone told you about jessica's party coming up?",
    "answer": "i was told about it already. i'm just waiting for my invitation."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was told about it already. i'm just waiting for my invitation.",
    "answer": "is that right? i already got my invitation from her earlier."
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right? i already got my invitation from her earlier.",
    "answer": "i believe that she will give me the invitation today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i believe that she will give me the invitation today.",
    "answer": "are you even going to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you even going to go?",
    "answer": "yeah, it sounds like it's going to be the best party of the year."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, it sounds like it's going to be the best party of the year.",
    "answer": "exactly, it seems like it's going to be loads of fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "exactly, it seems like it's going to be loads of fun.",
    "answer": "when exactly does the party start?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when exactly does the party start?",
    "answer": "the invitation says it starts at 8:00 p.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "the invitation says it starts at 8:00 p.m.",
    "answer": "has she given out a lot of invitations yet?"
  },
  {
    "question": "has she given out a lot of invitations yet?",
    "answer": "i have no idea, she hasn't given out many though."
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, what's up?",
    "answer": "nothing really."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing really.",
    "answer": "i'm throwing a party on friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm throwing a party on friday.",
    "answer": "i didn't realize that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't realize that.",
    "answer": "you didn't?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you didn't?",
    "answer": "nobody has told me anything about your party."
  },
  {
    "question": "nobody has told me anything about your party.",
    "answer": "did you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you want to go?",
    "answer": "when does it start?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when does it start?",
    "answer": "at 8:00 p.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "at 8:00 p.m.",
    "answer": "i'll be there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll be there.",
    "answer": "i'd better see you there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd better see you there.",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's going on with you?",
    "answer": "fine. what's going on with you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "fine. what's going on with you?",
    "answer": "i'm having a party this friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm having a party this friday.",
    "answer": "i had no idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had no idea.",
    "answer": "is that right?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right?",
    "answer": "i didn't hear anything about it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't hear anything about it.",
    "answer": "can you go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can you go?",
    "answer": "what time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time?",
    "answer": "it starts at 8 o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "it starts at 8 o'clock.",
    "answer": "i'll go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll go.",
    "answer": "i hope that i'll see you there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope that i'll see you there.",
    "answer": "no doubt."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's going on?",
    "answer": "not much."
  },
  {
    "question": "not much.",
    "answer": "this friday, i'm throwing a party."
  },
  {
    "question": "this friday, i'm throwing a party.",
    "answer": "oh really? i didn't know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh really? i didn't know that.",
    "answer": "are you serious?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you serious?",
    "answer": "i haven't heard anything about it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't heard anything about it.",
    "answer": "can you make it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can you make it?",
    "answer": "what time does it start?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time does it start?",
    "answer": "the party starts at 8."
  },
  {
    "question": "the party starts at 8.",
    "answer": "yeah, i think i'll go."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, i think i'll go.",
    "answer": "am i going to see you there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's going on?",
    "answer": "nothing really, you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing really, you?",
    "answer": "i'm throwing a party next saturday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm throwing a party next saturday.",
    "answer": "is that right?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that right?",
    "answer": "yeah, are you going to come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, are you going to come?",
    "answer": "i'm sorry, i can't."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sorry, i can't.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "i don't really want to."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't really want to.",
    "answer": "well, why don't you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, why don't you?",
    "answer": "i hate going to parties."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate going to parties.",
    "answer": "well, that's okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, that's okay.",
    "answer": "yeah, sorry."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's up?",
    "answer": "nothing, how about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing, how about you?",
    "answer": "next saturday, i'm going to have a party."
  },
  {
    "question": "next saturday, i'm going to have a party.",
    "answer": "oh, really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, really?",
    "answer": "you are coming?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you are coming?",
    "answer": "probably not."
  },
  {
    "question": "probably not.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "i don't feel like going."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't feel like going.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "i really can't stand going to parties."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really can't stand going to parties.",
    "answer": "i understand, i guess."
  },
  {
    "question": "i understand, i guess.",
    "answer": "sorry about that."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's happening?",
    "answer": "not a lot, what about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "not a lot, what about you?",
    "answer": "i'm having a party next saturday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm having a party next saturday.",
    "answer": "that's nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's nice.",
    "answer": "are you going to be there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to be there?",
    "answer": "i don't think so."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't think so.",
    "answer": "is there a reason why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is there a reason why?",
    "answer": "i just really don't want to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i just really don't want to go.",
    "answer": "how come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how come?",
    "answer": "i don't really like parties."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't really like parties.",
    "answer": "i wish you would go, but that's okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's up?",
    "answer": "nothing much, what's going on?"
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing much, what's going on?",
    "answer": "i'm having a party this friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm having a party this friday.",
    "answer": "oh, really? that's nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, really? that's nice.",
    "answer": "i wanted to see if you wanted to come."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wanted to see if you wanted to come.",
    "answer": "this friday? sorry, i already have plans."
  },
  {
    "question": "this friday? sorry, i already have plans.",
    "answer": "doing what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "doing what?",
    "answer": "i'm going to dinner with my family."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to dinner with my family.",
    "answer": "i really wanted you to come, but i understand."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really wanted you to come, but i understand.",
    "answer": "yeah, maybe next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, maybe next time.",
    "answer": "i'll hold you to that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll hold you to that.",
    "answer": "sounds like a plan."
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, what's good with you?",
    "answer": "not a lot. what about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "not a lot. what about you?",
    "answer": "i'm throwing a party on friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm throwing a party on friday.",
    "answer": "that sounds like fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like fun.",
    "answer": "do you think you can come?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think you can come?",
    "answer": "i'm sorry. i'm already doing something this friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sorry. i'm already doing something this friday.",
    "answer": "what are you going to be doing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to be doing?",
    "answer": "my family and i are going to dinner."
  },
  {
    "question": "my family and i are going to dinner.",
    "answer": "i was hoping you would come."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was hoping you would come.",
    "answer": "i'll definitely try to make it the next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll definitely try to make it the next time.",
    "answer": "i'd better see you there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd better see you there.",
    "answer": "all right. i'll see you next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's going on?",
    "answer": "nothing really. how about you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing really. how about you?",
    "answer": "a lot, like the party i'm having on friday."
  },
  {
    "question": "a lot, like the party i'm having on friday.",
    "answer": "well, that's cool."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, that's cool.",
    "answer": "will you be able to make it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "will you be able to make it?",
    "answer": "i'm busy this friday. i'm sorry."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm busy this friday. i'm sorry.",
    "answer": "what do you have to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you have to do?",
    "answer": "i'm having dinner with my family"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm having dinner with my family",
    "answer": "maybe you can come next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you can come next time.",
    "answer": "i'll make sure and come to your next party."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll make sure and come to your next party.",
    "answer": "i'll look for you at my next party."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was nice talking to you.",
    "answer": "why are you trying to rush me off the phone?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why are you trying to rush me off the phone?",
    "answer": "i really have to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really have to go.",
    "answer": "why? i still wanted to talk to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "why? i still wanted to talk to you.",
    "answer": "i have things to do."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have things to do.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "don't be nosey."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't be nosey.",
    "answer": "i'm not. i just want to know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not. i just want to know.",
    "answer": "well, it's really none of your business."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's really none of your business.",
    "answer": "that's harsh."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's harsh.",
    "answer": "i'm sorry, but i have to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sorry, but i have to go.",
    "answer": "fine."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've enjoyed conversing with you.",
    "answer": "is there a reason why you're trying to get off the phone so fast?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is there a reason why you're trying to get off the phone so fast?",
    "answer": "i've got to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've got to go.",
    "answer": "i wasn't done talking to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wasn't done talking to you.",
    "answer": "i have to do some things, and besides, it's not polite to be nosey."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to do some things, and besides, it's not polite to be nosey.",
    "answer": "i'm not being nosey. i'm just asking."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not being nosey. i'm just asking.",
    "answer": "i really don't think it's any of your business."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really don't think it's any of your business.",
    "answer": "that's not nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not nice.",
    "answer": "i apologize, but i'm getting off the phone now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i apologize, but i'm getting off the phone now.",
    "answer": "okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll talk to you later.",
    "answer": "what's the rush?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the rush?",
    "answer": "i have to get off the phone now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to get off the phone now.",
    "answer": "i'm not ready to get off the phone with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not ready to get off the phone with you.",
    "answer": "there are other things i need to take care of."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are other things i need to take care of.",
    "answer": "what is it that you need to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is it that you need to do?",
    "answer": "please don't be nosey."
  },
  {
    "question": "please don't be nosey.",
    "answer": "i'm not being nosey, it's just a question."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not being nosey, it's just a question.",
    "answer": "you don't need to worry about that."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't need to worry about that.",
    "answer": "that was mean to say."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was mean to say.",
    "answer": "i am very sorry, but i must go."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it was nice talking to you.",
    "answer": "it was nice talking to you too."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was nice talking to you too.",
    "answer": "we should really hang out again."
  },
  {
    "question": "we should really hang out again.",
    "answer": "that would be fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "that would be fun.",
    "answer": "where do you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you want to go?",
    "answer": "i think we should go out to eat."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think we should go out to eat.",
    "answer": "that sounds good."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds good.",
    "answer": "all right, so i'll see you then."
  },
  {
    "question": "all right, so i'll see you then.",
    "answer": "i'll call you later."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll call you later.",
    "answer": "okay, i'll talk to you later then."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, i'll talk to you later then.",
    "answer": "see you later."
  },
  {
    "question": "see you later.",
    "answer": "bye."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoyed talking to you.",
    "answer": "i enjoyed talking to you too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoyed talking to you too.",
    "answer": "we should hang out some time."
  },
  {
    "question": "we should hang out some time.",
    "answer": "i think that would be nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think that would be nice.",
    "answer": "is there anything you would like to do next time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is there anything you would like to do next time?",
    "answer": "do you want to go out to eat?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you want to go out to eat?",
    "answer": "i'd like that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd like that.",
    "answer": "so i'll see you next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "so i'll see you next time.",
    "answer": "i'm going to call you soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to call you soon.",
    "answer": "i'll talk to you later."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll talk to you later.",
    "answer": "see you soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "see you soon.",
    "answer": "goodbye."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had fun talking to you.",
    "answer": "it was really nice talking to you also."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was really nice talking to you also.",
    "answer": "i think we should really do something sometime."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think we should really do something sometime.",
    "answer": "that should be loads of fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "that should be loads of fun.",
    "answer": "what do you want to do next time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you want to do next time?",
    "answer": "would you like to go to dinner or something?"
  },
  {
    "question": "would you like to go to dinner or something?",
    "answer": "yeah, let's do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah, let's do that.",
    "answer": "okay, until next time then."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, until next time then.",
    "answer": "i'll call you so we can set that up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll call you so we can set that up.",
    "answer": "talk to you then."
  },
  {
    "question": "talk to you then.",
    "answer": "all right, see you."
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you live?",
    "answer": "i live in pasadena."
  },
  {
    "question": "i live in pasadena.",
    "answer": "where is pasadena?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where is pasadena?",
    "answer": "it's in california."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's in california.",
    "answer": "is it in northern california?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it in northern california?",
    "answer": "no. it's in southern california."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. it's in southern california.",
    "answer": "is pasadena a big city?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is pasadena a big city?",
    "answer": "it's pretty big."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's pretty big.",
    "answer": "how big is \"pretty big\"?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how big is \"pretty big\"?",
    "answer": "it has about 140,000 people."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has about 140,000 people.",
    "answer": "how big is los angeles?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how big is los angeles?",
    "answer": "it has about 3 million people."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you have a car?",
    "answer": "yes, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i do.",
    "answer": "what kind of car do you have?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of car do you have?",
    "answer": "i have a honda."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have a honda.",
    "answer": "is it new?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it new?",
    "answer": "it was new in 2003."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was new in 2003.",
    "answer": "so, it's pretty old now."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, it's pretty old now.",
    "answer": "yes, it is. but it still looks good."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it is. but it still looks good.",
    "answer": "do you take good care of it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you take good care of it?",
    "answer": "oh, yes. i wash it once a week."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes. i wash it once a week.",
    "answer": "do you change the oil?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you change the oil?",
    "answer": "my mechanic changes the oil twice a year."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you have a girlfriend?",
    "answer": "no, i don't. do you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i don't. do you?",
    "answer": "i don't have a girlfriend, either."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have a girlfriend, either.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "i don't know. maybe i'm not rich enough."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. maybe i'm not rich enough.",
    "answer": "girls like guys with money."
  },
  {
    "question": "girls like guys with money.",
    "answer": "they sure do."
  },
  {
    "question": "they sure do.",
    "answer": "they like guys with new cars."
  },
  {
    "question": "they like guys with new cars.",
    "answer": "i don't have money or a new car."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have money or a new car.",
    "answer": "me, neither."
  },
  {
    "question": "me, neither.",
    "answer": "but girls like guys who are funny."
  },
  {
    "question": "but girls like guys who are funny.",
    "answer": "maybe we should learn some good jokes."
  },
  {
    "question": "where are you going?",
    "answer": "i have to walk the dog."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to walk the dog.",
    "answer": "what kind of dog do you have?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of dog do you have?",
    "answer": "i have a little poodle."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have a little poodle.",
    "answer": "poodles bark a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "poodles bark a lot.",
    "answer": "they sure do."
  },
  {
    "question": "they sure do.",
    "answer": "they bark at everything."
  },
  {
    "question": "they bark at everything.",
    "answer": "they never shut up."
  },
  {
    "question": "they never shut up.",
    "answer": "why did you get a poodle?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did you get a poodle?",
    "answer": "it's my mom's dog."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's my mom's dog.",
    "answer": "so she likes poodles."
  },
  {
    "question": "so she likes poodles.",
    "answer": "she says they're good watchdogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "can i borrow $5?",
    "answer": "sure. why do you need it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure. why do you need it?",
    "answer": "i want to buy lunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to buy lunch.",
    "answer": "where's your money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where's your money?",
    "answer": "it's not in my wallet."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not in my wallet.",
    "answer": "your wallet is empty?"
  },
  {
    "question": "your wallet is empty?",
    "answer": "i don't have even one dollar in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have even one dollar in it.",
    "answer": "being broke is no fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "being broke is no fun.",
    "answer": "even if it's only for a short while."
  },
  {
    "question": "even if it's only for a short while.",
    "answer": "it's always good to have friends."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's always good to have friends.",
    "answer": "friends will lend you money when you're broke."
  },
  {
    "question": "friends will lend you money when you're broke.",
    "answer": "as long as you pay them back."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to the beach.",
    "answer": "that's a great idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a great idea.",
    "answer": "we haven't been in a while."
  },
  {
    "question": "we haven't been in a while.",
    "answer": "we haven't been in a month."
  },
  {
    "question": "we haven't been in a month.",
    "answer": "the last time we went, you almost drowned."
  },
  {
    "question": "the last time we went, you almost drowned.",
    "answer": "no, i didn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i didn't.",
    "answer": "then why did the lifeguard dive into the water?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why did the lifeguard dive into the water?",
    "answer": "i think he wanted to cool off."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think he wanted to cool off.",
    "answer": "he swam right up to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "he swam right up to you.",
    "answer": "and then he turned right around."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then he turned right around.",
    "answer": "maybe you're right."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you're right.",
    "answer": "maybe we should get going."
  },
  {
    "question": "are you married?",
    "answer": "no. i'm divorced."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. i'm divorced.",
    "answer": "when did you get divorced?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when did you get divorced?",
    "answer": "i got divorced two years ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got divorced two years ago.",
    "answer": "why did you get divorced?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did you get divorced?",
    "answer": "my wife left me."
  },
  {
    "question": "my wife left me.",
    "answer": "why did she leave you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did she leave you?",
    "answer": "she said she didn't love me anymore."
  },
  {
    "question": "she said she didn't love me anymore.",
    "answer": "wow! that's terrible."
  },
  {
    "question": "wow! that's terrible.",
    "answer": "yes, it was."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it was.",
    "answer": "why didn't she love you anymore?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why didn't she love you anymore?",
    "answer": "she fell in love with my best friend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm bored.",
    "answer": "what's on tv?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's on tv?",
    "answer": "nothing."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing.",
    "answer": "there must be something on tv!"
  },
  {
    "question": "there must be something on tv!",
    "answer": "nothing that's interesting."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing that's interesting.",
    "answer": "what about that new game show?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about that new game show?",
    "answer": "which one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "which one?",
    "answer": "deal or no deal"
  },
  {
    "question": "deal or no deal",
    "answer": "tell me you're joking."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me you're joking.",
    "answer": "i love that show."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love that show.",
    "answer": "i watched it once. that was enough."
  },
  {
    "question": "i watched it once. that was enough.",
    "answer": "it's on right now. let's watch it together."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like living here.",
    "answer": "i agree. pasadena is a nice city."
  },
  {
    "question": "i agree. pasadena is a nice city.",
    "answer": "it's not too big."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not too big.",
    "answer": "and it's not too small."
  },
  {
    "question": "and it's not too small.",
    "answer": "it has great weather all year long."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has great weather all year long.",
    "answer": "it has the rose parade."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has the rose parade.",
    "answer": "it has beautiful houses."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has beautiful houses.",
    "answer": "it has wonderful restaurants."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has wonderful restaurants.",
    "answer": "it has great schools."
  },
  {
    "question": "it has great schools.",
    "answer": "it's close to the mountains."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's close to the mountains.",
    "answer": "the people are friendly."
  },
  {
    "question": "the people are friendly.",
    "answer": "i'm not ever going to leave."
  },
  {
    "question": "we need a new mattress.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with this one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with this one?",
    "answer": "it's not comfortable."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not comfortable.",
    "answer": "it seems fine to me."
  },
  {
    "question": "it seems fine to me.",
    "answer": "i toss and turn all night."
  },
  {
    "question": "i toss and turn all night.",
    "answer": "you should stop drinking coffee."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should stop drinking coffee.",
    "answer": "look at these marks on my arms."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at these marks on my arms.",
    "answer": "what are they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are they?",
    "answer": "they are bites."
  },
  {
    "question": "they are bites.",
    "answer": "did the cat bite you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did the cat bite you?",
    "answer": "no. the bedbugs in that mattress bit me."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. the bedbugs in that mattress bit me.",
    "answer": "okay. let's get a new mattress."
  },
  {
    "question": "my laptop is so slow.",
    "answer": "buy a new one."
  },
  {
    "question": "buy a new one.",
    "answer": "i would if i had the money."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would if i had the money.",
    "answer": "why is it so slow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is it so slow?",
    "answer": "that's a good question."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good question.",
    "answer": "did you take it to a computer shop?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you take it to a computer shop?",
    "answer": "i would if i had the money."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would if i had the money.",
    "answer": "well, i guess you have to live with it."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i guess you have to live with it.",
    "answer": "sometimes i want to throw it out the window."
  },
  {
    "question": "sometimes i want to throw it out the window.",
    "answer": "you don't want to do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't want to do that.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "you might hit someone in the head."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's for dinner?",
    "answer": "i'm not sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sure.",
    "answer": "how about a pizza?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about a pizza?",
    "answer": "you had pizza for lunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "you had pizza for lunch.",
    "answer": "but i love pizza."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i love pizza.",
    "answer": "everybody loves pizza."
  },
  {
    "question": "everybody loves pizza.",
    "answer": "so why can't i have pizza for dinner?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so why can't i have pizza for dinner?",
    "answer": "because you need variety."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you need variety.",
    "answer": "what's \"variety?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's \"variety?",
    "answer": "different thingsÂ—not the same thing all the time."
  },
  {
    "question": "different thingsÂ—not the same thing all the time.",
    "answer": "you mean, like a pepperoni pizza instead of a cheese pizza?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you mean, like a pepperoni pizza instead of a cheese pizza?",
    "answer": "no, i mean a salad instead of a pizza."
  },
  {
    "question": "we need to save money.",
    "answer": "why do we need to save money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do we need to save money?",
    "answer": "because we need to buy a house."
  },
  {
    "question": "because we need to buy a house.",
    "answer": "but a house is so expensive."
  },
  {
    "question": "but a house is so expensive.",
    "answer": "that's why we need to save money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's why we need to save money.",
    "answer": "how much do we need to save?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much do we need to save?",
    "answer": "we need to save enough for a down payment."
  },
  {
    "question": "we need to save enough for a down payment.",
    "answer": "how much is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much is that?",
    "answer": "that's about $30,000."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's about $30,000.",
    "answer": "thirty thousand dollars! that will take forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "thirty thousand dollars! that will take forever.",
    "answer": "not if we save every penny."
  },
  {
    "question": "not if we save every penny.",
    "answer": "okay. here's seven pennies."
  },
  {
    "question": "the ocean is so big.",
    "answer": "you can't see the end of it."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can't see the end of it.",
    "answer": "it goes on and on forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "it goes on and on forever.",
    "answer": "and it's deep, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "and it's deep, too.",
    "answer": "i think it's five miles deep."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it's five miles deep.",
    "answer": "are there fish at the bottom?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are there fish at the bottom?",
    "answer": "there are fish at the top and the bottom."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are fish at the top and the bottom.",
    "answer": "are there more fish or more people?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are there more fish or more people?",
    "answer": "i think there are more fish."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think there are more fish.",
    "answer": "i hope so. i love to eat fish."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm upset with my mom.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "i warned her about her new boyfriend. she didn't listen to me."
  },
  {
    "question": "i warned her about her new boyfriend. she didn't listen to me.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "i gave her $1,000 for her birthday. i told her to spend it on herself."
  },
  {
    "question": "i gave her $1,000 for her birthday. i told her to spend it on herself.",
    "answer": "that was very nice of you."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was very nice of you.",
    "answer": "i found out that she gave it to her new boyfriend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i found out that she gave it to her new boyfriend.",
    "answer": "why did she do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did she do that?",
    "answer": "he said he would buy her a nice ring."
  },
  {
    "question": "he said he would buy her a nice ring.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with that?",
    "answer": "he went to las vegas. he lost it all gambling."
  },
  {
    "question": "he went to las vegas. he lost it all gambling.",
    "answer": "i hope your mom broke up with him."
  },
  {
    "question": "do animals talk to each other?",
    "answer": "of course they talk to each other."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course they talk to each other.",
    "answer": "what do they talk about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do they talk about?",
    "answer": "they talk about other animals."
  },
  {
    "question": "they talk about other animals.",
    "answer": "what else do they talk about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what else do they talk about?",
    "answer": "they talk about food and the weather."
  },
  {
    "question": "they talk about food and the weather.",
    "answer": "do they talk about us?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do they talk about us?",
    "answer": "of course they talk about us."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course they talk about us.",
    "answer": "what do they say about us?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do they say about us?",
    "answer": "they say that we are funny-looking."
  },
  {
    "question": "they say that we are funny-looking.",
    "answer": "ha! we're not funny-looking; animals are funny-looking."
  },
  {
    "question": "ha! we're not funny-looking; animals are funny-looking.",
    "answer": "we're funny-looking because we wear clothes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to clean the house.",
    "answer": "yes, it's very dirty."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's very dirty.",
    "answer": "you can help me."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can help me.",
    "answer": "why me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why me?",
    "answer": "because you helped make it dirty."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you helped make it dirty.",
    "answer": "what do you want me to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you want me to do?",
    "answer": "i want you to clean the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want you to clean the bathroom.",
    "answer": "oh, that's easy."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, that's easy.",
    "answer": "clean the sink, the tub, the counter, and the toilet."
  },
  {
    "question": "clean the sink, the tub, the counter, and the toilet.",
    "answer": "that's a lot of work."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a lot of work.",
    "answer": "tell me when you finish."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me when you finish.",
    "answer": "i don't think so. you'll just give me more work."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're watching too much tv.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i mean you're wasting your life."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean you're wasting your life.",
    "answer": "i'm having fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm having fun.",
    "answer": "you're sitting there with your mouth open."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're sitting there with your mouth open.",
    "answer": "who cares?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who cares?",
    "answer": "i care. do something."
  },
  {
    "question": "i care. do something.",
    "answer": "okay. i did something."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i did something.",
    "answer": "what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do?",
    "answer": "i turned up the volume."
  },
  {
    "question": "i turned up the volume.",
    "answer": "that's not what i meant by \"do something."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not what i meant by \"do something.",
    "answer": "will you do something? leave me alone."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you write a letter to grandma?",
    "answer": "yes, i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did.",
    "answer": "did you tell her about school?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you tell her about school?",
    "answer": "i told her that school is fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i told her that school is fun.",
    "answer": "did you put the letter in an envelope?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you put the letter in an envelope?",
    "answer": "yes, and i sealed the envelope."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and i sealed the envelope.",
    "answer": "did you put a stamp on the envelope?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you put a stamp on the envelope?",
    "answer": "i couldn't find any stamps."
  },
  {
    "question": "i couldn't find any stamps.",
    "answer": "they're in the kitchen drawer."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're in the kitchen drawer.",
    "answer": "okay. i just put a stamp on the envelope."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i just put a stamp on the envelope.",
    "answer": "give me the envelope, and i'll mail it for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "give me the envelope, and i'll mail it for you.",
    "answer": "when is grandma going to learn about e-mail?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why are you yawning?",
    "answer": "i'm sleepy."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sleepy.",
    "answer": "why don't you go to bed?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why don't you go to bed?",
    "answer": "i want to watch this tv show."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to watch this tv show.",
    "answer": "maybe you should record it."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you should record it.",
    "answer": "the tape recorder is broken."
  },
  {
    "question": "the tape recorder is broken.",
    "answer": "then you should watch the rerun."
  },
  {
    "question": "then you should watch the rerun.",
    "answer": "why? i'm watching the original."
  },
  {
    "question": "why? i'm watching the original.",
    "answer": "but you'll be asleep in about one minute."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you'll be asleep in about one minute.",
    "answer": "i'm just yawning because the commercials are on."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm just yawning because the commercials are on.",
    "answer": "okay. i'll tell you how the show ends."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i'll tell you how the show ends.",
    "answer": "zzz."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's sunday.",
    "answer": "so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so?",
    "answer": "you know what that means."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know what that means.",
    "answer": "i forgot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i forgot.",
    "answer": "sunday means we go to church."
  },
  {
    "question": "sunday means we go to church.",
    "answer": "oh, yeah."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yeah.",
    "answer": "put on a coat and tie."
  },
  {
    "question": "put on a coat and tie.",
    "answer": "why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why?",
    "answer": "to show respect to god and others."
  },
  {
    "question": "to show respect to god and others.",
    "answer": "i'm glad sunday is only once a week."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm glad sunday is only once a week.",
    "answer": "i hope god didn't hear that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope god didn't hear that.",
    "answer": "he'll forgive me."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you feed the cat?",
    "answer": "i'll do that in a minute."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll do that in a minute.",
    "answer": "the cat is meowing. he's hungry."
  },
  {
    "question": "the cat is meowing. he's hungry.",
    "answer": "okay. i'll feed him right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i'll feed him right now.",
    "answer": "you shouldn't make him wait."
  },
  {
    "question": "you shouldn't make him wait.",
    "answer": "i was doing my homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was doing my homework.",
    "answer": "the cat doesn't care about your homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "the cat doesn't care about your homework.",
    "answer": "the cat doesn't care about anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "the cat doesn't care about anything.",
    "answer": "that's the way cats are."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's the way cats are.",
    "answer": "all they think about is themselves."
  },
  {
    "question": "all they think about is themselves.",
    "answer": "maybe we should get rid of him."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe we should get rid of him.",
    "answer": "of course not! he's family."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate shaving.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "i just cut myself again."
  },
  {
    "question": "i just cut myself again.",
    "answer": "did you use a new blade?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you use a new blade?",
    "answer": "it doesn't matter. old blades cut, new blades cut."
  },
  {
    "question": "it doesn't matter. old blades cut, new blades cut.",
    "answer": "maybe you should use an electric shaver."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you should use an electric shaver.",
    "answer": "they make a lot of noise, but they don't give a close shave."
  },
  {
    "question": "they make a lot of noise, but they don't give a close shave.",
    "answer": "maybe you should stop shaving."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you should stop shaving.",
    "answer": "and grow a beard?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and grow a beard?",
    "answer": "sure. why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure. why not?",
    "answer": "because food and other stuff sticks in my beard."
  },
  {
    "question": "because food and other stuff sticks in my beard.",
    "answer": "hmm. here's an idea. put cream on your face and have the cat lick it off."
  },
  {
    "question": "excuse me.",
    "answer": "yes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes?",
    "answer": "are you reading this paper?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you reading this paper?",
    "answer": "oh, no. help yourself."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no. help yourself.",
    "answer": "i asked because the paper is sitting next to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i asked because the paper is sitting next to you.",
    "answer": "thank you. that's polite of you to ask."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. that's polite of you to ask.",
    "answer": "some people would just pick it up."
  },
  {
    "question": "some people would just pick it up.",
    "answer": "yes, i know. some people are rude."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i know. some people are rude.",
    "answer": "i always try to be polite."
  },
  {
    "question": "i always try to be polite.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "the world needs more polite people like us."
  },
  {
    "question": "the world needs more polite people like us.",
    "answer": "i agree 100 percent."
  },
  {
    "question": "mom, i want a puppy.",
    "answer": "let me think about it."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me think about it.",
    "answer": "why do you have to think about it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you have to think about it?",
    "answer": "because a puppy costs money."
  },
  {
    "question": "because a puppy costs money.",
    "answer": "no, it doesn't. puppies are free."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it doesn't. puppies are free.",
    "answer": "yes, but a puppy needs shots."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but a puppy needs shots.",
    "answer": "shots for what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "shots for what?",
    "answer": "so it won't get sick. just like you get shots."
  },
  {
    "question": "so it won't get sick. just like you get shots.",
    "answer": "i hate shots."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate shots.",
    "answer": "and a puppy eats food. food costs money."
  },
  {
    "question": "and a puppy eats food. food costs money.",
    "answer": "no problem. i'll give him food off my plate."
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem. i'll give him food off my plate.",
    "answer": "oh, no you don't. puppies don't eat vegetables."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at all these kittens!",
    "answer": "how many are there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many are there?",
    "answer": "eight."
  },
  {
    "question": "eight.",
    "answer": "they're all so cute."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're all so cute.",
    "answer": "yes, but i can't keep them."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i can't keep them.",
    "answer": "what are you going to do with them?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do with them?",
    "answer": "i'm going to give them away. do you want one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to give them away. do you want one?",
    "answer": "yes, i would love one."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i would love one.",
    "answer": "which one do you want?"
  },
  {
    "question": "which one do you want?",
    "answer": "that one. the one that's all black."
  },
  {
    "question": "that one. the one that's all black.",
    "answer": "yes, i like that one, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i like that one, too.",
    "answer": "i'll call him blacky."
  },
  {
    "question": "my parents go to church every sunday.",
    "answer": "they trust in god."
  },
  {
    "question": "they trust in god.",
    "answer": "they hope they will go to heaven."
  },
  {
    "question": "they hope they will go to heaven.",
    "answer": "they probably will."
  },
  {
    "question": "they probably will.",
    "answer": "but no one knows for sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "but no one knows for sure.",
    "answer": "that's for sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's for sure.",
    "answer": "no one knows what happens after we die."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one knows what happens after we die.",
    "answer": "if we are good, we will be happy in heaven with god."
  },
  {
    "question": "if we are good, we will be happy in heaven with god.",
    "answer": "that's what many people believe."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what many people believe.",
    "answer": "if we are bad, we will be unhappy forever in hell."
  },
  {
    "question": "if we are bad, we will be unhappy forever in hell.",
    "answer": "i don't want to go to hell."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want to go to hell.",
    "answer": "let's go to church with your parents on sunday."
  },
  {
    "question": "my husband died.",
    "answer": "i'm sorry for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sorry for you.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "when did he die?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when did he die?",
    "answer": "a couple of months ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "a couple of months ago.",
    "answer": "you still miss him."
  },
  {
    "question": "you still miss him.",
    "answer": "yes, but i talk to him almost every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i talk to him almost every day.",
    "answer": "when you go to church?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when you go to church?",
    "answer": "no, when i call him on his cell phone."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, when i call him on his cell phone.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i buried him with his cell phone."
  },
  {
    "question": "i buried him with his cell phone.",
    "answer": "what will you do when the battery dies?"
  },
  {
    "question": "today is friday the thirteenth.",
    "answer": "that's a bad day."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a bad day.",
    "answer": "it's supposed to be unlucky."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's supposed to be unlucky.",
    "answer": "you're supposed to stay home all day."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're supposed to stay home all day.",
    "answer": "that's what i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what i do.",
    "answer": "my friend stayed in a hotel on friday the thirteenth."
  },
  {
    "question": "my friend stayed in a hotel on friday the thirteenth.",
    "answer": "that was a mistake."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a mistake.",
    "answer": "he stayed on the thirteenth floor."
  },
  {
    "question": "he stayed on the thirteenth floor.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "someone stole his laptop."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone stole his laptop.",
    "answer": "he was asking for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "he was asking for it.",
    "answer": "he learned his lesson. he's home today."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you really love me?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "prove it."
  },
  {
    "question": "prove it.",
    "answer": "how can i prove it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how can i prove it?",
    "answer": "take me to dinner."
  },
  {
    "question": "take me to dinner.",
    "answer": "that's it? that's all i have to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's it? that's all i have to do?",
    "answer": "take me to a nice restaurant, not to mcdonald's."
  },
  {
    "question": "take me to a nice restaurant, not to mcdonald's.",
    "answer": "but a nice restaurant costs money."
  },
  {
    "question": "but a nice restaurant costs money.",
    "answer": "yes, and you have to make a reservation."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and you have to make a reservation.",
    "answer": "that's such a hassle."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's such a hassle.",
    "answer": "i knew you didn't love me."
  },
  {
    "question": "i knew you didn't love me.",
    "answer": "okay, okay! i'll make a reservation right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "my parents are divorced.",
    "answer": "so are mine."
  },
  {
    "question": "so are mine.",
    "answer": "why did your parents get divorced?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did your parents get divorced?",
    "answer": "my father found a new girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "question": "my father found a new girlfriend.",
    "answer": "that's too bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's too bad.",
    "answer": "my mother was hurt and angry."
  },
  {
    "question": "my mother was hurt and angry.",
    "answer": "she had good reason. what did she do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "she had good reason. what did she do?",
    "answer": "she told him to drop his girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "question": "she told him to drop his girlfriend.",
    "answer": "what did your father do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did your father do?",
    "answer": "he moved out of our house."
  },
  {
    "question": "he moved out of our house.",
    "answer": "i guess he really liked his new girlfriend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess he really liked his new girlfriend.",
    "answer": "yes, but she left him a year later."
  },
  {
    "question": "my grandma's apartment smells funny.",
    "answer": "so does mine."
  },
  {
    "question": "so does mine.",
    "answer": "i think it's an old people's smell."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it's an old people's smell.",
    "answer": "really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really?",
    "answer": "yes. i think when you get old, you begin to smell."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i think when you get old, you begin to smell.",
    "answer": "like fruit that is too ripe?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like fruit that is too ripe?",
    "answer": "yes, just like fruit that is too ripe."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, just like fruit that is too ripe.",
    "answer": "but the smell is different."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the smell is different.",
    "answer": "yes, old people don't smell like fruit."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, old people don't smell like fruit.",
    "answer": "no, they smell like a thrift shop."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, they smell like a thrift shop.",
    "answer": "yes, a thrift shop has that same smell."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, a thrift shop has that same smell.",
    "answer": "yes, an old smell."
  },
  {
    "question": "the price of stamps goes up and up.",
    "answer": "i think stamps used to cost a penny."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think stamps used to cost a penny.",
    "answer": "that was a long time ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a long time ago.",
    "answer": "it was before i was born."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was before i was born.",
    "answer": "now a stamp is 42 cents."
  },
  {
    "question": "now a stamp is 42 cents.",
    "answer": "but in may it will be 44 cents."
  },
  {
    "question": "but in may it will be 44 cents.",
    "answer": "have you ever lost a letter in the mail?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you ever lost a letter in the mail?",
    "answer": "no, i haven't."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i haven't.",
    "answer": "neither have i."
  },
  {
    "question": "neither have i.",
    "answer": "so, they do a good job for the money."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, they do a good job for the money.",
    "answer": "yes, they do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, they do.",
    "answer": "maybe we shouldn't complain."
  },
  {
    "question": "a button came off my shirt.",
    "answer": "what are you going to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do?",
    "answer": "first, i have to find the button."
  },
  {
    "question": "first, i have to find the button.",
    "answer": "where did you lose it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where did you lose it?",
    "answer": "i have no idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have no idea.",
    "answer": "a button is hard to find. did you look in your pant cuffs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "a button is hard to find. did you look in your pant cuffs?",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "i found a button in my pant cuffs one time."
  },
  {
    "question": "i found a button in my pant cuffs one time.",
    "answer": "let me look. no, it's not there."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me look. no, it's not there.",
    "answer": "many shirts come with an extra button."
  },
  {
    "question": "many shirts come with an extra button.",
    "answer": "you're right. this one does have an extra button."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. this one does have an extra button.",
    "answer": "now all you have to do is sew it on."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to go to the bathroom.",
    "answer": "you drink too much coffee."
  },
  {
    "question": "you drink too much coffee.",
    "answer": "but i love coffee."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i love coffee.",
    "answer": "well, it's your life."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's your life.",
    "answer": "you eat too much chocolate."
  },
  {
    "question": "you eat too much chocolate.",
    "answer": "i don't think so."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't think so.",
    "answer": "have you looked in the mirror?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you looked in the mirror?",
    "answer": "do you think i'm getting fat?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think i'm getting fat?",
    "answer": "i didn't say that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't say that.",
    "answer": "what did you say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you say?",
    "answer": "i said i have to go to the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "i said i have to go to the bathroom.",
    "answer": "that's what i thought you said."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you do the laundry?",
    "answer": "yes, i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did.",
    "answer": "what did you wash?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you wash?",
    "answer": "i washed the sheets and towels."
  },
  {
    "question": "i washed the sheets and towels.",
    "answer": "what about the pillowcases?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about the pillowcases?",
    "answer": "yes, i took them off the pillows and washed them."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i took them off the pillows and washed them.",
    "answer": "did you dry everything in the dryer?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you dry everything in the dryer?",
    "answer": "yes, i dried everything in the dryer."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i dried everything in the dryer.",
    "answer": "then what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then what did you do?",
    "answer": "i folded all the towels."
  },
  {
    "question": "i folded all the towels.",
    "answer": "did you put the sheets on the beds?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you put the sheets on the beds?",
    "answer": "yes, and i put the pillowcases on the pillows."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you listen to the radio?",
    "answer": "i listen day and night."
  },
  {
    "question": "i listen day and night.",
    "answer": "what do you listen to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you listen to?",
    "answer": "mostly talk radio."
  },
  {
    "question": "mostly talk radio.",
    "answer": "what's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's that?",
    "answer": "people talk about current events."
  },
  {
    "question": "people talk about current events.",
    "answer": "what do they say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do they say?",
    "answer": "they say they want change."
  },
  {
    "question": "they say they want change.",
    "answer": "what kind of change?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of change?",
    "answer": "they want tax cuts."
  },
  {
    "question": "they want tax cuts.",
    "answer": "why do they want tax cuts?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do they want tax cuts?",
    "answer": "because tax cuts will save them money."
  },
  {
    "question": "mom, i'm hungry.",
    "answer": "look in the fridge."
  },
  {
    "question": "look in the fridge.",
    "answer": "i'm looking. there's nothing to eat."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm looking. there's nothing to eat.",
    "answer": "are you sure?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you sure?",
    "answer": "it's almost empty."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's almost empty.",
    "answer": "i went to the market yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to the market yesterday.",
    "answer": "i don't see anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't see anything.",
    "answer": "i bought lots of oranges and apples."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought lots of oranges and apples.",
    "answer": "i don't want fruit. i want something tasty."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want fruit. i want something tasty.",
    "answer": "eat the fruit. it's good for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "eat the fruit. it's good for you.",
    "answer": "next time you go to the market, let me go with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "next time you go to the market, let me go with you.",
    "answer": "no, thank you. all you want to eat are hot dogs and candy bars."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is there to eat?",
    "answer": "i don't know. look in the fridge."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. look in the fridge.",
    "answer": "i think i'll make a sandwich."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i'll make a sandwich.",
    "answer": "what kind?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind?",
    "answer": "a ham sandwich."
  },
  {
    "question": "a ham sandwich.",
    "answer": "the bread is in the cabinet."
  },
  {
    "question": "the bread is in the cabinet.",
    "answer": "where's the mustard?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where's the mustard?",
    "answer": "it's in the fridge, i think."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's in the fridge, i think.",
    "answer": "oh, yes, here it is. do you want a sandwich?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes, here it is. do you want a sandwich?",
    "answer": "yes, that sounds nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, that sounds nice.",
    "answer": "how about some potato chips?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about some potato chips?",
    "answer": "yes. and a pickle, if we have any."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's time for your bath, young lady.",
    "answer": "but, mom, i'm not dirty."
  },
  {
    "question": "but, mom, i'm not dirty.",
    "answer": "you need a bath every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "you need a bath every day.",
    "answer": "why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why?",
    "answer": "because you don't want to smell bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you don't want to smell bad.",
    "answer": "i don't smell bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't smell bad.",
    "answer": "that's what you think."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what you think.",
    "answer": "if i smelled bad, i could smell me."
  },
  {
    "question": "if i smelled bad, i could smell me.",
    "answer": "i can smell you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can smell you.",
    "answer": "i can smell you, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can smell you, too.",
    "answer": "that's my perfume."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's my perfume.",
    "answer": "when can i wear perfume?"
  },
  {
    "question": "something's wrong with my computer.",
    "answer": "exactly what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "exactly what?",
    "answer": "all i get is a black screen."
  },
  {
    "question": "all i get is a black screen.",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "i think i know, because this happened before."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i know, because this happened before.",
    "answer": "what happened before?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened before?",
    "answer": "my hard drive crashed."
  },
  {
    "question": "my hard drive crashed.",
    "answer": "oh, no. that's bad news."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no. that's bad news.",
    "answer": "it sure is, but i'm going to call hp first, just to make sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sure is, but i'm going to call hp first, just to make sure.",
    "answer": "will you lose all your files?"
  },
  {
    "question": "will you lose all your files?",
    "answer": "no, i always back up my files."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i always back up my files.",
    "answer": "you're smart."
  },
  {
    "question": "i called hp about my computer.",
    "answer": "what did they say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did they say?",
    "answer": "they said i need a new hard drive."
  },
  {
    "question": "they said i need a new hard drive.",
    "answer": "that's too bad. how much is a new one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's too bad. how much is a new one?",
    "answer": "it's not too much, only about $85."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not too much, only about $85.",
    "answer": "plus installation?"
  },
  {
    "question": "plus installation?",
    "answer": "no, my hard drive is easy to remove and replace."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, my hard drive is easy to remove and replace.",
    "answer": "really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really?",
    "answer": "yes, it's just a couple of screws."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's just a couple of screws.",
    "answer": "that's nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's nice.",
    "answer": "it's a lot better than paying someone $60."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a lot better than paying someone $60.",
    "answer": "if my hard drive crashes, i'll just call you."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's your email address?",
    "answer": "it's bluedog123."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's bluedog123.",
    "answer": "bluedog123. are you sure that's all?"
  },
  {
    "question": "bluedog123. are you sure that's all?",
    "answer": "yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes.",
    "answer": "no. that's incomplete."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. that's incomplete.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "what's your mailing address?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's your mailing address?",
    "answer": "456 cherry drive, pasadena, ca 91170."
  },
  {
    "question": "456 cherry drive, pasadena, ca 91170.",
    "answer": "that's correct."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's correct.",
    "answer": "so what's the problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what's the problem?",
    "answer": "bluedog123 is just the street. you have to give me the city, state, and zip code."
  },
  {
    "question": "bluedog123 is just the street. you have to give me the city, state, and zip code.",
    "answer": "oh, i get it. my email address is bluedog123@yahoo.com."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to take a nap.",
    "answer": "you should unplug the phone."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should unplug the phone.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "do you want me to wake you in an hour?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you want me to wake you in an hour?",
    "answer": "no, thanks. just let me sleep until i wake up."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, thanks. just let me sleep until i wake up.",
    "answer": "i'll start dinner at 6:00."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll start dinner at 6:00.",
    "answer": "okay. i think i'll be awake by then."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i think i'll be awake by then.",
    "answer": "if not, your nose will wake you up."
  },
  {
    "question": "if not, your nose will wake you up.",
    "answer": "you mean i will smell the food cooking?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you mean i will smell the food cooking?",
    "answer": "you might even dream about dinner."
  },
  {
    "question": "you might even dream about dinner.",
    "answer": "i don't think i'm going to dream about anything. i'm really tired."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't think i'm going to dream about anything. i'm really tired.",
    "answer": "have a nice nap."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a nice funeral.",
    "answer": "yes, dad, it was."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, dad, it was.",
    "answer": "the son gave a nice speech about his father."
  },
  {
    "question": "the son gave a nice speech about his father.",
    "answer": "it was long, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was long, too.",
    "answer": "i think it was about 45 minutes long."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it was about 45 minutes long.",
    "answer": "but it went by fast. it was interesting."
  },
  {
    "question": "but it went by fast. it was interesting.",
    "answer": "i liked it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i liked it.",
    "answer": "i'll give you a speech like that, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll give you a speech like that, too.",
    "answer": "do you think anyone will come to my funeral?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think anyone will come to my funeral?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "i think only the family will be there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think only the family will be there.",
    "answer": "you have lots of friends. they will be there, too!"
  },
  {
    "question": "yikes! what was that noise?",
    "answer": "i had to blow my nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had to blow my nose.",
    "answer": "did you have to blow right next to the phone?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you have to blow right next to the phone?",
    "answer": "did you hear that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear that?",
    "answer": "of course i heard that. i thought a plane had crashed into your house."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course i heard that. i thought a plane had crashed into your house.",
    "answer": "it wasn't that loud."
  },
  {
    "question": "it wasn't that loud.",
    "answer": "i will blow my nose sometime for you, and you'll see."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will blow my nose sometime for you, and you'll see.",
    "answer": "okay. i'll take your word for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i'll take your word for it.",
    "answer": "i thought you had an elephant in your house."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought you had an elephant in your house.",
    "answer": "you're funny."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're funny.",
    "answer": "what did you say? i think i've gone deaf."
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you say? i think i've gone deaf.",
    "answer": "i'm going into the bathroom to blow my nose. i'll be right back."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have lots of friends.",
    "answer": "really? how many do you have?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really? how many do you have?",
    "answer": "i don't know, maybe one hundred."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know, maybe one hundred.",
    "answer": "that is a lot of friends. do you have a best friend?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that is a lot of friends. do you have a best friend?",
    "answer": "of course. i have lots of best friends."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. i have lots of best friends.",
    "answer": "how many best friends do you have?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many best friends do you have?",
    "answer": "i think about twenty-five."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think about twenty-five.",
    "answer": "hmm. i have only one best friend."
  },
  {
    "question": "hmm. i have only one best friend.",
    "answer": "i feel sorry for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel sorry for you.",
    "answer": "i have only a few friends."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have only a few friends.",
    "answer": "you must be lonely. i will share my friends with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "you must be lonely. i will share my friends with you.",
    "answer": "that's very nice of you."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't you ever cheat on me.",
    "answer": "why would i do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why would i do that?",
    "answer": "because men like to cheat."
  },
  {
    "question": "because men like to cheat.",
    "answer": "some men do, but not me."
  },
  {
    "question": "some men do, but not me.",
    "answer": "i'm watching you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm watching you.",
    "answer": "i'm an open book. watch me all you want."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm an open book. watch me all you want.",
    "answer": "if i catch you, you'll be sorry."
  },
  {
    "question": "if i catch you, you'll be sorry.",
    "answer": "you won't catch me, because i love you. i'm not a cheater."
  },
  {
    "question": "you won't catch me, because i love you. i'm not a cheater.",
    "answer": "i will poke your eyes out."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will poke your eyes out.",
    "answer": "i don't want any other woman."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want any other woman.",
    "answer": "i will chop your toes off, one by one."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will chop your toes off, one by one.",
    "answer": "honey, please. you're the only woman for me, forever. i swear it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate to go outside.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "why do you hate to go outside?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you hate to go outside?",
    "answer": "i meet too many jerks."
  },
  {
    "question": "i meet too many jerks.",
    "answer": "i agree."
  },
  {
    "question": "i agree.",
    "answer": "this city is full of jerks."
  },
  {
    "question": "this city is full of jerks.",
    "answer": "rude people are everywhere."
  },
  {
    "question": "rude people are everywhere.",
    "answer": "but what can you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but what can you do?",
    "answer": "you can yell at them."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can yell at them.",
    "answer": "and they will yell back at you."
  },
  {
    "question": "and they will yell back at you.",
    "answer": "yelling doesn't do any good."
  },
  {
    "question": "yelling doesn't do any good.",
    "answer": "no. the best thing to do is just stay home."
  },
  {
    "question": "will you look at this form?",
    "answer": "are you having problems with it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you having problems with it?",
    "answer": "i don't understand some things."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't understand some things.",
    "answer": "let me help you."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me help you.",
    "answer": "what does \"mi\" mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does \"mi\" mean?",
    "answer": "mi\" stands for middle initial."
  },
  {
    "question": "mi\" stands for middle initial.",
    "answer": "what does \"mm/dd/yy\" mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does \"mm/dd/yy\" mean?",
    "answer": "that means month/day/year. use numbers."
  },
  {
    "question": "that means month/day/year. use numbers.",
    "answer": "i don't understand."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't understand.",
    "answer": "for example, if your birth date is january 12, 1987, write 01/12/87."
  },
  {
    "question": "for example, if your birth date is january 12, 1987, write 01/12/87.",
    "answer": "oh. that's simple enough."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh. that's simple enough.",
    "answer": "always print clearly, and fill in the bubbles completely."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to the animal shelter.",
    "answer": "what do you want to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you want to do?",
    "answer": "i want to get a puppy for my son."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to get a puppy for my son.",
    "answer": "that will make him so happy."
  },
  {
    "question": "that will make him so happy.",
    "answer": "i'll get him one of those little dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll get him one of those little dogs.",
    "answer": "one that won't grow up too big."
  },
  {
    "question": "one that won't grow up too big.",
    "answer": "and eat too much."
  },
  {
    "question": "and eat too much.",
    "answer": "do you know which one he would like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know which one he would like?",
    "answer": "oh, yes, i took him there yesterday. he showed me one that he really liked."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes, i took him there yesterday. he showed me one that he really liked.",
    "answer": "i bet you had to drag him away."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bet you had to drag him away.",
    "answer": "he wanted to take it home yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "he wanted to take it home yesterday.",
    "answer": "i wonder what he'll name it."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the weather like?",
    "answer": "i don't know. i just woke up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. i just woke up.",
    "answer": "why don't you look outside?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why don't you look outside?",
    "answer": "okay. it looks like rain."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. it looks like rain.",
    "answer": "why do you say that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you say that?",
    "answer": "the sky is gray."
  },
  {
    "question": "the sky is gray.",
    "answer": "is it raining right now?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it raining right now?",
    "answer": "no."
  },
  {
    "question": "no.",
    "answer": "how do you know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you know?",
    "answer": "the street isn't wet."
  },
  {
    "question": "the street isn't wet.",
    "answer": "i have to go shopping today."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to go shopping today.",
    "answer": "you'd better take an umbrella."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe how hot it is.",
    "answer": "it's not even noon yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not even noon yet.",
    "answer": "that means it will get hotter."
  },
  {
    "question": "that means it will get hotter.",
    "answer": "i am dying from the heat."
  },
  {
    "question": "i am dying from the heat.",
    "answer": "turn on the air conditioner."
  },
  {
    "question": "turn on the air conditioner.",
    "answer": "it doesn't work."
  },
  {
    "question": "it doesn't work.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "i don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know.",
    "answer": "did you call the repairman?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you call the repairman?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "when is he coming?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when is he coming?",
    "answer": "he's busy. he said next week."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll be glad when winter comes.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "because i love the snow."
  },
  {
    "question": "because i love the snow.",
    "answer": "yes, the snow is fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, the snow is fun.",
    "answer": "last year we made a big snowman."
  },
  {
    "question": "last year we made a big snowman.",
    "answer": "how big was it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how big was it?",
    "answer": "it was seven feet tall."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was seven feet tall.",
    "answer": "how long did it take?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how long did it take?",
    "answer": "it took us all day."
  },
  {
    "question": "it took us all day.",
    "answer": "did you give him a nose?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you give him a nose?",
    "answer": "of course. we gave him a big carrot for a nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. we gave him a big carrot for a nose.",
    "answer": "let me help you make one this year."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to the bank.",
    "answer": "what do you need to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you need to do?",
    "answer": "i need to withdraw some money."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need to withdraw some money.",
    "answer": "how are you going to do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how are you going to do that?",
    "answer": "i'll just use the atm."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll just use the atm.",
    "answer": "what's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's that?",
    "answer": "it's the automatic teller machine."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the automatic teller machine.",
    "answer": "it gives you money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it gives you money?",
    "answer": "i just insert my debit card into the machine."
  },
  {
    "question": "i just insert my debit card into the machine.",
    "answer": "and it gives you money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and it gives you money?",
    "answer": "well, it gives me money, but it's my own money."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it gives me money, but it's my own money.",
    "answer": "oh. what good is that? i thought it gave you free money."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you put the blue bin out on the street?",
    "answer": "oh, no. i forgot."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no. i forgot.",
    "answer": "well, you'd better take it out front."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you'd better take it out front.",
    "answer": "what time does the recycle truck come by?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time does the recycle truck come by?",
    "answer": "it usually gets here at noon on tuesday, which is tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "it usually gets here at noon on tuesday, which is tomorrow.",
    "answer": "i'll just take it out to the street tomorrow morning."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll just take it out to the street tomorrow morning.",
    "answer": "oh, no, you don't."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no, you don't.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "every morning you get up late and rush off to work late."
  },
  {
    "question": "every morning you get up late and rush off to work late.",
    "answer": "do you think i'll forget to do it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think i'll forget to do it?",
    "answer": "you'll remember to do it, but you won't have time to do it."
  },
  {
    "question": "you'll remember to do it, but you won't have time to do it.",
    "answer": "okay, i'll take it out front right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "are you ready?",
    "answer": "ready for what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "ready for what?",
    "answer": "ready for the big switch."
  },
  {
    "question": "ready for the big switch.",
    "answer": "what are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you talking about?",
    "answer": "the nation is switching to digital tv."
  },
  {
    "question": "the nation is switching to digital tv.",
    "answer": "oh. of course i'm ready."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh. of course i'm ready.",
    "answer": "did you buy the converter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you buy the converter?",
    "answer": "no, i don't need a converter because i bought a digital tv."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i don't need a converter because i bought a digital tv.",
    "answer": "how much was that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much was that?",
    "answer": "it was only about $120 for a 13-inch screen."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was only about $120 for a 13-inch screen.",
    "answer": "does it pick up any digital channels?"
  },
  {
    "question": "does it pick up any digital channels?",
    "answer": "oh, yes. i get six korean channels but nothing in english!"
  },
  {
    "question": "people are funny.",
    "answer": "they sure are."
  },
  {
    "question": "they sure are.",
    "answer": "did you hear about the pilot?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear about the pilot?",
    "answer": "the one that stole a small plane?"
  },
  {
    "question": "the one that stole a small plane?",
    "answer": "yes, he stole a plane in canada and flew into the u.s."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he stole a plane in canada and flew into the u.s.",
    "answer": "did they catch him?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did they catch him?",
    "answer": "yes. after two u.s. fighter jets followed him for an hour, he landed on a highway."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. after two u.s. fighter jets followed him for an hour, he landed on a highway.",
    "answer": "did he crash?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he crash?",
    "answer": "no, he just landed the plane and walked to a restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, he just landed the plane and walked to a restaurant.",
    "answer": "did the cops find out why he flew into the u.s.?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did the cops find out why he flew into the u.s.?",
    "answer": "his life sucked. he was hoping a fighter jet would shoot him down."
  },
  {
    "question": "his life sucked. he was hoping a fighter jet would shoot him down.",
    "answer": "poor guy."
  },
  {
    "question": "the police need our help finding a robber.",
    "answer": "how do you know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you know?",
    "answer": "the tv news is reporting a bank robbery."
  },
  {
    "question": "the tv news is reporting a bank robbery.",
    "answer": "do they know what the robber looks like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do they know what the robber looks like?",
    "answer": "yes, he's 6 feet tall, 200 pounds, black hair, and about 30 years old."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he's 6 feet tall, 200 pounds, black hair, and about 30 years old.",
    "answer": "what race is he?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what race is he?",
    "answer": "they didn't say."
  },
  {
    "question": "they didn't say.",
    "answer": "the tv news doesn't tell us the race anymore."
  },
  {
    "question": "the tv news doesn't tell us the race anymore.",
    "answer": "of course not. that would be racist."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course not. that would be racist.",
    "answer": "but how can we identify someone if we don't know their race?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but how can we identify someone if we don't know their race?",
    "answer": "don't ask me."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't ask me.",
    "answer": "then they also shouldn't tell us if the robber is male or female, because that is sexist."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't wipe your nose on your sleeve.",
    "answer": "but i don't have a tissue."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i don't have a tissue.",
    "answer": "then go find a tissue in the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "then go find a tissue in the bathroom.",
    "answer": "i didn't have time to get one from there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't have time to get one from there.",
    "answer": "your sleeves are not tissues."
  },
  {
    "question": "your sleeves are not tissues.",
    "answer": "but mom, all my friends use their sleeves."
  },
  {
    "question": "but mom, all my friends use their sleeves.",
    "answer": "that doesn't make it right."
  },
  {
    "question": "that doesn't make it right.",
    "answer": "i saw dad wipe his nose on his sleeve yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw dad wipe his nose on his sleeve yesterday.",
    "answer": "i will talk to your father about that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will talk to your father about that.",
    "answer": "i bet dad did it all the time when he was my age."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bet dad did it all the time when he was my age.",
    "answer": "your daddy was a good little boy."
  },
  {
    "question": "your daddy was a good little boy.",
    "answer": "how do you know? were you his mommy, too?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm worried.",
    "answer": "worried about what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "worried about what?",
    "answer": "i'm getting married."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm getting married.",
    "answer": "you should be happy, not worried."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should be happy, not worried.",
    "answer": "i am happy, but marriage is a lot of responsibility."
  },
  {
    "question": "i am happy, but marriage is a lot of responsibility.",
    "answer": "yes, you have to take care of your wife."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, you have to take care of your wife.",
    "answer": "and i have to take care of our children."
  },
  {
    "question": "and i have to take care of our children.",
    "answer": "are you going to start a family?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to start a family?",
    "answer": "yes. we want to have a little boy and a little girl."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. we want to have a little boy and a little girl.",
    "answer": "that sounds wonderful."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds wonderful.",
    "answer": "except we can't afford it!"
  },
  {
    "question": "except we can't afford it!",
    "answer": "no wonder you're worried."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't get art.",
    "answer": "or artists."
  },
  {
    "question": "or artists.",
    "answer": "they're in a different world."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're in a different world.",
    "answer": "i saw a painting of a jar that was full of pencils."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw a painting of a jar that was full of pencils.",
    "answer": "the artist said the jar was both full and empty."
  },
  {
    "question": "the artist said the jar was both full and empty.",
    "answer": "but it was full of pencils! how could he say it was empty?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but it was full of pencils! how could he say it was empty?",
    "answer": "artists see things differently."
  },
  {
    "question": "artists see things differently.",
    "answer": "did you ever see anything that picasso painted?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you ever see anything that picasso painted?",
    "answer": "of course! he's world famous."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course! he's world famous.",
    "answer": "did he ever take art lessons?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he ever take art lessons?",
    "answer": "i can't believe it. i drew paintings like that in third grade."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe it. i drew paintings like that in third grade.",
    "answer": "where are they? maybe they are worth millions."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the point?",
    "answer": "the point of what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "the point of what?",
    "answer": "of living."
  },
  {
    "question": "of living.",
    "answer": "who knows? you live, and then you die."
  },
  {
    "question": "who knows? you live, and then you die.",
    "answer": "we must be here for some reason."
  },
  {
    "question": "we must be here for some reason.",
    "answer": "maybe we're here to have fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe we're here to have fun.",
    "answer": "then why aren't i having fun?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why aren't i having fun?",
    "answer": "because you're thinking too much."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you're thinking too much.",
    "answer": "so i should stop thinking?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so i should stop thinking?",
    "answer": "stop thinking about what the point is."
  },
  {
    "question": "stop thinking about what the point is.",
    "answer": "okay. i'll start thinking about having some fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i'll start thinking about having some fun.",
    "answer": "just be patient. fun doesn't come along every five minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "beer is a powerful drug.",
    "answer": "so are cigarettes."
  },
  {
    "question": "so are cigarettes.",
    "answer": "which would you prefer?"
  },
  {
    "question": "which would you prefer?",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "when you die and go to heaven, they will offer you beer or cigarettes."
  },
  {
    "question": "when you die and go to heaven, they will offer you beer or cigarettes.",
    "answer": "i could pick only one or the other?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i could pick only one or the other?",
    "answer": "yes. nothing's perfect, not even in heaven."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. nothing's perfect, not even in heaven.",
    "answer": "boy, that's a tough one."
  },
  {
    "question": "boy, that's a tough one.",
    "answer": "what's so tough about it? of course, i would pick cigarettes."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's so tough about it? of course, i would pick cigarettes.",
    "answer": "but cigarettes taste much better when you have a cold beer."
  },
  {
    "question": "but cigarettes taste much better when you have a cold beer.",
    "answer": "well, you can't have everything."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you can't have everything.",
    "answer": "i don't think i want to go to your heaven."
  },
  {
    "question": "my pants have a hole in the front pocket.",
    "answer": "you shouldn't carry pens in your pocket."
  },
  {
    "question": "you shouldn't carry pens in your pocket.",
    "answer": "yesterday a pen fell through my pants onto my shoe."
  },
  {
    "question": "yesterday a pen fell through my pants onto my shoe.",
    "answer": "lucky for you it wasn't a sharp knife."
  },
  {
    "question": "lucky for you it wasn't a sharp knife.",
    "answer": "who carries a sharp knife in their pocket?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who carries a sharp knife in their pocket?",
    "answer": "criminals, of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "criminals, of course.",
    "answer": "anyway, i have to fix the hole."
  },
  {
    "question": "anyway, i have to fix the hole.",
    "answer": "you can sew it up or use an iron-on patch."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can sew it up or use an iron-on patch.",
    "answer": "tell me about this patch."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me about this patch.",
    "answer": "the patch has glue. the hot iron melts the glue so the patch sticks on."
  },
  {
    "question": "the patch has glue. the hot iron melts the glue so the patch sticks on.",
    "answer": "that sounds a lot easier than sewing."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds a lot easier than sewing.",
    "answer": "it is. but after about ten washings, the glue washes off."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know any good jokes?",
    "answer": "i can't remember jokes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't remember jokes.",
    "answer": "neither can i."
  },
  {
    "question": "neither can i.",
    "answer": "they go in one ear and out the other."
  },
  {
    "question": "they go in one ear and out the other.",
    "answer": "who makes up all these jokes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who makes up all these jokes?",
    "answer": "who knows? but there must be a hundred new ones every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "who knows? but there must be a hundred new ones every day.",
    "answer": "yes, just in english alone."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, just in english alone.",
    "answer": "i wonder if every language has jokes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wonder if every language has jokes.",
    "answer": "of course! people everywhere like good jokes."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course! people everywhere like good jokes.",
    "answer": "what do you think people joke about the most?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you think people joke about the most?",
    "answer": "i think most jokes are about women."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think most jokes are about women.",
    "answer": "oh, really? i think most jokes are about men!"
  },
  {
    "question": "you're very lucky.",
    "answer": "why do you say that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you say that?",
    "answer": "you speak two languages."
  },
  {
    "question": "you speak two languages.",
    "answer": "well, my english isn't perfect."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, my english isn't perfect.",
    "answer": "no one speaks perfect english."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one speaks perfect english.",
    "answer": "maybe i will be the first!"
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe i will be the first!",
    "answer": "i've been thinking about learning spanish."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been thinking about learning spanish.",
    "answer": "spanish is easy. i'll be happy to teach you."
  },
  {
    "question": "spanish is easy. i'll be happy to teach you.",
    "answer": "how long will it take me to learn?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how long will it take me to learn?",
    "answer": "i think it will only take you a year or two."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it will only take you a year or two.",
    "answer": "how soon can we begin?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how soon can we begin?",
    "answer": "ahora! that means right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know what today is?",
    "answer": "yes, it's april 22."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's april 22.",
    "answer": "it's more than just a date."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's more than just a date.",
    "answer": "is it your birthday or anniversary?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it your birthday or anniversary?",
    "answer": "no, it's earth day."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's earth day.",
    "answer": "what's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's that?",
    "answer": "it's a yearly reminder to take care of our planet."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a yearly reminder to take care of our planet.",
    "answer": "oh, you mean like reuse things and recycle stuff?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, you mean like reuse things and recycle stuff?",
    "answer": "yes. we need to think green, save water, and stop using plastic bags."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. we need to think green, save water, and stop using plastic bags.",
    "answer": "how about if i take shorter showers?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about if i take shorter showers?",
    "answer": "that's a good idea, because showers waste a lot of water."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea, because showers waste a lot of water.",
    "answer": "from now on i'll spend only 20 minutes in the shower."
  },
  {
    "question": "poetry sucks.",
    "answer": "i don't know anyone who likes it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know anyone who likes it.",
    "answer": "some of it is okay, i guess."
  },
  {
    "question": "some of it is okay, i guess.",
    "answer": "yes, the poems that rhyme and are easy to remember."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, the poems that rhyme and are easy to remember.",
    "answer": "like \"one, two, buckle my shoe."
  },
  {
    "question": "like \"one, two, buckle my shoe.",
    "answer": "but people still write poems."
  },
  {
    "question": "but people still write poems.",
    "answer": "no one makes any money at it."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one makes any money at it.",
    "answer": "shakespeare was a poet."
  },
  {
    "question": "shakespeare was a poet.",
    "answer": "did he get rich from his poetry?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he get rich from his poetry?",
    "answer": "probably not."
  },
  {
    "question": "probably not.",
    "answer": "poems are a little bit like songs."
  },
  {
    "question": "poems are a little bit like songs.",
    "answer": "yes, but songs have music. without music, songs would suck, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "how smart are you?",
    "answer": "i don't know. i think i'm average."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. i think i'm average.",
    "answer": "did you ever take an iq test?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you ever take an iq test?",
    "answer": "no, i never did. all i know is that i got a's and b's in school."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i never did. all i know is that i got a's and b's in school.",
    "answer": "i wish i was really smart."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i was really smart.",
    "answer": "don't be ridiculous."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't be ridiculous.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "if you're going to make a wish, wish that you were really rich or famous."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you're going to make a wish, wish that you were really rich or famous.",
    "answer": "don't you ever wonder what it's like to be super-smart?"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't you ever wonder what it's like to be super-smart?",
    "answer": "it must be very lonely."
  },
  {
    "question": "it must be very lonely.",
    "answer": "why's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why's that?",
    "answer": "because if you're super-smart, no one understands what you're saying."
  },
  {
    "question": "i missed the tv news last night. what was on?",
    "answer": "nothing that would pass as news."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing that would pass as news.",
    "answer": "what's the weather going to be like this weekend?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the weather going to be like this weekend?",
    "answer": "i don't know. whenever the weather comes on, i switch channels."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. whenever the weather comes on, i switch channels.",
    "answer": "what was the lead story on the news?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the lead story on the news?",
    "answer": "some actress was in court for driving without a license."
  },
  {
    "question": "some actress was in court for driving without a license.",
    "answer": "what was the second story?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the second story?",
    "answer": "some actor married a woman young enough to be his daughter."
  },
  {
    "question": "some actor married a woman young enough to be his daughter.",
    "answer": "what was the third story?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the third story?",
    "answer": "a bull chased a man in a supermarket."
  },
  {
    "question": "a bull chased a man in a supermarket.",
    "answer": "wasn't there anything about octo-mom?"
  },
  {
    "question": "wasn't there anything about octo-mom?",
    "answer": "of course. she's going to hire a nanny for her eight infants."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do about your death?",
    "answer": "well, mostly i'll try to avoid it."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, mostly i'll try to avoid it.",
    "answer": "i mean, are you going to get buried or cremated?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean, are you going to get buried or cremated?",
    "answer": "my wife and i will be cremated."
  },
  {
    "question": "my wife and i will be cremated.",
    "answer": "are you going to be buried next to each other?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to be buried next to each other?",
    "answer": "oh, no. our ashes will be shaken into the ocean."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no. our ashes will be shaken into the ocean.",
    "answer": "you're not going to be buried?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you're not going to be buried?",
    "answer": "a coffin costs too much and takes up too much space."
  },
  {
    "question": "a coffin costs too much and takes up too much space.",
    "answer": "yes, but it will be in a cemetery where your children can visit you."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but it will be in a cemetery where your children can visit you.",
    "answer": "children seldom visit their parents in a cemetery."
  },
  {
    "question": "children seldom visit their parents in a cemetery.",
    "answer": "that's true. a cemetery is for dead people, not living people."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's true. a cemetery is for dead people, not living people.",
    "answer": "we figure our kids can visit us whenever they go to the beach."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you wipe your feet?",
    "answer": "yes, of course i wiped my feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, of course i wiped my feet.",
    "answer": "then why is there mud on the carpet?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why is there mud on the carpet?",
    "answer": "i don't know. it's not my mud."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. it's not my mud.",
    "answer": "well, someone brought it into the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, someone brought it into the house.",
    "answer": "look at the bottom of my shoesÂ—they're clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at the bottom of my shoesÂ—they're clean.",
    "answer": "of course they're clean. you left all the mud on the carpet."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course they're clean. you left all the mud on the carpet.",
    "answer": "okay, i'll get the vacuum cleaner."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, i'll get the vacuum cleaner.",
    "answer": "don't vacuum it now."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't vacuum it now.",
    "answer": "don't you want me to clean up the mud?"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't you want me to clean up the mud?",
    "answer": "wait till it dries. it will be easier to vacuum."
  },
  {
    "question": "wait till it dries. it will be easier to vacuum.",
    "answer": "next time i will be more careful."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you getting for your mom?",
    "answer": "what are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you talking about?",
    "answer": "sunday is mother's day."
  },
  {
    "question": "sunday is mother's day.",
    "answer": "this sunday?"
  },
  {
    "question": "this sunday?",
    "answer": "of course. it's all over the news."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. it's all over the news.",
    "answer": "i thought it was next sunday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought it was next sunday.",
    "answer": "well, you'd better get her something."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you'd better get her something.",
    "answer": "i'll get her a nice card."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll get her a nice card.",
    "answer": "is that it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that it?",
    "answer": "yes. that's all i ever give her."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. that's all i ever give her.",
    "answer": "she raised you, and all you ever give her is a card?"
  },
  {
    "question": "she raised you, and all you ever give her is a card?",
    "answer": "it's okay. she knows that i love her."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like our flag.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with it?",
    "answer": "it's too much like other flags."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's too much like other flags.",
    "answer": "yes, a lot of flags have stripes."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, a lot of flags have stripes.",
    "answer": "a flag should be pretty."
  },
  {
    "question": "a flag should be pretty.",
    "answer": "what should our flag look like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what should our flag look like?",
    "answer": "it should have a pretty woman on it."
  },
  {
    "question": "it should have a pretty woman on it.",
    "answer": "that's ridiculous!"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's ridiculous!",
    "answer": "you don't like pretty women?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't like pretty women?",
    "answer": "of course i do. but not on our flag!"
  },
  {
    "question": "of course i do. but not on our flag!",
    "answer": "every nation should have a pretty woman on their flag."
  },
  {
    "question": "every nation should have a pretty woman on their flag.",
    "answer": "you can't go to war carrying a flag with a woman on it!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i had a busy morning.",
    "answer": "what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do?",
    "answer": "i watered all the plants."
  },
  {
    "question": "i watered all the plants.",
    "answer": "you have a lot of plants."
  },
  {
    "question": "you have a lot of plants.",
    "answer": "then i did my laundry."
  },
  {
    "question": "then i did my laundry.",
    "answer": "that takes some time."
  },
  {
    "question": "that takes some time.",
    "answer": "i took the dog for a walk."
  },
  {
    "question": "i took the dog for a walk.",
    "answer": "i'll bet he enjoyed his walk."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll bet he enjoyed his walk.",
    "answer": "i vacuumed the entire house."
  },
  {
    "question": "i vacuumed the entire house.",
    "answer": "that's a lot of work."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a lot of work.",
    "answer": "and then i made lunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then i made lunch.",
    "answer": "i'll bet you were hungry!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have long distance service with my home phone.",
    "answer": "so how do you make long distance calls?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so how do you make long distance calls?",
    "answer": "i use a calling card."
  },
  {
    "question": "i use a calling card.",
    "answer": "where do you get that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you get that?",
    "answer": "i buy it at the dollar store."
  },
  {
    "question": "i buy it at the dollar store.",
    "answer": "how much is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much is it?",
    "answer": "it's one dollar for 100 minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's one dollar for 100 minutes.",
    "answer": "that's only a penny a minute!"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's only a penny a minute!",
    "answer": "it's a great price. but you have to dial a lot of numbers."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a great price. but you have to dial a lot of numbers.",
    "answer": "how many?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many?",
    "answer": "first you dial seven numbers, then ten numbers, then ten more numbers."
  },
  {
    "question": "first you dial seven numbers, then ten numbers, then ten more numbers.",
    "answer": "yikes. i think i'll keep my long distance service."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you go to college?",
    "answer": "yes, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i do.",
    "answer": "what college do you go to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what college do you go to?",
    "answer": "i go to pasadena city college."
  },
  {
    "question": "i go to pasadena city college.",
    "answer": "do you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you like it?",
    "answer": "oh, yes, i really like it."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes, i really like it.",
    "answer": "why do you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you like it?",
    "answer": "because it has great teachers."
  },
  {
    "question": "because it has great teachers.",
    "answer": "what else?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what else?",
    "answer": "i like all my classmates, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like all my classmates, too.",
    "answer": "anything else?"
  },
  {
    "question": "anything else?",
    "answer": "yes. it's not expensive!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i lost my new pen.",
    "answer": "where did you lose it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where did you lose it?",
    "answer": "i don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know.",
    "answer": "when did you lose it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when did you lose it?",
    "answer": "i think i lost it today. i used it yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i lost it today. i used it yesterday.",
    "answer": "did you check all your pockets?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you check all your pockets?",
    "answer": "i checked all my pockets."
  },
  {
    "question": "i checked all my pockets.",
    "answer": "did you look in your desk?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you look in your desk?",
    "answer": "yes. it isn't there, either."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. it isn't there, either.",
    "answer": "it's probably around somewhere."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's probably around somewhere.",
    "answer": "oh, well, it only cost me a dollar."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, well, it only cost me a dollar.",
    "answer": "only a dollar? don't even look for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "gravity is very important.",
    "answer": "what is gravity?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is gravity?",
    "answer": "it's the force that pulls everything down."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the force that pulls everything down.",
    "answer": "i don't understand."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't understand.",
    "answer": "if you pour water into a glass, the water goes down into the glass."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you pour water into a glass, the water goes down into the glass.",
    "answer": "of course it does."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course it does.",
    "answer": "without gravity, the water would go up."
  },
  {
    "question": "without gravity, the water would go up.",
    "answer": "you're joking."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're joking.",
    "answer": "without gravity, you would go up."
  },
  {
    "question": "without gravity, you would go up.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "you would float into the sky like a balloon."
  },
  {
    "question": "you would float into the sky like a balloon.",
    "answer": "that would be fun!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't read my book.",
    "answer": "turn on the light."
  },
  {
    "question": "turn on the light.",
    "answer": "the light is on."
  },
  {
    "question": "the light is on.",
    "answer": "open the book."
  },
  {
    "question": "open the book.",
    "answer": "the book is open."
  },
  {
    "question": "the book is open.",
    "answer": "see an eye doctor."
  },
  {
    "question": "see an eye doctor.",
    "answer": "that's what i need to do."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what i need to do.",
    "answer": "he'll give you a prescription for glasses."
  },
  {
    "question": "he'll give you a prescription for glasses.",
    "answer": "i'll make an appointment tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll make an appointment tomorrow.",
    "answer": "i'll get the yellow pages for an eye doctor."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll get the yellow pages for an eye doctor.",
    "answer": "read the phone number to me."
  },
  {
    "question": "read the phone number to me.",
    "answer": "i'll read it very loud, in case your hearing is getting bad, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you need for school?",
    "answer": "i need pencils."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need pencils.",
    "answer": "anything else?"
  },
  {
    "question": "anything else?",
    "answer": "i need a notebook."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need a notebook.",
    "answer": "do you need a pen?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you need a pen?",
    "answer": "no. i already have a pen."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. i already have a pen.",
    "answer": "do you need a calculator?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you need a calculator?",
    "answer": "no. the teacher doesn't permit calculators."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. the teacher doesn't permit calculators.",
    "answer": "how about a dictionary?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about a dictionary?",
    "answer": "no, we have a big dictionary in the classroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, we have a big dictionary in the classroom.",
    "answer": "well, i guess that's it."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i guess that's it.",
    "answer": "yes, that's all i need for now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like this magazine.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "i read it once, and i subscribed."
  },
  {
    "question": "i read it once, and i subscribed.",
    "answer": "it gives you all the news."
  },
  {
    "question": "it gives you all the news.",
    "answer": "all the news in only 50 pages."
  },
  {
    "question": "all the news in only 50 pages.",
    "answer": "i like the political cartoons."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the political cartoons.",
    "answer": "i like the beautiful photos of the houses for sale."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the beautiful photos of the houses for sale.",
    "answer": "i always read the film reviews."
  },
  {
    "question": "i always read the film reviews.",
    "answer": "i never miss the food and drink section."
  },
  {
    "question": "i never miss the food and drink section.",
    "answer": "i gave a subscription to my parents."
  },
  {
    "question": "i gave a subscription to my parents.",
    "answer": "me too. they canceled their other news magazines."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. they canceled their other news magazines.",
    "answer": "so did mine!"
  },
  {
    "question": "my pen is out of ink.",
    "answer": "shake it a couple of times."
  },
  {
    "question": "shake it a couple of times.",
    "answer": "i shook it. there is no more ink."
  },
  {
    "question": "i shook it. there is no more ink.",
    "answer": "you can borrow mine."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can borrow mine.",
    "answer": "thank you. i'll buy a new one tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. i'll buy a new one tomorrow.",
    "answer": "what were you doing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what were you doing?",
    "answer": "i was writing a letter."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was writing a letter.",
    "answer": "who were you writing to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who were you writing to?",
    "answer": "it's to my mom."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's to my mom.",
    "answer": "tell her i said hello."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell her i said hello.",
    "answer": "okay. i'll return your pen when i'm done."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. i'll return your pen when i'm done.",
    "answer": "take your time."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you done your homework?",
    "answer": "not yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "not yet.",
    "answer": "then why are you watching tv?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why are you watching tv?",
    "answer": "this is my favorite show."
  },
  {
    "question": "this is my favorite show.",
    "answer": "go do your homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "go do your homework.",
    "answer": "but, mom!"
  },
  {
    "question": "but, mom!",
    "answer": "you can watch tv after you do your homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can watch tv after you do your homework.",
    "answer": "but the show will be over."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the show will be over.",
    "answer": "there will be another show next week."
  },
  {
    "question": "there will be another show next week.",
    "answer": "please?"
  },
  {
    "question": "please?",
    "answer": "you know the rules."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know the rules.",
    "answer": "i hate the rules! i can't wait till i grow up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't wait until i graduate.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "no more homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "no more homework.",
    "answer": "i hate homework."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate homework.",
    "answer": "are you going to college?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to college?",
    "answer": "i can't afford it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't afford it.",
    "answer": "me neither."
  },
  {
    "question": "me neither.",
    "answer": "so what are you going to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what are you going to do?",
    "answer": "i'm joining the army."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm joining the army.",
    "answer": "you're kidding. you might get killed."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're kidding. you might get killed.",
    "answer": "i don't think so. after i finish, i'll have enough money to go to college."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't think so. after i finish, i'll have enough money to go to college.",
    "answer": "that's not a bad idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "what is your major?",
    "answer": "english."
  },
  {
    "question": "english.",
    "answer": "what are you going to do with an english major?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do with an english major?",
    "answer": "i'm going to be a teacher."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to be a teacher.",
    "answer": "high school or middle school?"
  },
  {
    "question": "high school or middle school?",
    "answer": "high school."
  },
  {
    "question": "high school.",
    "answer": "i teach high school english."
  },
  {
    "question": "i teach high school english.",
    "answer": "i didn't know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't know that.",
    "answer": "i started teaching five years ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "i started teaching five years ago.",
    "answer": "how do you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you like it?",
    "answer": "do you see all this gray hair? it was totally black five years ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you see all this gray hair? it was totally black five years ago.",
    "answer": "maybe i'll teach middle school."
  },
  {
    "question": "parking at school is impossible.",
    "answer": "i'll say."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll say.",
    "answer": "i drove around for half an hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "i drove around for half an hour.",
    "answer": "did you find a spot?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you find a spot?",
    "answer": "i found a spot, but someone cut in and took it from me."
  },
  {
    "question": "i found a spot, but someone cut in and took it from me.",
    "answer": "did you yell at them?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you yell at them?",
    "answer": "yes, i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did.",
    "answer": "and?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and?",
    "answer": "and he yelled back at me."
  },
  {
    "question": "and he yelled back at me.",
    "answer": "how rude."
  },
  {
    "question": "how rude.",
    "answer": "but i got lucky a few minutes later."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i got lucky a few minutes later.",
    "answer": "you have to be lucky to find a parking space."
  },
  {
    "question": "this is a huge library.",
    "answer": "yes, it has lots of rooms and lots of space."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it has lots of rooms and lots of space.",
    "answer": "and lots of books."
  },
  {
    "question": "and lots of books.",
    "answer": "and lots of thieves."
  },
  {
    "question": "and lots of thieves.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i mean, keep your belongings close to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean, keep your belongings close to you.",
    "answer": "the only thing in my backpack is used books."
  },
  {
    "question": "the only thing in my backpack is used books.",
    "answer": "but thieves don't know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "but thieves don't know that.",
    "answer": "they might think that i've got an ipod or laptop in there."
  },
  {
    "question": "they might think that i've got an ipod or laptop in there.",
    "answer": "now you're thinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "now you're thinking.",
    "answer": "you'd think a library would be safe from thieves."
  },
  {
    "question": "you'd think a library would be safe from thieves.",
    "answer": "not even a church is safe from thieves."
  },
  {
    "question": "how good is your math?",
    "answer": "i can add two and two."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can add two and two.",
    "answer": "so you're not very good at math?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so you're not very good at math?",
    "answer": "i'm terrible at math."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm terrible at math.",
    "answer": "well, i need some help."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i need some help.",
    "answer": "with what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "with what?",
    "answer": "i'm taking a math course in school."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm taking a math course in school.",
    "answer": "well, you should ask your teacher or your classmates for help."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you should ask your teacher or your classmates for help.",
    "answer": "i can't do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't do that.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "they might think i'm stupid."
  },
  {
    "question": "they might think i'm stupid.",
    "answer": "they're not going to think that! they'll be glad to help you."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you believe in god?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "do you pray to god?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you pray to god?",
    "answer": "occasionally."
  },
  {
    "question": "occasionally.",
    "answer": "when's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when's that?",
    "answer": "when i need something."
  },
  {
    "question": "when i need something.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "well, if i have a big test at school."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, if i have a big test at school.",
    "answer": "does god answer your prayers?"
  },
  {
    "question": "does god answer your prayers?",
    "answer": "yes, i've passed all my tests."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i've passed all my tests.",
    "answer": "do you ever pray for money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you ever pray for money?",
    "answer": "not yet. i won't need to do that until i graduate from high school."
  },
  {
    "question": "the cops finally found the husband.",
    "answer": "what husband?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what husband?",
    "answer": "the husband of the driver who ran over two college students at 3 a.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "the husband of the driver who ran over two college students at 3 a.m.",
    "answer": "oh, yeah. the girl died instantly, and the boy is still in the hospital."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yeah. the girl died instantly, and the boy is still in the hospital.",
    "answer": "the husband said he tried to help the boy."
  },
  {
    "question": "the husband said he tried to help the boy.",
    "answer": "yes, he pushed him off the hood of the car."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he pushed him off the hood of the car.",
    "answer": "no, he said he gently placed the boy on the street."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, he said he gently placed the boy on the street.",
    "answer": "so what? they still drove off."
  },
  {
    "question": "so what? they still drove off.",
    "answer": "the husband said a fire department was nearby."
  },
  {
    "question": "the husband said a fire department was nearby.",
    "answer": "so what? did he dial 911?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what? did he dial 911?",
    "answer": "he said he was thinking about it, but he didn't get around to it."
  },
  {
    "question": "he said he was thinking about it, but he didn't get around to it.",
    "answer": "he didn't get around to turning himself in, either."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like riding the bus.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "the seats and windows are dirty."
  },
  {
    "question": "the seats and windows are dirty.",
    "answer": "don't they clean the bus every night?"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't they clean the bus every night?",
    "answer": "i think they do."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think they do.",
    "answer": "you should bring some wipes with you."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should bring some wipes with you.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "then you can wipe your seat and window."
  },
  {
    "question": "then you can wipe your seat and window.",
    "answer": "people will think i'm strange."
  },
  {
    "question": "people will think i'm strange.",
    "answer": "who cares? everyone is strange."
  },
  {
    "question": "who cares? everyone is strange.",
    "answer": "that's for sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's for sure.",
    "answer": "don't worry about what people think."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like riding the bus.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "number one, it's too slow."
  },
  {
    "question": "number one, it's too slow.",
    "answer": "you're right. a car is faster."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. a car is faster.",
    "answer": "number two, it's usually late."
  },
  {
    "question": "number two, it's usually late.",
    "answer": "you're right. the buses are never on time."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. the buses are never on time.",
    "answer": "number three, it doesn't run 24 hours."
  },
  {
    "question": "number three, it doesn't run 24 hours.",
    "answer": "you're right. buses don't run late at night."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. buses don't run late at night.",
    "answer": "number four, it's too crowded."
  },
  {
    "question": "number four, it's too crowded.",
    "answer": "you're right. you have to stand in the aisle."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right. you have to stand in the aisle.",
    "answer": "number five, it's unsafe."
  },
  {
    "question": "number five, it's unsafe.",
    "answer": "you're right. bad guys might rob you."
  },
  {
    "question": "we had a problem at school.",
    "answer": "what was the problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was the problem?",
    "answer": "someone cut the tires."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone cut the tires.",
    "answer": "what tires?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what tires?",
    "answer": "the tires on the cars."
  },
  {
    "question": "the tires on the cars.",
    "answer": "where were the cars?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where were the cars?",
    "answer": "they were in the student parking lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "they were in the student parking lot.",
    "answer": "how many tires were cut?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many tires were cut?",
    "answer": "one or two tires were cut on each car."
  },
  {
    "question": "one or two tires were cut on each car.",
    "answer": "how many cars?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many cars?",
    "answer": "eleven cars."
  },
  {
    "question": "eleven cars.",
    "answer": "that's terrible. i hope they catch the person."
  },
  {
    "question": "life isn't fair.",
    "answer": "it sure isn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sure isn't.",
    "answer": "i got a ticket yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a ticket yesterday.",
    "answer": "what for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what for?",
    "answer": "i was crossing the street."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was crossing the street.",
    "answer": "were you in a crosswalk?"
  },
  {
    "question": "were you in a crosswalk?",
    "answer": "yes, but the red hand was blinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but the red hand was blinking.",
    "answer": "so? that's a ticket?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so? that's a ticket?",
    "answer": "yes, it's a $140 ticket."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's a $140 ticket.",
    "answer": "that's not right!"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not right!",
    "answer": "when i started to cross the street, the white walk sign was blinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "when i started to cross the street, the white walk sign was blinking.",
    "answer": "you need to walk faster."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're driving too fast.",
    "answer": "why do you say that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you say that?",
    "answer": "the speed limit is 65."
  },
  {
    "question": "the speed limit is 65.",
    "answer": "i know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know that.",
    "answer": "but you're doing 75."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you're doing 75.",
    "answer": "so is everyone else."
  },
  {
    "question": "so is everyone else.",
    "answer": "but a cop might stop you."
  },
  {
    "question": "but a cop might stop you.",
    "answer": "no, he won't. some cars are doing 85."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, he won't. some cars are doing 85.",
    "answer": "so the cop will stop those cars?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so the cop will stop those cars?",
    "answer": "of course. he stops the fastest cars."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. he stops the fastest cars.",
    "answer": "my friend got a ticket for doing 75."
  },
  {
    "question": "my friend got a ticket for doing 75.",
    "answer": "your friend was unlucky."
  },
  {
    "question": "remember to put air in your tires.",
    "answer": "how often do i have to do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how often do i have to do that?",
    "answer": "once every two months."
  },
  {
    "question": "once every two months.",
    "answer": "that's a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a lot.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "that's six times a year!"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's six times a year!",
    "answer": "yes, and it takes about five minutes each time."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and it takes about five minutes each time.",
    "answer": "i'll try."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll try.",
    "answer": "check your tires or you'll get a flat."
  },
  {
    "question": "check your tires or you'll get a flat.",
    "answer": "oh. that's not good."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh. that's not good.",
    "answer": "no, it isn't. a flat costs you time and money."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it isn't. a flat costs you time and money.",
    "answer": "and i don't have either."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're driving too fast.",
    "answer": "i'm in a hurry."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm in a hurry.",
    "answer": "don't ever be in a hurry."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't ever be in a hurry.",
    "answer": "it's not my fault. you didn't wake me up."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not my fault. you didn't wake me up.",
    "answer": "that's not my fault. you didn't tell me to wake you up."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not my fault. you didn't tell me to wake you up.",
    "answer": "well, i meant to."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i meant to.",
    "answer": "don't ever be in a hurry when you're driving."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't ever be in a hurry when you're driving.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "because you'll have an accident. most accidents are because people are in a hurry."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you'll have an accident. most accidents are because people are in a hurry.",
    "answer": "how do you know that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you know that?",
    "answer": "i read a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i read a lot.",
    "answer": "i thought drunks caused most accidents."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go for a ride.",
    "answer": "where are we going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where are we going?",
    "answer": "into the mountains."
  },
  {
    "question": "into the mountains.",
    "answer": "that sounds nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds nice.",
    "answer": "i want to show you my new car."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to show you my new car.",
    "answer": "you bought a new car?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you bought a new car?",
    "answer": "yes. i bought a cadillac."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i bought a cadillac.",
    "answer": "a luxury car."
  },
  {
    "question": "a luxury car.",
    "answer": "luxury plus speed."
  },
  {
    "question": "luxury plus speed.",
    "answer": "what are we waiting for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are we waiting for?",
    "answer": "let me get the keys."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me get the keys.",
    "answer": "let me get my camera."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to go to the bathroom.",
    "answer": "why didn't you go before we left?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why didn't you go before we left?",
    "answer": "i did, but i have to go again."
  },
  {
    "question": "i did, but i have to go again.",
    "answer": "well, hold on a little longer."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, hold on a little longer.",
    "answer": "i think i'm going to explode."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i'm going to explode.",
    "answer": "just hold on."
  },
  {
    "question": "just hold on.",
    "answer": "oh! don't hit any more bumps!"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh! don't hit any more bumps!",
    "answer": "we'll be at mcdonald's in just a few minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll be at mcdonald's in just a few minutes.",
    "answer": "i hope they are fast minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope they are fast minutes.",
    "answer": "think about something else. think about a hamburger."
  },
  {
    "question": "think about something else. think about a hamburger.",
    "answer": "i'm thinking, but i still have to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm thinking, but i still have to go.",
    "answer": "it's the next exit. hold on!"
  },
  {
    "question": "where's the car?",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "the car isn't here."
  },
  {
    "question": "the car isn't here.",
    "answer": "where did you park it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where did you park it?",
    "answer": "i parked it right here."
  },
  {
    "question": "i parked it right here.",
    "answer": "are you sure?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you sure?",
    "answer": "yes. i remember this big tree."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i remember this big tree.",
    "answer": "maybe it's the wrong tree."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe it's the wrong tree.",
    "answer": "no, this is the tree."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, this is the tree.",
    "answer": "did someone steal it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did someone steal it?",
    "answer": "i sure hope not."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sure hope not.",
    "answer": "maybe they towed it away."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at this traffic.",
    "answer": "i'd rather not."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd rather not.",
    "answer": "it gets worse every year."
  },
  {
    "question": "it gets worse every year.",
    "answer": "why are you complaining? we're going almost 20 miles an hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "why are you complaining? we're going almost 20 miles an hour.",
    "answer": "the speed limit is 65!"
  },
  {
    "question": "the speed limit is 65!",
    "answer": "well, that's between 2:00 and 4:00 a.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, that's between 2:00 and 4:00 a.m.",
    "answer": "where are all these people going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where are all these people going?",
    "answer": "they're all asking the same question."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're all asking the same question.",
    "answer": "when are they going to fix this problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when are they going to fix this problem?",
    "answer": "they said they need more money."
  },
  {
    "question": "they said they need more money.",
    "answer": "they always need more money."
  },
  {
    "question": "they always need more money.",
    "answer": "it'll get worse before it gets better."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you see that car?",
    "answer": "yes, he went through the red light."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he went through the red light.",
    "answer": "can we call the police?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we call the police?",
    "answer": "no, the police don't care."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, the police don't care.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "they have to see it happen."
  },
  {
    "question": "they have to see it happen.",
    "answer": "they don't believe us?"
  },
  {
    "question": "they don't believe us?",
    "answer": "no. they can only give a ticket if they see it happen."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. they can only give a ticket if they see it happen.",
    "answer": "so, what do we do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so, what do we do?",
    "answer": "we don't do anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "we don't do anything.",
    "answer": "maybe we should honk the horn next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe we should honk the horn next time.",
    "answer": "the driver will just honk back at us."
  },
  {
    "question": "my car is dirty.",
    "answer": "why don't you wash it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why don't you wash it?",
    "answer": "that's what i'm going to do."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what i'm going to do.",
    "answer": "are you going to wash it yourself?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to wash it yourself?",
    "answer": "of course. it's not a hard job."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. it's not a hard job.",
    "answer": "i'll help you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll help you.",
    "answer": "okay, i'll get a bucket."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, i'll get a bucket.",
    "answer": "i'll rinse the car first."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll rinse the car first.",
    "answer": "then we can scrub it with a wet sponge and soap."
  },
  {
    "question": "then we can scrub it with a wet sponge and soap.",
    "answer": "after that, we can dry it with a towel."
  },
  {
    "question": "after that, we can dry it with a towel.",
    "answer": "then it will look like new"
  },
  {
    "question": "then it will look like new",
    "answer": "and you save $10."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sure is windy today.",
    "answer": "paper is flying everywhere."
  },
  {
    "question": "paper is flying everywhere.",
    "answer": "this wind is dangerous for drivers."
  },
  {
    "question": "this wind is dangerous for drivers.",
    "answer": "especially for drivers of big trucks."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially for drivers of big trucks.",
    "answer": "the wind blows those trucks over."
  },
  {
    "question": "the wind blows those trucks over.",
    "answer": "it blows trees over, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "it blows trees over, too.",
    "answer": "a tree fell onto my dad's car."
  },
  {
    "question": "a tree fell onto my dad's car.",
    "answer": "was there much damage?"
  },
  {
    "question": "was there much damage?",
    "answer": "my dad had to buy a new car."
  },
  {
    "question": "my dad had to buy a new car.",
    "answer": "wow! that's terrible."
  },
  {
    "question": "wow! that's terrible.",
    "answer": "never park your car under a tree."
  },
  {
    "question": "never park your car under a tree.",
    "answer": "the wind will get you, or the birds will get you."
  },
  {
    "question": "when are we going to stop?",
    "answer": "we'll stop at the next mcdonald's."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll stop at the next mcdonald's.",
    "answer": "how far away is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how far away is that?",
    "answer": "i think we'll be there in half an hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think we'll be there in half an hour.",
    "answer": "i hope so. i have to go to the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope so. i have to go to the bathroom.",
    "answer": "well, i can always pull over."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i can always pull over.",
    "answer": "no, thank you, i'll just wait."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, thank you, i'll just wait.",
    "answer": "we can kill two birds with one stone."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can kill two birds with one stone.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "while you're using the bathroom, i'll order some food."
  },
  {
    "question": "while you're using the bathroom, i'll order some food.",
    "answer": "don't order for me. i'm not hungry."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't order for me. i'm not hungry.",
    "answer": "i'm very hungry. i'll order for you, and then i'll eat yours."
  },
  {
    "question": "this is such a long light.",
    "answer": "look how many cars are waiting in line."
  },
  {
    "question": "look how many cars are waiting in line.",
    "answer": "they need a left-turn arrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "they need a left-turn arrow.",
    "answer": "only two cars can make a left turn every three or four minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "only two cars can make a left turn every three or four minutes.",
    "answer": "we'll be here forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll be here forever.",
    "answer": "get out of this lane."
  },
  {
    "question": "get out of this lane.",
    "answer": "but we need to turn left."
  },
  {
    "question": "but we need to turn left.",
    "answer": "forget it. go straight."
  },
  {
    "question": "forget it. go straight.",
    "answer": "then what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then what?",
    "answer": "then we'll just make a u-turn."
  },
  {
    "question": "then we'll just make a u-turn.",
    "answer": "and then we can turn right at the light."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then we can turn right at the light.",
    "answer": "good idea. it will be so much quicker."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need a cheap car.",
    "answer": "how much money do you have?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much money do you have?",
    "answer": "$1,000.00"
  },
  {
    "question": "$1,000.00",
    "answer": "well, that should get you something."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, that should get you something.",
    "answer": "but i need something that's reliable."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i need something that's reliable.",
    "answer": "you need a car with low mileage."
  },
  {
    "question": "you need a car with low mileage.",
    "answer": "a car that was owned by a little old lady."
  },
  {
    "question": "a car that was owned by a little old lady.",
    "answer": "where have you looked?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where have you looked?",
    "answer": "i haven't looked anywhere yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't looked anywhere yet.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "because i'll never find one for such a low price."
  },
  {
    "question": "because i'll never find one for such a low price.",
    "answer": "you're right about that. keep saving your money."
  },
  {
    "question": "good afternoon, officer.",
    "answer": "your driver's license and registration, please."
  },
  {
    "question": "your driver's license and registration, please.",
    "answer": "here you go."
  },
  {
    "question": "here you go.",
    "answer": "do you know why i pulled you over?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know why i pulled you over?",
    "answer": "i have no idea. all of a sudden i heard your siren."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have no idea. all of a sudden i heard your siren.",
    "answer": "you rolled through that stop sign back there."
  },
  {
    "question": "you rolled through that stop sign back there.",
    "answer": "but i stopped!"
  },
  {
    "question": "but i stopped!",
    "answer": "no, you didn't. you slowed down, but you didn't come to a full stop."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, you didn't. you slowed down, but you didn't come to a full stop.",
    "answer": "well, nobody else does, so why should i?"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, nobody else does, so why should i?",
    "answer": "that's not the attitude of a good driver."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not the attitude of a good driver.",
    "answer": "but i am a good driver. i've never had a ticket in my life."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i am a good driver. i've never had a ticket in my life.",
    "answer": "well, you've got one now. here. have a nice day."
  },
  {
    "question": "$140. i can't believe it.",
    "answer": "what are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you talking about?",
    "answer": "i got a ticket downtown for $140."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a ticket downtown for $140.",
    "answer": "were you speeding?"
  },
  {
    "question": "were you speeding?",
    "answer": "no, i was crossing the street."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i was crossing the street.",
    "answer": "were you jaywalking?"
  },
  {
    "question": "were you jaywalking?",
    "answer": "no, i was in the crosswalk."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i was in the crosswalk.",
    "answer": "so why did you get a ticket?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so why did you get a ticket?",
    "answer": "the officer said the red hand was blinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "the officer said the red hand was blinking.",
    "answer": "was it blinking when you entered the crosswalk?"
  },
  {
    "question": "was it blinking when you entered the crosswalk?",
    "answer": "no, the white walk sign was blinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, the white walk sign was blinking.",
    "answer": "you should fight that ticket. i'll be your witness."
  },
  {
    "question": "they were in a crosswalk near school at 3 a.m.",
    "answer": "who?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who?",
    "answer": "two students from usc."
  },
  {
    "question": "two students from usc.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "a speeding car ran a red light, killing the girl."
  },
  {
    "question": "a speeding car ran a red light, killing the girl.",
    "answer": "what happened to the other student?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened to the other student?",
    "answer": "he landed on the hood of the car."
  },
  {
    "question": "he landed on the hood of the car.",
    "answer": "did he get off the hood?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he get off the hood?",
    "answer": "no, the car stopped and the passenger pushed the injured student off the hood."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, the car stopped and the passenger pushed the injured student off the hood.",
    "answer": "i'll bet the car continued on its way."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll bet the car continued on its way.",
    "answer": "of course it did. why stop after you've run over two people?"
  },
  {
    "question": "of course it did. why stop after you've run over two people?",
    "answer": "i hope they find them and put them in jail for life."
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened to your car?",
    "answer": "i got a dent in the parking lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a dent in the parking lot.",
    "answer": "how did you get it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did you get it?",
    "answer": "i don't know. maybe it was from a shopping cart."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. maybe it was from a shopping cart.",
    "answer": "those shopping carts are dangerous."
  },
  {
    "question": "those shopping carts are dangerous.",
    "answer": "especially the metal ones."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially the metal ones.",
    "answer": "i don't park at a store that uses metal shopping carts."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't park at a store that uses metal shopping carts.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea, but there was a good sale at this store."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea, but there was a good sale at this store.",
    "answer": "did you save any money on the sale?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you save any money on the sale?",
    "answer": "yes, i did. i saved about $50."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did. i saved about $50.",
    "answer": "that's great."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's great.",
    "answer": "yes, except this dent will cost about $150."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you see \"titanic\"?",
    "answer": "yes. it is a great movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. it is a great movie.",
    "answer": "i saw it twelve times."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw it twelve times.",
    "answer": "i saw it eight times."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw it eight times.",
    "answer": "i have the dvd."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have the dvd.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "let's go to your home."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to your home.",
    "answer": "we can watch my dvd."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can watch my dvd.",
    "answer": "and then we can go to my home."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then we can go to my home.",
    "answer": "and watch your dvd."
  },
  {
    "question": "and watch your dvd.",
    "answer": "i always cry at the end."
  },
  {
    "question": "i always cry at the end.",
    "answer": "me too. it's so sad."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's play cards.",
    "answer": "i don't know any card games."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know any card games.",
    "answer": "i'll teach you one."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll teach you one.",
    "answer": "okay. what will you teach me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. what will you teach me?",
    "answer": "it's called poker."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's called poker.",
    "answer": "is it easy to learn?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it easy to learn?",
    "answer": "yes, it will only take about 30 minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it will only take about 30 minutes.",
    "answer": "okay. teach me how to play."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay. teach me how to play.",
    "answer": "we each get five cards."
  },
  {
    "question": "we each get five cards.",
    "answer": "oh, look. i have four tens."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, look. i have four tens.",
    "answer": "that's great, but you're not supposed to tell me."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's great, but you're not supposed to tell me.",
    "answer": "oh. sorry. okay, i don't have four tens."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm a good card player.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "because i watch the other players."
  },
  {
    "question": "because i watch the other players.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "people will tell you if they have a good hand."
  },
  {
    "question": "people will tell you if they have a good hand.",
    "answer": "how do they do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do they do that?",
    "answer": "for example, a friend of mine licks his lips."
  },
  {
    "question": "for example, a friend of mine licks his lips.",
    "answer": "when he licks his lips, you know he has a good hand?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when he licks his lips, you know he has a good hand?",
    "answer": "i know he has a good hand, so i don't bet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know he has a good hand, so i don't bet.",
    "answer": "he never wins your money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "he never wins your money?",
    "answer": "nope, and it drives him crazy."
  },
  {
    "question": "nope, and it drives him crazy.",
    "answer": "he knows you can't read his mind. maybe he thinks you're cheating."
  },
  {
    "question": "turn the radio down, please.",
    "answer": "but i'm listening to it."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i'm listening to it.",
    "answer": "well, listen to it more quietly."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, listen to it more quietly.",
    "answer": "i can't wait till i grow up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't wait till i grow up.",
    "answer": "what will you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what will you do?",
    "answer": "i will play the radio as loud as i want."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will play the radio as loud as i want.",
    "answer": "that's okay with me."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's okay with me.",
    "answer": "i will have a radio in every room of my house."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will have a radio in every room of my house.",
    "answer": "remind me to never visit you."
  },
  {
    "question": "remind me to never visit you.",
    "answer": "all the radios will be on extra loud."
  },
  {
    "question": "all the radios will be on extra loud.",
    "answer": "your neighbors will hate you."
  },
  {
    "question": "your neighbors will hate you.",
    "answer": "if they don't like it, they can move."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope i win the lotto.",
    "answer": "your chances are very small."
  },
  {
    "question": "your chances are very small.",
    "answer": "but you can't win if you don't play."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you can't win if you don't play.",
    "answer": "ha! you can't win if you do play."
  },
  {
    "question": "ha! you can't win if you do play.",
    "answer": "someone has to win."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone has to win.",
    "answer": "that's what everyone says."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what everyone says.",
    "answer": "it might as well be me."
  },
  {
    "question": "it might as well be me.",
    "answer": "that's what everyone says."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what everyone says.",
    "answer": "you're trying to tell me something."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're trying to tell me something.",
    "answer": "that didn't take long."
  },
  {
    "question": "that didn't take long.",
    "answer": "you think i should quit playing."
  },
  {
    "question": "you think i should quit playing.",
    "answer": "save your money for school."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's on tv?",
    "answer": "nothing much."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing much.",
    "answer": "what about the baseball game?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about the baseball game?",
    "answer": "it got rained out."
  },
  {
    "question": "it got rained out.",
    "answer": "rained out?"
  },
  {
    "question": "rained out?",
    "answer": "yes, rained out."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, rained out.",
    "answer": "how could that be?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how could that be?",
    "answer": "well, you can't play baseball in a rainstorm."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you can't play baseball in a rainstorm.",
    "answer": "i thought they were playing under a dome."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought they were playing under a dome.",
    "answer": "the dome doesn't close."
  },
  {
    "question": "the dome doesn't close.",
    "answer": "why doesn't it close?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why doesn't it close?",
    "answer": "who knows? they said they'll fix it before next season."
  },
  {
    "question": "can i try your coffee?",
    "answer": "sure. here you go."
  },
  {
    "question": "sure. here you go.",
    "answer": "hmm, that's not bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "hmm, that's not bad.",
    "answer": "there's nothing in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's nothing in it.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i mean, it's just coffee."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean, it's just coffee.",
    "answer": "i figured that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i figured that.",
    "answer": "it's not too bitter for you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not too bitter for you?",
    "answer": "it's a little bitter, but it's okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a little bitter, but it's okay.",
    "answer": "there's no sugar or cream in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's no sugar or cream in it.",
    "answer": "no, it's a taste you have to get used to."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's a taste you have to get used to.",
    "answer": "sort of like beer."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's take a walk.",
    "answer": "what's the weather like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the weather like?",
    "answer": "let me step outside and see."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me step outside and see.",
    "answer": "it's a little chilly, right?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a little chilly, right?",
    "answer": "yes, it is."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it is.",
    "answer": "i'll put on my cap."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll put on my cap.",
    "answer": "wear a jacket, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "wear a jacket, too.",
    "answer": "i wonder if i should bring my gloves."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wonder if i should bring my gloves.",
    "answer": "maybe you should, just in case it gets colder."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you should, just in case it gets colder.",
    "answer": "i'll put a glove in each pocket."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll put a glove in each pocket.",
    "answer": "we'll get warmer as we walk."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll get warmer as we walk.",
    "answer": "yes, but it gets colder as the sun goes down."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at the car chase on tv!",
    "answer": "that driver is crazy."
  },
  {
    "question": "that driver is crazy.",
    "answer": "i can't believe he hasn't crashed."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe he hasn't crashed.",
    "answer": "how fast is he going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how fast is he going?",
    "answer": "they say he's going 80 miles per hour."
  },
  {
    "question": "they say he's going 80 miles per hour.",
    "answer": "he's going to kill someone."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's going to kill someone.",
    "answer": "look! he just hit that car."
  },
  {
    "question": "look! he just hit that car.",
    "answer": "oh, my goodness. no one is safe on the streets."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, my goodness. no one is safe on the streets.",
    "answer": "now he's slowing down."
  },
  {
    "question": "now he's slowing down.",
    "answer": "maybe he ran out of gas."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe he ran out of gas.",
    "answer": "look! he just got out of the car and started running."
  },
  {
    "question": "look! he just got out of the car and started running.",
    "answer": "i hope the police catch him."
  },
  {
    "question": "tv news is so stupid.",
    "answer": "they shouldn't even call it news."
  },
  {
    "question": "they shouldn't even call it news.",
    "answer": "last night they told us about a cat in a sofa."
  },
  {
    "question": "last night they told us about a cat in a sofa.",
    "answer": "yesterday they told us about a dog in a pipe."
  },
  {
    "question": "yesterday they told us about a dog in a pipe.",
    "answer": "last week they told us about a bear in a back yard."
  },
  {
    "question": "last week they told us about a bear in a back yard.",
    "answer": "last month they told us about a mouse in a restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "last month they told us about a mouse in a restaurant.",
    "answer": "the weatherman tells us the temperature in every town."
  },
  {
    "question": "the weatherman tells us the temperature in every town.",
    "answer": "the sports guy shows us players fighting."
  },
  {
    "question": "the sports guy shows us players fighting.",
    "answer": "they always tell us \"what's next."
  },
  {
    "question": "they always tell us \"what's next.",
    "answer": "they always make \"what's next\" sound exciting, but it never is."
  },
  {
    "question": "they always make \"what's next\" sound exciting, but it never is.",
    "answer": "it's more like news for kids."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's more like news for kids.",
    "answer": "they should have kid reporters."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love my computer.",
    "answer": "computers are so cool."
  },
  {
    "question": "computers are so cool.",
    "answer": "i love to go online."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love to go online.",
    "answer": "the internet is amazing."
  },
  {
    "question": "the internet is amazing.",
    "answer": "you can travel all over the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can travel all over the world.",
    "answer": "i know. i went to china yesterday."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know. i went to china yesterday.",
    "answer": "what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do?",
    "answer": "i stood on the great wall and looked all around."
  },
  {
    "question": "i stood on the great wall and looked all around.",
    "answer": "what was it like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was it like?",
    "answer": "it was like the real thing."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was like the real thing.",
    "answer": "it was like being there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it was like being there?",
    "answer": "yes, i felt like i was actually there."
  },
  {
    "question": "the beatles are the best.",
    "answer": "they are the best musical group ever."
  },
  {
    "question": "they are the best musical group ever.",
    "answer": "i love all their songs."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love all their songs.",
    "answer": "i don't know which one i like the best."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know which one i like the best.",
    "answer": "i like the ones i can sing along with."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the ones i can sing along with.",
    "answer": "so do i, like \"she loves you."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i, like \"she loves you.",
    "answer": "she loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah!..."
  },
  {
    "question": "she loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah!...",
    "answer": "Â…and you know you should be glad!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Â…and you know you should be glad!",
    "answer": "what a great song."
  },
  {
    "question": "what a great song.",
    "answer": "how about \"let it be?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about \"let it be?",
    "answer": "oh, yes! \"let it be, let it beÂ…"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes! \"let it be, let it beÂ…",
    "answer": "Â…there will be an answer, let it be!"
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to a movie.",
    "answer": "i'd rather not."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd rather not.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "you know i don't like crowds."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know i don't like crowds.",
    "answer": "let's go to an early movie."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to an early movie.",
    "answer": "okay, that won't be very crowded."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, that won't be very crowded.",
    "answer": "what would you like to see?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what would you like to see?",
    "answer": "oh, i don't care. you're the one who wants to go out."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, i don't care. you're the one who wants to go out.",
    "answer": "well, i want to see \"the pursuit of happyness."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i want to see \"the pursuit of happyness.",
    "answer": "what have you heard about it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what have you heard about it?",
    "answer": "it's based on a true story about a divorced man and his young son."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's based on a true story about a divorced man and his young son.",
    "answer": "well, i hope it has a happy ending."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's your favorite thing to do?",
    "answer": "i like to watch people."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to watch people.",
    "answer": "that's your favorite thing to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's your favorite thing to do?",
    "answer": "well, it's one of them."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's one of them.",
    "answer": "where do you go to watch people?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you go to watch people?",
    "answer": "my girlfriend and i sit outside starbucks."
  },
  {
    "question": "my girlfriend and i sit outside starbucks.",
    "answer": "that sounds like a good spot."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like a good spot.",
    "answer": "we watch people walk by with their dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "we watch people walk by with their dogs.",
    "answer": "i guess you see lots of different dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess you see lots of different dogs.",
    "answer": "we don't even know what kind most of them are."
  },
  {
    "question": "we don't even know what kind most of them are.",
    "answer": "there are lots of different kinds, but they all have one thing in common."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are lots of different kinds, but they all have one thing in common.",
    "answer": "yes, they love to sniff each other when they meet."
  },
  {
    "question": "they call him father dollar bill.",
    "answer": "yes, he was on the tv news today."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he was on the tv news today.",
    "answer": "every easter sunday he gives away money."
  },
  {
    "question": "every easter sunday he gives away money.",
    "answer": "is it his money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it his money?",
    "answer": "no. movie stars give him money to give to homeless people."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. movie stars give him money to give to homeless people.",
    "answer": "how much money does he give away?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much money does he give away?",
    "answer": "this year he gave away $15,000."
  },
  {
    "question": "this year he gave away $15,000.",
    "answer": "that's a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a lot of money.",
    "answer": "he gave $100 to people in wheelchairs."
  },
  {
    "question": "he gave $100 to people in wheelchairs.",
    "answer": "what about the other homeless people?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about the other homeless people?",
    "answer": "they got $1 each."
  },
  {
    "question": "they got $1 each.",
    "answer": "people stood in line just to get one dollar?!"
  },
  {
    "question": "old movies are the best.",
    "answer": "even though they're in black and white."
  },
  {
    "question": "even though they're in black and white.",
    "answer": "a good story is more important than color."
  },
  {
    "question": "a good story is more important than color.",
    "answer": "actors didn't curse back then."
  },
  {
    "question": "actors didn't curse back then.",
    "answer": "and there was no violence."
  },
  {
    "question": "and there was no violence.",
    "answer": "people today don't like that."
  },
  {
    "question": "people today don't like that.",
    "answer": "no, today people like lots of action."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, today people like lots of action.",
    "answer": "i like a good story."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like a good story.",
    "answer": "i like to see actors who are like real people."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to see actors who are like real people.",
    "answer": "like real people with real problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "like real people with real problems.",
    "answer": "they still make movies like that."
  },
  {
    "question": "they still make movies like that.",
    "answer": "yes, but they never make much money."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you get pbs on tv?",
    "answer": "yes, everybody gets the public broadcasting system."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, everybody gets the public broadcasting system.",
    "answer": "it puts me to sleep."
  },
  {
    "question": "it puts me to sleep.",
    "answer": "tell me about it."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me about it.",
    "answer": "a gardening show follows a knitting show."
  },
  {
    "question": "a gardening show follows a knitting show.",
    "answer": "a cooking show follows a sewing show."
  },
  {
    "question": "a cooking show follows a sewing show.",
    "answer": "a travel show follows another travel show."
  },
  {
    "question": "a travel show follows another travel show.",
    "answer": "i'll say! i've gone around the world a dozen times already!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll say! i've gone around the world a dozen times already!",
    "answer": "now they're adding old tv shows to the old movies."
  },
  {
    "question": "now they're adding old tv shows to the old movies.",
    "answer": "i sure would like to see something interesting for a change."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sure would like to see something interesting for a change.",
    "answer": "if more people donate money, pbs could offer new shows."
  },
  {
    "question": "if more people donate money, pbs could offer new shows.",
    "answer": "who wants to donate? public tv should be free."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love to watch \"judge judy.",
    "answer": "is that a tv show?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that a tv show?",
    "answer": "yes. it's on every afternoon."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. it's on every afternoon.",
    "answer": "what's so good about it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's so good about it?",
    "answer": "they have interesting lawsuits."
  },
  {
    "question": "they have interesting lawsuits.",
    "answer": "such as?"
  },
  {
    "question": "such as?",
    "answer": "yesterday, a woman complained about a cell phone she bought on ebay."
  },
  {
    "question": "yesterday, a woman complained about a cell phone she bought on ebay.",
    "answer": "was something wrong with the phone?"
  },
  {
    "question": "was something wrong with the phone?",
    "answer": "it works only in canada."
  },
  {
    "question": "it works only in canada.",
    "answer": "did the seller know that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did the seller know that?",
    "answer": "yes, and he didn't tell the buyer."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and he didn't tell the buyer.",
    "answer": "i hope judge judy made the seller take the phone back."
  },
  {
    "question": "that woman is a very good singer.",
    "answer": "yes, but she looks like a man."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but she looks like a man.",
    "answer": "what difference does it make?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what difference does it make?",
    "answer": "female singers are supposed to be pretty."
  },
  {
    "question": "female singers are supposed to be pretty.",
    "answer": "singers are supposed to sound good."
  },
  {
    "question": "singers are supposed to sound good.",
    "answer": "they should look good, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "they should look good, too.",
    "answer": "there are lots of ugly men singers."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are lots of ugly men singers.",
    "answer": "men singers don't have to look good."
  },
  {
    "question": "men singers don't have to look good.",
    "answer": "then neither do women singers."
  },
  {
    "question": "then neither do women singers.",
    "answer": "well, i would never buy her cd."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i would never buy her cd.",
    "answer": "but you would buy her cd if she was pretty?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but you would buy her cd if she was pretty?",
    "answer": "yes. i would buy all of her cds."
  },
  {
    "question": "all the tv stations are going to go digital.",
    "answer": "yes, that will occur next month."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, that will occur next month.",
    "answer": "most of them are already broadcasting in digital."
  },
  {
    "question": "most of them are already broadcasting in digital.",
    "answer": "the digital signal is very clear."
  },
  {
    "question": "the digital signal is very clear.",
    "answer": "oh, no, it isn't!"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no, it isn't!",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i can't get a single channel."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't get a single channel.",
    "answer": "do you have a digital tv?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you have a digital tv?",
    "answer": "of course. but i don't have cable."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. but i don't have cable.",
    "answer": "you don't need to have cable, but you do need a good antenna."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't need to have cable, but you do need a good antenna.",
    "answer": "but i have rabbit ears."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i have rabbit ears.",
    "answer": "rabbit ears aren't strong enough. buy a digital antenna."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've got a date for you.",
    "answer": "oh, really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, really?",
    "answer": "are you interested?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you interested?",
    "answer": "maybe. what is she like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe. what is she like?",
    "answer": "she's got a great personality."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's got a great personality.",
    "answer": "uh-oh. that means that she's fat and ugly."
  },
  {
    "question": "uh-oh. that means that she's fat and ugly.",
    "answer": "she's cute."
  },
  {
    "question": "she's cute.",
    "answer": "okay, so she's not ugly; she's just fat."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, so she's not ugly; she's just fat.",
    "answer": "she weighs 98 pounds."
  },
  {
    "question": "she weighs 98 pounds.",
    "answer": "okay, she's not fat. so what's the problem with her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, she's not fat. so what's the problem with her?",
    "answer": "who said there is a problem with her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who said there is a problem with her?",
    "answer": "the problem is she has no problemsÂ—she's too good for me!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think you're very pretty.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "would you have dinner with me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "would you have dinner with me?",
    "answer": "i would like to."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would like to.",
    "answer": "can i pick you up friday night?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i pick you up friday night?",
    "answer": "what time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time?",
    "answer": "eight o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "eight o'clock.",
    "answer": "that sounds great."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds great.",
    "answer": "we'll go to a french restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll go to a french restaurant.",
    "answer": "i've never been to a french restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've never been to a french restaurant.",
    "answer": "i think you'll love the food."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think you'll love the food.",
    "answer": "i'm not going to eat any snails!"
  },
  {
    "question": "you have pretty eyes.",
    "answer": "thank you. so do you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you. so do you.",
    "answer": "i wish my eyes were blue."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish my eyes were blue.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with green eyes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with green eyes?",
    "answer": "nothing, except my favorite color is blue."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing, except my favorite color is blue.",
    "answer": "maybe in your next life you'll have blue eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe in your next life you'll have blue eyes.",
    "answer": "but what if i'm a fish in my next life?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but what if i'm a fish in my next life?",
    "answer": "i think some fish have blue eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think some fish have blue eyes.",
    "answer": "i hope i don't come back as a fish."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope i don't come back as a fish.",
    "answer": "i hope i come back as a cat."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope i come back as a cat.",
    "answer": "cats have beautiful eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "cats have beautiful eyes.",
    "answer": "i would love to have blue cat-eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love you.",
    "answer": "i love you, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love you, too.",
    "answer": "i loved you the first day i saw you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i loved you the first day i saw you.",
    "answer": "it was love at first sight?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it was love at first sight?",
    "answer": "yes, it was love at first sight."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it was love at first sight.",
    "answer": "i didn't love you at first."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't love you at first.",
    "answer": "i know. i had to chase you for a while."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know. i had to chase you for a while.",
    "answer": "yes, you chased me and then you caught me."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, you chased me and then you caught me.",
    "answer": "now you're mine forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "now you're mine forever.",
    "answer": "and you're mine forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "and you're mine forever.",
    "answer": "we'll grow old together."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll grow old together.",
    "answer": "and be happy together."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm in love with that girl.",
    "answer": "have you told her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you told her?",
    "answer": "of course not."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course not.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "she would laugh at me."
  },
  {
    "question": "she would laugh at me.",
    "answer": "how do you know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you know?",
    "answer": "because they always do."
  },
  {
    "question": "because they always do.",
    "answer": "maybe she's different."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe she's different.",
    "answer": "they're all the same."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're all the same.",
    "answer": "just ask her out to dinner."
  },
  {
    "question": "just ask her out to dinner.",
    "answer": "and then what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and then what?",
    "answer": "and then she'll know that you like her."
  },
  {
    "question": "give me a hug.",
    "answer": "i'm not in the mood."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not in the mood.",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "i saw you looking at that woman."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw you looking at that woman.",
    "answer": "what woman?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what woman?",
    "answer": "you know, that woman with the big boobs."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know, that woman with the big boobs.",
    "answer": "i was not looking at her."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was not looking at her.",
    "answer": "you were, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "you were, too.",
    "answer": "i'm not interested in her."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not interested in her.",
    "answer": "then why were you looking at her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why were you looking at her?",
    "answer": "i was looking at something else."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was looking at something else.",
    "answer": "oh, really? then spend tonight looking at the sofa."
  },
  {
    "question": "would you like to go on a blind date?",
    "answer": "you must be joking."
  },
  {
    "question": "you must be joking.",
    "answer": "no, i'm serious."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i'm serious.",
    "answer": "i don't want to date a blind woman."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't want to date a blind woman.",
    "answer": "a blind date doesn't mean that she is blind!"
  },
  {
    "question": "a blind date doesn't mean that she is blind!",
    "answer": "what does it mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does it mean?",
    "answer": "a blind date is a date with someone you don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "a blind date is a date with someone you don't know.",
    "answer": "why would i date someone i don't even know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why would i date someone i don't even know?",
    "answer": "to try something new and exciting."
  },
  {
    "question": "to try something new and exciting.",
    "answer": "what if i don't like her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what if i don't like her?",
    "answer": "then you don't date her again."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have a date tomorrow night.",
    "answer": "really? who with?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really? who with?",
    "answer": "a girl i met at the market."
  },
  {
    "question": "a girl i met at the market.",
    "answer": "you met a girl at the supermarket?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you met a girl at the supermarket?",
    "answer": "she was standing behind me in a really slow line at the checkout counter."
  },
  {
    "question": "she was standing behind me in a really slow line at the checkout counter.",
    "answer": "what did you say to her?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you say to her?",
    "answer": "i had two pineapples in my cart, and she asked where i had found them."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had two pineapples in my cart, and she asked where i had found them.",
    "answer": "she asked you about your pineapples?"
  },
  {
    "question": "she asked you about your pineapples?",
    "answer": "i told her i had gotten the last two on the shelf, but i offered her one of mine."
  },
  {
    "question": "i told her i had gotten the last two on the shelf, but i offered her one of mine.",
    "answer": "that was nice of you."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was nice of you.",
    "answer": "she asked me how she could return the favor, so i asked her out."
  },
  {
    "question": "she asked me how she could return the favor, so i asked her out.",
    "answer": "sometimes a slow line can be a good thing."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you have a date friday night?",
    "answer": "yes, in fact, i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, in fact, i did.",
    "answer": "who did you go out with?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who did you go out with?",
    "answer": "a man i met in a coffee shop."
  },
  {
    "question": "a man i met in a coffee shop.",
    "answer": "where did you go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where did you go?",
    "answer": "we went to a nice restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "we went to a nice restaurant.",
    "answer": "anywhere else?"
  },
  {
    "question": "anywhere else?",
    "answer": "then we went to a jazz club."
  },
  {
    "question": "then we went to a jazz club.",
    "answer": "that sounds like a nice date."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like a nice date.",
    "answer": "yes, it was pleasant."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it was pleasant.",
    "answer": "but you won't date him again?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but you won't date him again?",
    "answer": "no. he was nice, but there was no chemistry."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had the worst date the other night.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "first of all, he was half an hour late."
  },
  {
    "question": "first of all, he was half an hour late.",
    "answer": "that's not a good start."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not a good start.",
    "answer": "then he didn't bother to apologize."
  },
  {
    "question": "then he didn't bother to apologize.",
    "answer": "that's rude."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's rude.",
    "answer": "then he drove too fast to the restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "then he drove too fast to the restaurant.",
    "answer": "that's dangerous."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's dangerous.",
    "answer": "i thought about getting out and taking a taxi home."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought about getting out and taking a taxi home.",
    "answer": "what happened at the restaurant?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened at the restaurant?",
    "answer": "we had a $40 meal, and he left a $1 tip!"
  },
  {
    "question": "we had a $40 meal, and he left a $1 tip!",
    "answer": "i guess you can't go back to that restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like that man.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "he's a dirty old man."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's a dirty old man.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "he's old enough to be my father, yet he asked me out."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's old enough to be my father, yet he asked me out.",
    "answer": "well, you can't blame a man for asking."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you can't blame a man for asking.",
    "answer": "he should act his age."
  },
  {
    "question": "he should act his age.",
    "answer": "but a lot of old people are still interested in dating."
  },
  {
    "question": "but a lot of old people are still interested in dating.",
    "answer": "they should find a nice hobby."
  },
  {
    "question": "they should find a nice hobby.",
    "answer": "just wait until you're 50 years old."
  },
  {
    "question": "just wait until you're 50 years old.",
    "answer": "dating will be the furthest thing from my mind."
  },
  {
    "question": "dating will be the furthest thing from my mind.",
    "answer": "that's what you say now. wait till you're 50."
  },
  {
    "question": "does your girlfriend ever make you angry?",
    "answer": "sometimes."
  },
  {
    "question": "sometimes.",
    "answer": "what does she do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does she do?",
    "answer": "just yesterday, i told her i wouldn't trade her for all the money in the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "just yesterday, i told her i wouldn't trade her for all the money in the world.",
    "answer": "that was a nice thing to say."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a nice thing to say.",
    "answer": "that's what i thought."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's what i thought.",
    "answer": "what did she say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did she say?",
    "answer": "she laughed! she didn't believe me."
  },
  {
    "question": "she laughed! she didn't believe me.",
    "answer": "that wasn't very nice of her."
  },
  {
    "question": "that wasn't very nice of her.",
    "answer": "she said that nothing is more important to me than money."
  },
  {
    "question": "she said that nothing is more important to me than money.",
    "answer": "what did you say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you say?",
    "answer": "i told her i wouldn't trade her for any other woman in the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "some people have good noses.",
    "answer": "i wish i had a good nose. mine is way too big."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i had a good nose. mine is way too big.",
    "answer": "i don't mean good-looking. i mean good-smelling."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't mean good-looking. i mean good-smelling.",
    "answer": "oh. but that can be a curse."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh. but that can be a curse.",
    "answer": "yes, because you can be too sensitive to odors."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, because you can be too sensitive to odors.",
    "answer": "i'll say. my girlfriend has a nose like a drug dog."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll say. my girlfriend has a nose like a drug dog.",
    "answer": "did she catch you using drugs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did she catch you using drugs?",
    "answer": "sort of. she knows whenever i sneak a cigarette."
  },
  {
    "question": "sort of. she knows whenever i sneak a cigarette.",
    "answer": "you don't need a good nose for thatÂ—cigarettes stink."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't need a good nose for thatÂ—cigarettes stink.",
    "answer": "but when i sneak just one cigarette in the morning, she can smell it that evening!"
  },
  {
    "question": "but when i sneak just one cigarette in the morning, she can smell it that evening!",
    "answer": "boy, that is a good nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "boy, that is a good nose.",
    "answer": "i told her she should apply for a job at customs."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go out to eat.",
    "answer": "that sounds like fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like fun.",
    "answer": "where do you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you want to go?",
    "answer": "let me think a minute."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me think a minute.",
    "answer": "i feel like chinese."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel like chinese.",
    "answer": "that sounds delicious."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds delicious.",
    "answer": "i know a good chinese restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know a good chinese restaurant.",
    "answer": "how far away is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how far away is it?",
    "answer": "it's only 10 minutes from here."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's only 10 minutes from here.",
    "answer": "do we need reservations?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do we need reservations?",
    "answer": "oh, no. we can walk right in."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, no. we can walk right in.",
    "answer": "let's go now. i'm hungry!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe how long this line is.",
    "answer": "this is a popular restaurant, isn't it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is a popular restaurant, isn't it?",
    "answer": "yes, but it isn't a fast-food restaurant, is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but it isn't a fast-food restaurant, is it?",
    "answer": "it's the slowest hamburger in town."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the slowest hamburger in town.",
    "answer": "that's because they cook it while you wait."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's because they cook it while you wait.",
    "answer": "yes. that's why it's also the best hamburger in town."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. that's why it's also the best hamburger in town.",
    "answer": "a great burger and great service."
  },
  {
    "question": "a great burger and great service.",
    "answer": "yes, the workers are very polite."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, the workers are very polite.",
    "answer": "and they're clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "and they're clean.",
    "answer": "i've been coming here for years."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been coming here for years.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "excuse me. they just called my number."
  },
  {
    "question": "lunch was delicious.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "what kind of soup was that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of soup was that?",
    "answer": "it was tomato soup."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was tomato soup.",
    "answer": "that tasted so good."
  },
  {
    "question": "that tasted so good.",
    "answer": "i put lemon and butter in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i put lemon and butter in it.",
    "answer": "the sandwich was good, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "the sandwich was good, too.",
    "answer": "everyone likes bacon and tomato sandwiches."
  },
  {
    "question": "everyone likes bacon and tomato sandwiches.",
    "answer": "especially on toast."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially on toast.",
    "answer": "and the pickles were great, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "and the pickles were great, too.",
    "answer": "tomorrow we'll have rice and fish for lunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "tomorrow we'll have rice and fish for lunch.",
    "answer": "i can't wait."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm calling the waiter.",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "this steak has too much fat."
  },
  {
    "question": "this steak has too much fat.",
    "answer": "what do you want the waiter to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you want the waiter to do?",
    "answer": "bring me a better steak."
  },
  {
    "question": "bring me a better steak.",
    "answer": "i wouldn't do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wouldn't do that.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "they will drop the new steak on the floor, step on it, and then spit on it."
  },
  {
    "question": "they will drop the new steak on the floor, step on it, and then spit on it.",
    "answer": "you're crazy."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're crazy.",
    "answer": "then the waiter will give you a big smile as he brings you the new steak."
  },
  {
    "question": "then the waiter will give you a big smile as he brings you the new steak.",
    "answer": "where do you get these crazy ideas?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you get these crazy ideas?",
    "answer": "i used to cook in a restaurant!"
  },
  {
    "question": "let's leave.",
    "answer": "but we just got here."
  },
  {
    "question": "but we just got here.",
    "answer": "did you see the waiter's hands?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you see the waiter's hands?",
    "answer": "no."
  },
  {
    "question": "no.",
    "answer": "he had dirty fingernails."
  },
  {
    "question": "he had dirty fingernails.",
    "answer": "really?"
  },
  {
    "question": "really?",
    "answer": "his nails were black!"
  },
  {
    "question": "his nails were black!",
    "answer": "that's disgusting."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's disgusting.",
    "answer": "and he poured water into our glasses."
  },
  {
    "question": "and he poured water into our glasses.",
    "answer": "yuck! no water for me."
  },
  {
    "question": "yuck! no water for me.",
    "answer": "i wonder if the cooks' nails are dirty, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wonder if the cooks' nails are dirty, too.",
    "answer": "who cares? let's get out of here."
  },
  {
    "question": "this hot bread is delicious.",
    "answer": "i like this restaurant because they give you free bread."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like this restaurant because they give you free bread.",
    "answer": "well, i think we are paying for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i think we are paying for it.",
    "answer": "no. look at the bill when we get it. there's no charge for the bread."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. look at the bill when we get it. there's no charge for the bread.",
    "answer": "it is delicious, especially with butter."
  },
  {
    "question": "it is delicious, especially with butter.",
    "answer": "i think we should just leave after we fill up on the bread."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think we should just leave after we fill up on the bread.",
    "answer": "they probably wouldn't like that."
  },
  {
    "question": "they probably wouldn't like that.",
    "answer": "i'm eating so much bread that i'm getting full."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm eating so much bread that i'm getting full.",
    "answer": "then stop eating the bread!"
  },
  {
    "question": "then stop eating the bread!",
    "answer": "okay, just one more piece. pass the butter, please."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, just one more piece. pass the butter, please.",
    "answer": "if i owned a restaurant, i would never serve hot bread before the main course."
  },
  {
    "question": "if i owned a restaurant, i would never serve hot bread before the main course.",
    "answer": "that's terrible. i would never go to your restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "is this a clean restaurant?",
    "answer": "well, the tables and chairs look okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, the tables and chairs look okay.",
    "answer": "okay, let's sit down."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, let's sit down.",
    "answer": "check out the silverware."
  },
  {
    "question": "check out the silverware.",
    "answer": "it passes inspection."
  },
  {
    "question": "it passes inspection.",
    "answer": "here comes the waiter. see if his hands and nails are clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "here comes the waiter. see if his hands and nails are clean.",
    "answer": "well, the waiter looked clean, so i guess it's okay to eat here."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, the waiter looked clean, so i guess it's okay to eat here.",
    "answer": "you're forgetting about the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're forgetting about the bathroom.",
    "answer": "i'm going to just hope that the bathroom is clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to just hope that the bathroom is clean.",
    "answer": "you're not going to examine it before we order dinner?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you're not going to examine it before we order dinner?",
    "answer": "no, i'd rather not find out that it's dirty, because i'm pretty hungry right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i'd rather not find out that it's dirty, because i'm pretty hungry right now.",
    "answer": "me, too. let's forget about germs and focus on food."
  },
  {
    "question": "have you seen our waiter?",
    "answer": "here he comes now."
  },
  {
    "question": "here he comes now.",
    "answer": "we've been sitting here for almost 10 minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "we've been sitting here for almost 10 minutes.",
    "answer": "oops, i guess i was wrong. that isn't our waiter."
  },
  {
    "question": "oops, i guess i was wrong. that isn't our waiter.",
    "answer": "we can give him five more minutes, and then leave."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can give him five more minutes, and then leave.",
    "answer": "i'll go up front and talk to the manager."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll go up front and talk to the manager.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "maybe they'll give us free drinks for waiting so long."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe they'll give us free drinks for waiting so long.",
    "answer": "maybe he'll send us our waiter immediately."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe he'll send us our waiter immediately.",
    "answer": "every time we eat out, it's an adventure."
  },
  {
    "question": "every time we eat out, it's an adventure.",
    "answer": "last time, we got seats next to the kitchen."
  },
  {
    "question": "last time, we got seats next to the kitchen.",
    "answer": "we'll never go there again."
  },
  {
    "question": "is this table okay?",
    "answer": "no, it's too close to the kitchen door."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's too close to the kitchen door.",
    "answer": "how about this table?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how about this table?",
    "answer": "no, it's too close to the front door."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's too close to the front door.",
    "answer": "this looks like a nice table."
  },
  {
    "question": "this looks like a nice table.",
    "answer": "no, it's too close to the salad bar."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's too close to the salad bar.",
    "answer": "okay, i give up."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, i give up.",
    "answer": "well, there is one good table."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, there is one good table.",
    "answer": "great. which one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "great. which one?",
    "answer": "that one. a group of eight just sat down at it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't believe the art world.",
    "answer": "what is it this time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is it this time?",
    "answer": "an andy warhol drawing."
  },
  {
    "question": "an andy warhol drawing.",
    "answer": "he's a famous artist."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's a famous artist.",
    "answer": "he drew two butterflies and a flower on a napkin in a restaurant."
  },
  {
    "question": "he drew two butterflies and a flower on a napkin in a restaurant.",
    "answer": "did he sign it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he sign it?",
    "answer": "yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes.",
    "answer": "is it beautiful?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it beautiful?",
    "answer": "it's just black ink on a white napkin. and the napkin has food stains!"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's just black ink on a white napkin. and the napkin has food stains!",
    "answer": "so it's not worth much?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so it's not worth much?",
    "answer": "only about $30,000."
  },
  {
    "question": "only about $30,000.",
    "answer": "without the food stains, it would probably be worth more."
  },
  {
    "question": "can we go to the baseball game?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "i love baseball."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love baseball.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "i love to eat the peanuts."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love to eat the peanuts.",
    "answer": "i love to eat the hot dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love to eat the hot dogs.",
    "answer": "i hope we'll see a home run."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope we'll see a home run.",
    "answer": "i hope we'll catch a foul ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope we'll catch a foul ball.",
    "answer": "bring a jacket."
  },
  {
    "question": "bring a jacket.",
    "answer": "yes. it gets a little cool at night."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. it gets a little cool at night.",
    "answer": "bring a glove to catch a foul ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "bring a glove to catch a foul ball.",
    "answer": "no. i'll just use my cap to catch a foul ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "golf is a silly game.",
    "answer": "it certainly is."
  },
  {
    "question": "it certainly is.",
    "answer": "you hit a white ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "you hit a white ball.",
    "answer": "and then you chase it."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then you chase it.",
    "answer": "and then you hit it again."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then you hit it again.",
    "answer": "finally, you put the ball into a hole in the ground."
  },
  {
    "question": "finally, you put the ball into a hole in the ground.",
    "answer": "you do this 18 times, because there are 18 holes."
  },
  {
    "question": "you do this 18 times, because there are 18 holes.",
    "answer": "what's the point?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the point?",
    "answer": "how can it be fun?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how can it be fun?",
    "answer": "they pay money to play this silly game!"
  },
  {
    "question": "they pay money to play this silly game!",
    "answer": "i think golfers have a mental problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think golfers have a mental problem.",
    "answer": "i think they're nuts."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you want to go fishing?",
    "answer": "yes. that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "where do you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do you want to go?",
    "answer": "we can go to the river."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can go to the river.",
    "answer": "or we can go to the lake."
  },
  {
    "question": "or we can go to the lake.",
    "answer": "or we can go to the ocean."
  },
  {
    "question": "or we can go to the ocean.",
    "answer": "let's go to the lake."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go to the lake.",
    "answer": "yes. the lake is only 10 miles away."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. the lake is only 10 miles away.",
    "answer": "we can be there in 20 minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can be there in 20 minutes.",
    "answer": "i'll get our fishing rods."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll get our fishing rods.",
    "answer": "i'll get the bait."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll get the bait.",
    "answer": "we'll have fresh fish for dinner!"
  },
  {
    "question": "baseball is fun.",
    "answer": "i like to hit the ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to hit the ball.",
    "answer": "i like to run around the bases."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to run around the bases.",
    "answer": "i like to slide into the bases."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like to slide into the bases.",
    "answer": "yeah. it's a lot of fun to slide."
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah. it's a lot of fun to slide.",
    "answer": "i want to be a baseball player when i grow up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to be a baseball player when i grow up.",
    "answer": "me too. i want to play for the yankees."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. i want to play for the yankees.",
    "answer": "not me. i want to play for the dodgers."
  },
  {
    "question": "not me. i want to play for the dodgers.",
    "answer": "we have to practice every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "we have to practice every day.",
    "answer": "i don't like practice."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like practice.",
    "answer": "me neither. it's boring."
  },
  {
    "question": "me neither. it's boring.",
    "answer": "but practice makes perfect."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's go jogging.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good idea.",
    "answer": "i bought some new shoes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought some new shoes.",
    "answer": "are they comfortable?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are they comfortable?",
    "answer": "they're very comfortable."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're very comfortable.",
    "answer": "how much were they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much were they?",
    "answer": "they were on sale for $80."
  },
  {
    "question": "they were on sale for $80.",
    "answer": "do they help you run faster?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do they help you run faster?",
    "answer": "no, but my feet don't hurt anymore."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, but my feet don't hurt anymore.",
    "answer": "then they're worth every penny."
  },
  {
    "question": "then they're worth every penny.",
    "answer": "you might want to buy a pair."
  },
  {
    "question": "you might want to buy a pair.",
    "answer": "i'll wait until i wear this pair out."
  },
  {
    "question": "tiger is the greatest golfer in the world.",
    "answer": "you can say that again."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can say that again.",
    "answer": "but i'm worried about tiger."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i'm worried about tiger.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "because he likes to scuba dive."
  },
  {
    "question": "because he likes to scuba dive.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with that?",
    "answer": "it can be dangerous."
  },
  {
    "question": "it can be dangerous.",
    "answer": "you mean he could drown."
  },
  {
    "question": "you mean he could drown.",
    "answer": "he shouldn't scuba dive until he retires."
  },
  {
    "question": "he shouldn't scuba dive until he retires.",
    "answer": "but he dives to relax."
  },
  {
    "question": "but he dives to relax.",
    "answer": "he might relax, but it makes me nervous."
  },
  {
    "question": "he might relax, but it makes me nervous.",
    "answer": "if his wife doesn't mind, you shouldn't mind."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you watch that golf tournament?",
    "answer": "the one that tiger won?"
  },
  {
    "question": "the one that tiger won?",
    "answer": "how did he do it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did he do it?",
    "answer": "it was nothing for him."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was nothing for him.",
    "answer": "he sank a 20-foot putt on the last hole to win by one stroke!"
  },
  {
    "question": "he sank a 20-foot putt on the last hole to win by one stroke!",
    "answer": "he sank a 25-footer last year at the same tournament to win by one stroke."
  },
  {
    "question": "he sank a 25-footer last year at the same tournament to win by one stroke.",
    "answer": "i think he is from outer space."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think he is from outer space.",
    "answer": "no human could possibly play golf that well."
  },
  {
    "question": "no human could possibly play golf that well.",
    "answer": "whenever he needs a shot to win a tournament, he makes that shot."
  },
  {
    "question": "whenever he needs a shot to win a tournament, he makes that shot.",
    "answer": "no human can do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "no human can do that.",
    "answer": "somebody should check his birth record."
  },
  {
    "question": "somebody should check his birth record.",
    "answer": "i bet it says he was born on mars."
  },
  {
    "question": "who's the greatest baseball player?",
    "answer": "there are so many great players."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are so many great players.",
    "answer": "yes, but who is the greatest?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but who is the greatest?",
    "answer": "i'd have to say babe ruth."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'd have to say babe ruth.",
    "answer": "most people would say that."
  },
  {
    "question": "most people would say that.",
    "answer": "he changed the game."
  },
  {
    "question": "he changed the game.",
    "answer": "yes, he made the home run popular."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he made the home run popular.",
    "answer": "everybody loved him, all over the nation."
  },
  {
    "question": "everybody loved him, all over the nation.",
    "answer": "he helped make the yankees the best team ever."
  },
  {
    "question": "he helped make the yankees the best team ever.",
    "answer": "and ruth was a good person, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "and ruth was a good person, too.",
    "answer": "he always visited hospitals to cheer up sick kids."
  },
  {
    "question": "he always visited hospitals to cheer up sick kids.",
    "answer": "there will never be another babe."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear what happened at the baseball game?",
    "answer": "no, please tell me."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, please tell me.",
    "answer": "someone punched out someone."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone punched out someone.",
    "answer": "that's not nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not nice.",
    "answer": "it's worse than that."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's worse than that.",
    "answer": "how so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how so?",
    "answer": "two guys got into an argument."
  },
  {
    "question": "two guys got into an argument.",
    "answer": "i'll bet they were drinking."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll bet they were drinking.",
    "answer": "a third guy punched one of the two guys."
  },
  {
    "question": "a third guy punched one of the two guys.",
    "answer": "i'll bet he was drinking, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll bet he was drinking, too.",
    "answer": "the victim hit his head on the concrete steps and died."
  },
  {
    "question": "the victim hit his head on the concrete steps and died.",
    "answer": "that's terrible. can't people just have fun at a baseball game?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to go to the ball game.",
    "answer": "is there a game tonight?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is there a game tonight?",
    "answer": "yes, it starts at 7 p.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it starts at 7 p.m.",
    "answer": "can we get tickets?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we get tickets?",
    "answer": "yes, but only the cheap tickets."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but only the cheap tickets.",
    "answer": "how much are they?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much are they?",
    "answer": "they're only $5 each."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're only $5 each.",
    "answer": "that's a good price."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good price.",
    "answer": "yes, it's cheaper than a hot dog or a beer."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's cheaper than a hot dog or a beer.",
    "answer": "where are the seats?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where are the seats?",
    "answer": "they're behind the outfield."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're behind the outfield.",
    "answer": "maybe we can catch a home run ball."
  },
  {
    "question": "golf is so hard.",
    "answer": "what's so hard about hitting a little white ball?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's so hard about hitting a little white ball?",
    "answer": "it's hard if you want to do it right."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's hard if you want to do it right.",
    "answer": "you mean like tiger?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you mean like tiger?",
    "answer": "no, like a good amateur golfer."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, like a good amateur golfer.",
    "answer": "what's so hard about golf?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's so hard about golf?",
    "answer": "there are so many things you have to do right."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are so many things you have to do right.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "like keep your left arm straight, keep your head down, and follow through."
  },
  {
    "question": "like keep your left arm straight, keep your head down, and follow through.",
    "answer": "yikes! who can remember all that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yikes! who can remember all that?",
    "answer": "you need to get a lot of lessons when you're really young."
  },
  {
    "question": "you need to get a lot of lessons when you're really young.",
    "answer": "forget it. golf sounds more like work than fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you hear about the ball player?",
    "answer": "the home run hitter on drugs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "the home run hitter on drugs?",
    "answer": "he said a doctor helped him with a personal problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "he said a doctor helped him with a personal problem.",
    "answer": "he said he wasn't using drugs."
  },
  {
    "question": "he said he wasn't using drugs.",
    "answer": "he apologized to the fans."
  },
  {
    "question": "he apologized to the fans.",
    "answer": "the league suspended him for 50 games."
  },
  {
    "question": "the league suspended him for 50 games.",
    "answer": "that will cost him some money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that will cost him some money.",
    "answer": "yes, about $7 million."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, about $7 million.",
    "answer": "that will teach him a good lesson."
  },
  {
    "question": "that will teach him a good lesson.",
    "answer": "he probably won't use drugs anymore."
  },
  {
    "question": "he probably won't use drugs anymore.",
    "answer": "but it won't stop other players from using drugs."
  },
  {
    "question": "but it won't stop other players from using drugs.",
    "answer": "no. everyone always figures that they won't get caught."
  },
  {
    "question": "why is there so much crime?",
    "answer": "because parents don't teach their kids right from wrong."
  },
  {
    "question": "because parents don't teach their kids right from wrong.",
    "answer": "is that it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that it?",
    "answer": "also, there aren't enough police."
  },
  {
    "question": "also, there aren't enough police.",
    "answer": "but there are a lot of police."
  },
  {
    "question": "but there are a lot of police.",
    "answer": "there's only one police officer per 100 criminals."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's only one police officer per 100 criminals.",
    "answer": "can't we hire more police?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can't we hire more police?",
    "answer": "no. it costs too much money."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. it costs too much money.",
    "answer": "doesn't crime cost more than police?"
  },
  {
    "question": "doesn't crime cost more than police?",
    "answer": "yes, it does."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it does.",
    "answer": "so it would be cheaper to hire more police?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so it would be cheaper to hire more police?",
    "answer": "yes, it would."
  },
  {
    "question": "this is a great neighborhood.",
    "answer": "yes, it is."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it is.",
    "answer": "people are friendly."
  },
  {
    "question": "people are friendly.",
    "answer": "yes, they are."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, they are.",
    "answer": "the streets and sidewalks are clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "the streets and sidewalks are clean.",
    "answer": "yes, they are."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, they are.",
    "answer": "there's a real nice park nearby."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's a real nice park nearby.",
    "answer": "yes, there is."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, there is.",
    "answer": "i feel safe here."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel safe here.",
    "answer": "there is no crime here."
  },
  {
    "question": "there is no crime here.",
    "answer": "i wish i could move here."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i could move here.",
    "answer": "maybe you can, if someone moves out."
  },
  {
    "question": "the house burned down.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "the man fell asleep."
  },
  {
    "question": "the man fell asleep.",
    "answer": "was he smoking?"
  },
  {
    "question": "was he smoking?",
    "answer": "yes, he was smoking a cigarette."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he was smoking a cigarette.",
    "answer": "did he die?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he die?",
    "answer": "yes, he did. his cat died, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, he did. his cat died, too.",
    "answer": "that's too bad. what about his smoke alarm?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's too bad. what about his smoke alarm?",
    "answer": "the battery was dead."
  },
  {
    "question": "the battery was dead.",
    "answer": "a good battery would have saved his life."
  },
  {
    "question": "a good battery would have saved his life.",
    "answer": "he had cigarettes, but no battery."
  },
  {
    "question": "he had cigarettes, but no battery.",
    "answer": "it happens all the time."
  },
  {
    "question": "they say he has started fifteen big fires.",
    "answer": "he's been in jail three times already."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's been in jail three times already.",
    "answer": "why did they ever let him out?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did they ever let him out?",
    "answer": "it's the law. they can't keep him in jail forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the law. they can't keep him in jail forever.",
    "answer": "why not? everyone knows he's a firebug. he loves to start fires."
  },
  {
    "question": "why not? everyone knows he's a firebug. he loves to start fires.",
    "answer": "i don't know. sometimes the law doesn't make sense."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. sometimes the law doesn't make sense.",
    "answer": "but his latest fire killed someone."
  },
  {
    "question": "but his latest fire killed someone.",
    "answer": "this time they have charged him with murder."
  },
  {
    "question": "this time they have charged him with murder.",
    "answer": "so maybe he'll go to jail forever?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so maybe he'll go to jail forever?",
    "answer": "i sure hope so."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sure hope so.",
    "answer": "someone should set him on fire."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone should set him on fire.",
    "answer": "that would teach him a good lesson."
  },
  {
    "question": "put your seatbelt on.",
    "answer": "why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why?",
    "answer": "because it will protect you in case of an accident."
  },
  {
    "question": "because it will protect you in case of an accident.",
    "answer": "but it's uncomfortable."
  },
  {
    "question": "but it's uncomfortable.",
    "answer": "it's the law."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the law.",
    "answer": "it's so much trouble."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's so much trouble.",
    "answer": "it's common sense."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's common sense.",
    "answer": "it's so tight that it's hard for me to breathe."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's so tight that it's hard for me to breathe.",
    "answer": "hold your breath till we get there."
  },
  {
    "question": "hold your breath till we get there.",
    "answer": "okay, my seatbelt is on."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, my seatbelt is on.",
    "answer": "i'm glad you don't complain very much."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm glad you don't complain very much.",
    "answer": "i'm ready for an accident."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you doing?",
    "answer": "i'm going to change the light bulb. it burnt out."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to change the light bulb. it burnt out.",
    "answer": "what are you standing on?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you standing on?",
    "answer": "a couple of dictionaries and some textbooks."
  },
  {
    "question": "a couple of dictionaries and some textbooks.",
    "answer": "are you crazy?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you crazy?",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "those books will slip and you'll fall."
  },
  {
    "question": "those books will slip and you'll fall.",
    "answer": "it's only a couple of feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's only a couple of feet.",
    "answer": "what if you fall while you're holding the light bulb, and it breaks and pieces go into your eyes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what if you fall while you're holding the light bulb, and it breaks and pieces go into your eyes?",
    "answer": "i never thought about that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i never thought about that.",
    "answer": "you'd be blind for the rest of your life!"
  },
  {
    "question": "you'd be blind for the rest of your life!",
    "answer": "i'll get the stepladder."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you see that puddle of water on the floor?",
    "answer": "yes. i called for a clean-up."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i called for a clean-up.",
    "answer": "a puddle of water is very dangerous."
  },
  {
    "question": "a puddle of water is very dangerous.",
    "answer": "it isn't easy to see."
  },
  {
    "question": "it isn't easy to see.",
    "answer": "but it's real easy to slip on."
  },
  {
    "question": "but it's real easy to slip on.",
    "answer": "especially on these slick floors."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially on these slick floors.",
    "answer": "someone who slips could hurt their back."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone who slips could hurt their back.",
    "answer": "they could even crack their head open."
  },
  {
    "question": "they could even crack their head open.",
    "answer": "we should stand here till the clean-up person gets here."
  },
  {
    "question": "we should stand here till the clean-up person gets here.",
    "answer": "we can leave if we put an orange cone here."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can leave if we put an orange cone here.",
    "answer": "yes, but i don't know where the orange cones are."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i don't know where the orange cones are.",
    "answer": "it doesn't matter. here he comes now with the mop."
  },
  {
    "question": "what happens when the fire alarm rings?",
    "answer": "we tell our students to leave the classroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "we tell our students to leave the classroom.",
    "answer": "can they take their belongings?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can they take their belongings?",
    "answer": "yes, if they do it quickly."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, if they do it quickly.",
    "answer": "where do the students go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where do the students go?",
    "answer": "they go out to the north parking lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "they go out to the north parking lot.",
    "answer": "what do the teachers do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do the teachers do?",
    "answer": "we take our rosters to the parking lot and take roll."
  },
  {
    "question": "we take our rosters to the parking lot and take roll.",
    "answer": "why do you do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you do that?",
    "answer": "we want to make sure all the students are out of the building."
  },
  {
    "question": "we want to make sure all the students are out of the building.",
    "answer": "if they are all outside, then what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "if they are all outside, then what?",
    "answer": "then we just wait outside for a fireman to tell us to go back in."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to go back upstairs.",
    "answer": "why? we're already late."
  },
  {
    "question": "why? we're already late.",
    "answer": "i have to check the stove."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to check the stove.",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "maybe i left the burner on."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe i left the burner on.",
    "answer": "no, you didn't. i checked the stove before we left."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, you didn't. i checked the stove before we left.",
    "answer": "are you sure?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you sure?",
    "answer": "of course i'm sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course i'm sure.",
    "answer": "well, i have to go back upstairs anyway."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i have to go back upstairs anyway.",
    "answer": "it's getting later every minute."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's getting later every minute.",
    "answer": "i think i left the water running."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i left the water running.",
    "answer": "no, you didn't. let's go! the only thing running is the clock!"
  },
  {
    "question": "the city is buying guns.",
    "answer": "what are they paying?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are they paying?",
    "answer": "up to $200 for each gun, no questions asked."
  },
  {
    "question": "up to $200 for each gun, no questions asked.",
    "answer": "why are they doing this?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why are they doing this?",
    "answer": "they want to get guns off the street."
  },
  {
    "question": "they want to get guns off the street.",
    "answer": "who would turn in a gun for $200?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who would turn in a gun for $200?",
    "answer": "that isn't a good deal?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that isn't a good deal?",
    "answer": "a good gun costs $400 or more."
  },
  {
    "question": "a good gun costs $400 or more.",
    "answer": "well, if you bring your receipt, maybe they'll give you $400."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, if you bring your receipt, maybe they'll give you $400.",
    "answer": "i'll keep my receipt and my gun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll keep my receipt and my gun.",
    "answer": "i didn't know you had a gun."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't know you had a gun.",
    "answer": "everyone in america should have a gun."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're yawning.",
    "answer": "i sure am."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sure am.",
    "answer": "you should go to bed."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should go to bed.",
    "answer": "i will as soon as i finish this article."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will as soon as i finish this article.",
    "answer": "what are you reading?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you reading?",
    "answer": "it's about crime in los angeles."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's about crime in los angeles.",
    "answer": "what does it say?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does it say?",
    "answer": "the mayor says the crime rate is going down."
  },
  {
    "question": "the mayor says the crime rate is going down.",
    "answer": "then why does everyone lock their doors?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why does everyone lock their doors?",
    "answer": "i guess they haven't read this article."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess they haven't read this article.",
    "answer": "no one believes that the crime rate is going down."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one believes that the crime rate is going down.",
    "answer": "maybe the mayor is just talking about his own neighborhood."
  },
  {
    "question": "people who live in california are crazy.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "because of all the earthquakes and fires."
  },
  {
    "question": "because of all the earthquakes and fires.",
    "answer": "but big earthquakes happen only once in a while."
  },
  {
    "question": "but big earthquakes happen only once in a while.",
    "answer": "once in a while is once too many."
  },
  {
    "question": "once in a while is once too many.",
    "answer": "but you're right. there are a lot of fires."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you're right. there are a lot of fires.",
    "answer": "a recent fire destroyed 85 homes."
  },
  {
    "question": "a recent fire destroyed 85 homes.",
    "answer": "still, it's safer than florida."
  },
  {
    "question": "still, it's safer than florida.",
    "answer": "florida doesn't have earthquakes or fires."
  },
  {
    "question": "florida doesn't have earthquakes or fires.",
    "answer": "no, florida just has hurricanes every year from june to october."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, florida just has hurricanes every year from june to october.",
    "answer": "but most of those hurricanes are harmless."
  },
  {
    "question": "but most of those hurricanes are harmless.",
    "answer": "excuse me. hurricane andrew destroyed 30,000 homes!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to hawaii on vacation.",
    "answer": "did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you like it?",
    "answer": "i loved it. i want to live there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i loved it. i want to live there.",
    "answer": "what did you like?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you like?",
    "answer": "the island is so green, and the water is so blue."
  },
  {
    "question": "the island is so green, and the water is so blue.",
    "answer": "did you go swimming?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you go swimming?",
    "answer": "i went to the beach every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i went to the beach every day.",
    "answer": "how was the weather?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how was the weather?",
    "answer": "it was hot and sunny every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was hot and sunny every day.",
    "answer": "what did you do at night?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do at night?",
    "answer": "at night i went out to eat. the food was delicious."
  },
  {
    "question": "at night i went out to eat. the food was delicious.",
    "answer": "people who live in hawaii are lucky."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like this hotel.",
    "answer": "what do you like about it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you like about it?",
    "answer": "we get a free breakfast."
  },
  {
    "question": "we get a free breakfast.",
    "answer": "coffee and a roll?"
  },
  {
    "question": "coffee and a roll?",
    "answer": "no, a real breakfast."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, a real breakfast.",
    "answer": "bacon and eggs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "bacon and eggs?",
    "answer": "with toast, ham, sausage, fresh fruit, and juice."
  },
  {
    "question": "with toast, ham, sausage, fresh fruit, and juice.",
    "answer": "wow! that is nice. let's stay for two nights."
  },
  {
    "question": "wow! that is nice. let's stay for two nights.",
    "answer": "and the rooms are clean, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "and the rooms are clean, too.",
    "answer": "do they allow pets?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do they allow pets?",
    "answer": "no pets, no smoking."
  },
  {
    "question": "no pets, no smoking.",
    "answer": "i like that. let's stay three nights."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sleeping here tonight.",
    "answer": "what's the matter? this is a nice room."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter? this is a nice room.",
    "answer": "maybe the room is nice, but not the bed."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe the room is nice, but not the bed.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with the bed?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with the bed?",
    "answer": "look at this sheet."
  },
  {
    "question": "look at this sheet.",
    "answer": "yes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes?",
    "answer": "see those stains?"
  },
  {
    "question": "see those stains?",
    "answer": "i sure do."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sure do.",
    "answer": "i'm not sleeping on that sheet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sleeping on that sheet.",
    "answer": "well, just call the front desk. they'll give us new sheets."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, just call the front desk. they'll give us new sheets.",
    "answer": "i want sheets without stains on them."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want sheets without stains on them.",
    "answer": "from now on, let's bring our own sheets."
  },
  {
    "question": "what time does your plane leave?",
    "answer": "it leaves at 12:15."
  },
  {
    "question": "it leaves at 12:15.",
    "answer": "when do you have to be at the airport?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when do you have to be at the airport?",
    "answer": "i have to be there two hours early."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to be there two hours early.",
    "answer": "so we have to be at the airport at 10:15."
  },
  {
    "question": "so we have to be at the airport at 10:15.",
    "answer": "that means we have to leave the house at 9:15."
  },
  {
    "question": "that means we have to leave the house at 9:15.",
    "answer": "well, it's an hour to get there, if there are no traffic problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's an hour to get there, if there are no traffic problems.",
    "answer": "so maybe we better leave at 8:15?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so maybe we better leave at 8:15?",
    "answer": "yes, it's better to get there too early than too late."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's better to get there too early than too late.",
    "answer": "i agree."
  },
  {
    "question": "i agree.",
    "answer": "you never know what might happen on these freeways."
  },
  {
    "question": "you never know what might happen on these freeways.",
    "answer": "there's at least one huge accident every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need to fly to new york.",
    "answer": "when are you going?"
  },
  {
    "question": "when are you going?",
    "answer": "during the christmas holidays."
  },
  {
    "question": "during the christmas holidays.",
    "answer": "you'd better buy your ticket now."
  },
  {
    "question": "you'd better buy your ticket now.",
    "answer": "you must be kidding."
  },
  {
    "question": "you must be kidding.",
    "answer": "no, i'm not. it's march. time is running out. seats are selling out right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i'm not. it's march. time is running out. seats are selling out right now.",
    "answer": "i thought i would wait until october."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought i would wait until october.",
    "answer": "i'll bet this is the first time you've ever flown during christmas."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll bet this is the first time you've ever flown during christmas.",
    "answer": "you're right."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right.",
    "answer": "well, listen to me. you need to buy a ticket now."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, listen to me. you need to buy a ticket now.",
    "answer": "but maybe prices will be cheaper in october."
  },
  {
    "question": "but maybe prices will be cheaper in october.",
    "answer": "cheaper prices won't do you any good if there are no seats."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate flying.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "a long time ago, flying used to be okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "a long time ago, flying used to be okay.",
    "answer": "now it's like riding a bus."
  },
  {
    "question": "now it's like riding a bus.",
    "answer": "you're jammed in with people all around you."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're jammed in with people all around you.",
    "answer": "half of them are coughing, and the other half are sneezing."
  },
  {
    "question": "half of them are coughing, and the other half are sneezing.",
    "answer": "you don't have any elbow room or knee room."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't have any elbow room or knee room.",
    "answer": "people are always getting up to use the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "people are always getting up to use the bathroom.",
    "answer": "kids are crying or climbing over you."
  },
  {
    "question": "kids are crying or climbing over you.",
    "answer": "it's a flying zoo!"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a flying zoo!",
    "answer": "i wish i could afford first class seats."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i could afford first class seats.",
    "answer": "doesn't everybody?"
  },
  {
    "question": "some guy rowed across the atlantic ocean.",
    "answer": "good for him."
  },
  {
    "question": "good for him.",
    "answer": "why would he do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why would he do that?",
    "answer": "did he set a new record?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he set a new record?",
    "answer": "yes, i think he did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i think he did.",
    "answer": "well, i guess that's why he did it."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i guess that's why he did it.",
    "answer": "what's the point?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the point?",
    "answer": "now he has the world record!"
  },
  {
    "question": "now he has the world record!",
    "answer": "but someone's going to break it, so what good is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "but someone's going to break it, so what good is it?",
    "answer": "well, he can enjoy it while it lasts."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, he can enjoy it while it lasts.",
    "answer": "i don't think he even got paid for it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't think he even got paid for it.",
    "answer": "some people do it just to do it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to go on a cruise ship.",
    "answer": "that sounds like fun. where do you want to go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like fun. where do you want to go?",
    "answer": "i want to cruise to hawaii."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to cruise to hawaii.",
    "answer": "that should be a nice trip. lots of fun, and lots of food."
  },
  {
    "question": "that should be a nice trip. lots of fun, and lots of food.",
    "answer": "i have no idea how much it will cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have no idea how much it will cost.",
    "answer": "i think it depends on the season and on your cabin."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it depends on the season and on your cabin.",
    "answer": "well, of course i want to go when the weather is nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, of course i want to go when the weather is nice.",
    "answer": "yes, you don't want to travel in winter storms."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, you don't want to travel in winter storms.",
    "answer": "and i want to get a big cabin with a view."
  },
  {
    "question": "and i want to get a big cabin with a view.",
    "answer": "are you going to travel alone?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to travel alone?",
    "answer": "no, my sister and i will travel together."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, my sister and i will travel together.",
    "answer": "well, you should go online and try to find a good deal."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate to fly.",
    "answer": "because of all the security?"
  },
  {
    "question": "because of all the security?",
    "answer": "no, because it hurts my ears."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, because it hurts my ears.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "every time we land or take off, my ears hurt so much."
  },
  {
    "question": "every time we land or take off, my ears hurt so much.",
    "answer": "that's just the altitude change, i think."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's just the altitude change, i think.",
    "answer": "whatever it is, it hurts."
  },
  {
    "question": "whatever it is, it hurts.",
    "answer": "can't you take medicine or something for it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can't you take medicine or something for it?",
    "answer": "i've tried everything, but nothing works."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've tried everything, but nothing works.",
    "answer": "have you tried earplugs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you tried earplugs?",
    "answer": "they don't work, either."
  },
  {
    "question": "they don't work, either.",
    "answer": "well, be glad you're not a pilot."
  },
  {
    "question": "spring break starts tomorrow.",
    "answer": "are you going to go anywhere?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to go anywhere?",
    "answer": "i was thinking of driving to arizona."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was thinking of driving to arizona.",
    "answer": "to the grand canyon?"
  },
  {
    "question": "to the grand canyon?",
    "answer": "yes. i've never been there."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i've never been there.",
    "answer": "i was there when i was a kid."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was there when i was a kid.",
    "answer": "how did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did you like it?",
    "answer": "i loved it. i still remember how amazing it was."
  },
  {
    "question": "i loved it. i still remember how amazing it was.",
    "answer": "i'm sure i'll like it, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sure i'll like it, too.",
    "answer": "you should try riding a mule on a trail to the bottom."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should try riding a mule on a trail to the bottom.",
    "answer": "no way! i don't want to fall to my death."
  },
  {
    "question": "no way! i don't want to fall to my death.",
    "answer": "don't worry. only one person has ever fallen off a mule."
  },
  {
    "question": "that hotel was terrible.",
    "answer": "the worst in the whole world."
  },
  {
    "question": "the worst in the whole world.",
    "answer": "the walls were so thin."
  },
  {
    "question": "the walls were so thin.",
    "answer": "all day long we heard tvs or telephones."
  },
  {
    "question": "all day long we heard tvs or telephones.",
    "answer": "all night long we heard people snoring."
  },
  {
    "question": "all night long we heard people snoring.",
    "answer": "housekeeping didn't give us fresh towels."
  },
  {
    "question": "housekeeping didn't give us fresh towels.",
    "answer": "room service brought us a cold dinner."
  },
  {
    "question": "room service brought us a cold dinner.",
    "answer": "our nonsmoking room stunk of cigarette smoke."
  },
  {
    "question": "our nonsmoking room stunk of cigarette smoke.",
    "answer": "our room was right next to the elevator and the ice machine."
  },
  {
    "question": "our room was right next to the elevator and the ice machine.",
    "answer": "they added phony charges to our bill."
  },
  {
    "question": "they added phony charges to our bill.",
    "answer": "how did we end up in that terrible hotel?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did we end up in that terrible hotel?",
    "answer": "the travel agent gave us a 50-percent discount!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to hang up. i'm so sleepy.",
    "answer": "it's not even 10 o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not even 10 o'clock.",
    "answer": "i'm falling asleep on the phone."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm falling asleep on the phone.",
    "answer": "you got up real early."
  },
  {
    "question": "you got up real early.",
    "answer": "i had to take my friend to the airport."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had to take my friend to the airport.",
    "answer": "why didn't you take a nap when you got home?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why didn't you take a nap when you got home?",
    "answer": "i didn't get home until 30 minutes ago."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't get home until 30 minutes ago.",
    "answer": "why is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why is that?",
    "answer": "there was a bomb threat at the airport."
  },
  {
    "question": "there was a bomb threat at the airport.",
    "answer": "only a threat?"
  },
  {
    "question": "only a threat?",
    "answer": "yes, but i was stuck there all day while they looked for the bomb."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i was stuck there all day while they looked for the bomb.",
    "answer": "someday the bomb is going to be for real."
  },
  {
    "question": "my dad went to washington, d.c.",
    "answer": "why did he do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did he do that?",
    "answer": "he was invited, along with about 90 other veterans."
  },
  {
    "question": "he was invited, along with about 90 other veterans.",
    "answer": "who invited them?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who invited them?",
    "answer": "some private organization."
  },
  {
    "question": "some private organization.",
    "answer": "why did they invite him?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did they invite him?",
    "answer": "to thank him and all the other soldiers who served in world war ii."
  },
  {
    "question": "to thank him and all the other soldiers who served in world war ii.",
    "answer": "that's very nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's very nice.",
    "answer": "my dad got to see the beautiful new world war ii monument."
  },
  {
    "question": "my dad got to see the beautiful new world war ii monument.",
    "answer": "that trip must have cost a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that trip must have cost a lot of money.",
    "answer": "he said all the money came from private donations."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a great trip to washington, d.c.",
    "answer": "tell me about it, dad."
  },
  {
    "question": "tell me about it, dad.",
    "answer": "about 90 of us world war ii veterans got on the plane at 8 a.m."
  },
  {
    "question": "about 90 of us world war ii veterans got on the plane at 8 a.m.",
    "answer": "how long was the flight?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how long was the flight?",
    "answer": "it only took about two hours."
  },
  {
    "question": "it only took about two hours.",
    "answer": "did you take pictures at the world war ii monument?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you take pictures at the world war ii monument?",
    "answer": "oh, yes. we all took lots of pictures."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes. we all took lots of pictures.",
    "answer": "then you flew back home that evening?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then you flew back home that evening?",
    "answer": "yes. when we landed, tv reporters and the army band were there."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. when we landed, tv reporters and the army band were there.",
    "answer": "that must have made you feel really special."
  },
  {
    "question": "that must have made you feel really special.",
    "answer": "oh, it did. there were about 300 people there to honor us."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, it did. there were about 300 people there to honor us.",
    "answer": "well, you all deserve it. you helped save our country."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need a job.",
    "answer": "i thought you had a job."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought you had a job.",
    "answer": "i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "i did.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "i got laid off."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got laid off.",
    "answer": "that's terrible! when did it happen?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's terrible! when did it happen?",
    "answer": "i got laid off last week."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got laid off last week.",
    "answer": "just you?"
  },
  {
    "question": "just you?",
    "answer": "no, ten of my coworkers got laid off, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, ten of my coworkers got laid off, too.",
    "answer": "what are you going to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do?",
    "answer": "i'm looking in the newspaper for a job."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm looking in the newspaper for a job.",
    "answer": "good luck!"
  },
  {
    "question": "before you go to that interview, check yourself.",
    "answer": "what's to check?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's to check?",
    "answer": "are your nails clean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are your nails clean?",
    "answer": "yes, they are."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, they are.",
    "answer": "did you double-check your nose and teeth?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you double-check your nose and teeth?",
    "answer": "they are clean, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "they are clean, too.",
    "answer": "did you shine your shoes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you shine your shoes?",
    "answer": "my shoes are shined."
  },
  {
    "question": "my shoes are shined.",
    "answer": "do your socks match?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do your socks match?",
    "answer": "of course they match."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course they match.",
    "answer": "no, they don't. one is black and one is dark blue."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, they don't. one is black and one is dark blue.",
    "answer": "yikes! thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "life is hard.",
    "answer": "it sure is."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sure is.",
    "answer": "i thought school was hard."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought school was hard.",
    "answer": "me, too. i couldn't wait to graduate."
  },
  {
    "question": "me, too. i couldn't wait to graduate.",
    "answer": "but now work is hard, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "but now work is hard, too.",
    "answer": "i agree. work is just as hard as school."
  },
  {
    "question": "i agree. work is just as hard as school.",
    "answer": "sometimes i wish i was back in school."
  },
  {
    "question": "sometimes i wish i was back in school.",
    "answer": "me, too. school was fun."
  },
  {
    "question": "me, too. school was fun.",
    "answer": "and it was only 12 years."
  },
  {
    "question": "and it was only 12 years.",
    "answer": "it went by pretty fast."
  },
  {
    "question": "it went by pretty fast.",
    "answer": "but work goes on forever!"
  },
  {
    "question": "but work goes on forever!",
    "answer": "we have to work for 30 years!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sleepy.",
    "answer": "so am i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so am i.",
    "answer": "i had a long day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had a long day.",
    "answer": "so did i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so did i.",
    "answer": "i didn't even have lunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't even have lunch.",
    "answer": "neither did i."
  },
  {
    "question": "neither did i.",
    "answer": "i was busy the whole day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was busy the whole day.",
    "answer": "so was i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so was i.",
    "answer": "i had to bring work home with me."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had to bring work home with me.",
    "answer": "i did too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i did too.",
    "answer": "your day was just like mine."
  },
  {
    "question": "your day was just like mine.",
    "answer": "of course it was. we work together!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like my job.",
    "answer": "what do you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you do?",
    "answer": "i'm a babysitter."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm a babysitter.",
    "answer": "is that a lot of work?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that a lot of work?",
    "answer": "babies cry all the time."
  },
  {
    "question": "babies cry all the time.",
    "answer": "you have to change their diapers."
  },
  {
    "question": "you have to change their diapers.",
    "answer": "i have to feed them."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have to feed them.",
    "answer": "are you looking for another job?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you looking for another job?",
    "answer": "no, i'm looking for another family."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i'm looking for another family.",
    "answer": "another family?"
  },
  {
    "question": "another family?",
    "answer": "a family with only one baby."
  },
  {
    "question": "a family with only one baby.",
    "answer": "that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need a job.",
    "answer": "what was your last job?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what was your last job?",
    "answer": "i was a painter."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was a painter.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "i got laid off because there was no work."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got laid off because there was no work.",
    "answer": "what else can you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what else can you do?",
    "answer": "i'm a handyman."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm a handyman.",
    "answer": "can you fix a dripping faucet in a kitchen sink?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can you fix a dripping faucet in a kitchen sink?",
    "answer": "of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course.",
    "answer": "then i have a job for you in my kitchen."
  },
  {
    "question": "then i have a job for you in my kitchen.",
    "answer": "it will cost you only $20 plus parts."
  },
  {
    "question": "it will cost you only $20 plus parts.",
    "answer": "okay. that sounds like a fair price."
  },
  {
    "question": "what would you do if you lost your job?",
    "answer": "i have no idea. i've been here for 20 years."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have no idea. i've been here for 20 years.",
    "answer": "do you have any other skills?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you have any other skills?",
    "answer": "well, i know how to flip hamburgers."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i know how to flip hamburgers.",
    "answer": "no one would hire you to flip hamburgers."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one would hire you to flip hamburgers.",
    "answer": "have you heard something that you're not telling me?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard something that you're not telling me?",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "are there going to be layoffs at this place?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are there going to be layoffs at this place?",
    "answer": "i certainly hope not!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i certainly hope not!",
    "answer": "if you got laid off, you'd be flipping hamburgers, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you got laid off, you'd be flipping hamburgers, too.",
    "answer": "oh great, we could both work at burger king."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh great, we could both work at burger king.",
    "answer": "maybe we'd get laid off there, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "do your students ever talk about their jobs?",
    "answer": "yes, and they ask me what jobs are the best."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, and they ask me what jobs are the best.",
    "answer": "i tell my students to become a teacher."
  },
  {
    "question": "i tell my students to become a teacher.",
    "answer": "teaching is a great job."
  },
  {
    "question": "teaching is a great job.",
    "answer": "it's the best job i've ever had."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's the best job i've ever had.",
    "answer": "what makes it so good?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what makes it so good?",
    "answer": "for me, it's the students."
  },
  {
    "question": "for me, it's the students.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i mean i have wonderful students."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean i have wonderful students.",
    "answer": "that must be nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "that must be nice.",
    "answer": "teaching is the best part of my whole day."
  },
  {
    "question": "teaching is the best part of my whole day.",
    "answer": "you're a lucky man to have a job you love."
  },
  {
    "question": "boy, i'm glad that job is finished.",
    "answer": "how long did it take?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how long did it take?",
    "answer": "four hours, without a break."
  },
  {
    "question": "four hours, without a break.",
    "answer": "it's always nice to finish a job."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's always nice to finish a job.",
    "answer": "well, it's good and bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it's good and bad.",
    "answer": "what's bad about it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's bad about it?",
    "answer": "when you finish, all you do is start another job!"
  },
  {
    "question": "when you finish, all you do is start another job!",
    "answer": "yes, that's right. it does get boring."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, that's right. it does get boring.",
    "answer": "especially if it's the same work, over and over."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially if it's the same work, over and over.",
    "answer": "but that's what most people do."
  },
  {
    "question": "but that's what most people do.",
    "answer": "yes, i guess most of us are stuck in a routine."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i guess most of us are stuck in a routine.",
    "answer": "i wonder if there is any job that you don't repeat over and over."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i have the worst boss in the world.",
    "answer": "what makes him so bad?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what makes him so bad?",
    "answer": "he's rude and he yells a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's rude and he yells a lot.",
    "answer": "that's hard to take."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's hard to take.",
    "answer": "i've never heard him say please or thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've never heard him say please or thank you.",
    "answer": "he sounds like a real jerk."
  },
  {
    "question": "he sounds like a real jerk.",
    "answer": "no one at work likes him."
  },
  {
    "question": "no one at work likes him.",
    "answer": "can't you report him to his supervisor?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can't you report him to his supervisor?",
    "answer": "of course not. if i do that, i'll lose my job."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course not. if i do that, i'll lose my job.",
    "answer": "yes, they don't like troublemakers or complainers."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, they don't like troublemakers or complainers.",
    "answer": "i can't quit, because i'm making a good salary."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't quit, because i'm making a good salary.",
    "answer": "you shouldn't choose money over happiness."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are we going to do?",
    "answer": "about what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "about what?",
    "answer": "about finding a job for me."
  },
  {
    "question": "about finding a job for me.",
    "answer": "you don't need a job. i make enough money for both of us."
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't need a job. i make enough money for both of us.",
    "answer": "that doesn't matter. i don't want to sit around."
  },
  {
    "question": "that doesn't matter. i don't want to sit around.",
    "answer": "okay, what kind of job do you want?"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, what kind of job do you want?",
    "answer": "i'm not sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not sure.",
    "answer": "well, you should do something that you enjoy."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you should do something that you enjoy.",
    "answer": "i enjoy selling. i was born to sell."
  },
  {
    "question": "i enjoy selling. i was born to sell.",
    "answer": "okay, what do you want to sell?"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, what do you want to sell?",
    "answer": "cigarette lighters. i'll make a fortune."
  },
  {
    "question": "cigarette lighters. i'll make a fortune.",
    "answer": "but you hate cigarettes and you hate smoking!"
  },
  {
    "question": "a new hotel is looking for workers.",
    "answer": "yes, i saw it on the tv news."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i saw it on the tv news.",
    "answer": "they need 300 new workers."
  },
  {
    "question": "they need 300 new workers.",
    "answer": "and 4,000 people showed up."
  },
  {
    "question": "and 4,000 people showed up.",
    "answer": "so many people are out of work."
  },
  {
    "question": "so many people are out of work.",
    "answer": "i still have my job, thank goodness."
  },
  {
    "question": "i still have my job, thank goodness.",
    "answer": "so do i, but i'm worried."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i, but i'm worried.",
    "answer": "me too. there are no guarantees."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too. there are no guarantees.",
    "answer": "if you lose your job, you can move in with me."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you lose your job, you can move in with me.",
    "answer": "oh, thank you. that's very nice of you."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, thank you. that's very nice of you.",
    "answer": "you would do the same for me."
  },
  {
    "question": "you would do the same for me.",
    "answer": "of course. what are friends for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i did something real stupid.",
    "answer": "what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do?",
    "answer": "i bought some stock."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought some stock.",
    "answer": "everybody buys stock."
  },
  {
    "question": "everybody buys stock.",
    "answer": "i bought it on a hunch."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought it on a hunch.",
    "answer": "you didn't read about the company first?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you didn't read about the company first?",
    "answer": "i didn't have to. it's been in business for 60 years."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't have to. it's been in business for 60 years.",
    "answer": "so what's the problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what's the problem?",
    "answer": "i used all my savings on this one company."
  },
  {
    "question": "i used all my savings on this one company.",
    "answer": "you put all your eggs into one basket."
  },
  {
    "question": "you put all your eggs into one basket.",
    "answer": "if the company goes out of business, i'll have nothing."
  },
  {
    "question": "if the company goes out of business, i'll have nothing.",
    "answer": "oh, you'll have somethingÂ—you'll have a lesson you'll never forget!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i was going to be a doctor.",
    "answer": "what happened to your plans?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened to your plans?",
    "answer": "i got a d in college chemistry."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got a d in college chemistry.",
    "answer": "well, a d is better than an f."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, a d is better than an f.",
    "answer": "a tutor helped me get the d!"
  },
  {
    "question": "a tutor helped me get the d!",
    "answer": "so, you didn't become a doctor."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, you didn't become a doctor.",
    "answer": "and now i'm glad that i didn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "and now i'm glad that i didn't.",
    "answer": "why's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why's that?",
    "answer": "a hospital is the most dangerous place in the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "a hospital is the most dangerous place in the world.",
    "answer": "oh, yes, because of all the killer germs."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes, because of all the killer germs.",
    "answer": "if you're a smart doctor, you stay away from hospitals."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you're a smart doctor, you stay away from hospitals.",
    "answer": "yes, the smart doctors are those tv news doctorsÂ—no hospitals, no patients."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to be a mail carrier when i grow up.",
    "answer": "why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why?",
    "answer": "because you get to meet a lot of people."
  },
  {
    "question": "because you get to meet a lot of people.",
    "answer": "you sure do."
  },
  {
    "question": "you sure do.",
    "answer": "and you get a lot of exercise every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "and you get a lot of exercise every day.",
    "answer": "that's the truth."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's the truth.",
    "answer": "and you get to play with a lot of dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "and you get to play with a lot of dogs.",
    "answer": "well, you're supposed to be working."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you're supposed to be working.",
    "answer": "yes, but i will always pet the friendly dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but i will always pet the friendly dogs.",
    "answer": "what about the unfriendly dogs?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about the unfriendly dogs?",
    "answer": "i think if you are friendly to dogs, they are friendly to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think if you are friendly to dogs, they are friendly to you.",
    "answer": "dogs are like peopleÂ—not all of them are friendly."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to move to new york.",
    "answer": "to the state or the city?"
  },
  {
    "question": "to the state or the city?",
    "answer": "to the city, of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "to the city, of course.",
    "answer": "why do you want to move there?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do you want to move there?",
    "answer": "because i want to make a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "question": "because i want to make a lot of money.",
    "answer": "there are a lot of poor people in new york."
  },
  {
    "question": "there are a lot of poor people in new york.",
    "answer": "there sure areÂ—at least a million."
  },
  {
    "question": "there sure areÂ—at least a million.",
    "answer": "so how do you plan to become rich?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so how do you plan to become rich?",
    "answer": "i will knock on the doors of all the corporations."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will knock on the doors of all the corporations.",
    "answer": "that won't make you rich. nobody will talk to you."
  },
  {
    "question": "that won't make you rich. nobody will talk to you.",
    "answer": "i will keep knocking on doors."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will keep knocking on doors.",
    "answer": "all you will get is sore knuckles."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love salads.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "i usually eat a simple salad."
  },
  {
    "question": "i usually eat a simple salad.",
    "answer": "what do you put in it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you put in it?",
    "answer": "just lettuce, tomato, and celery."
  },
  {
    "question": "just lettuce, tomato, and celery.",
    "answer": "that's it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's it?",
    "answer": "i add some pepper and salt."
  },
  {
    "question": "i add some pepper and salt.",
    "answer": "i always put cheese in my salads."
  },
  {
    "question": "i always put cheese in my salads.",
    "answer": "yes, cheese is nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, cheese is nice.",
    "answer": "what kind of dressing do you use?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of dressing do you use?",
    "answer": "i pour lots of french dressing on top."
  },
  {
    "question": "i pour lots of french dressing on top.",
    "answer": "me too. french dressing is so delicious! who cares about calories?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i love cheese.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "where does cheese come from?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where does cheese come from?",
    "answer": "it comes from cows."
  },
  {
    "question": "it comes from cows.",
    "answer": "so we get cheese from cows, and we get milk, too?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so we get cheese from cows, and we get milk, too?",
    "answer": "yes, we do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, we do.",
    "answer": "what else do we get from cows?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what else do we get from cows?",
    "answer": "we get hamburgers and steak."
  },
  {
    "question": "we get hamburgers and steak.",
    "answer": "oh, that's so delicious."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, that's so delicious.",
    "answer": "we also get leather."
  },
  {
    "question": "we also get leather.",
    "answer": "we get a lot of things from cows, don't we?"
  },
  {
    "question": "we get a lot of things from cows, don't we?",
    "answer": "yes. a cow is man's best friend."
  },
  {
    "question": "i used to work in a deli.",
    "answer": "how did you like it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did you like it?",
    "answer": "i loved it!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i loved it!",
    "answer": "did you get free food?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you get free food?",
    "answer": "i ate free cheese and meat every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i ate free cheese and meat every day.",
    "answer": "that sounds like a great job."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like a great job.",
    "answer": "whatever a customer ordered, i sliced off a little more for me."
  },
  {
    "question": "whatever a customer ordered, i sliced off a little more for me.",
    "answer": "did you get fat?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you get fat?",
    "answer": "no, but i did put on a few pounds."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, but i did put on a few pounds.",
    "answer": "that sounds like a dream job."
  },
  {
    "question": "that sounds like a dream job.",
    "answer": "it was, until one day my manager caught me."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was, until one day my manager caught me.",
    "answer": "no more free cheese for you, huh?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm on a new diet.",
    "answer": "what are you eating now?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you eating now?",
    "answer": "i switched from pasta to potatoes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i switched from pasta to potatoes.",
    "answer": "why did you do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did you do that?",
    "answer": "pasta is processed food. potatoes are natural food."
  },
  {
    "question": "pasta is processed food. potatoes are natural food.",
    "answer": "natural food has more vitamins."
  },
  {
    "question": "natural food has more vitamins.",
    "answer": "and it's just as easy to prepare."
  },
  {
    "question": "and it's just as easy to prepare.",
    "answer": "how do you prepare the potatoes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you prepare the potatoes?",
    "answer": "i wash them, and then steam them for 15 minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wash them, and then steam them for 15 minutes.",
    "answer": "that's pretty simple."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's pretty simple.",
    "answer": "then i add butter, salt, and pepper."
  },
  {
    "question": "then i add butter, salt, and pepper.",
    "answer": "can i have all those cans of tomato sauce you bought for your pasta?"
  },
  {
    "question": "my girlfriend's mom got mad at me at the dinner table.",
    "answer": "why was that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why was that?",
    "answer": "i sprinkled salt and pepper on the food before i tasted it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sprinkled salt and pepper on the food before i tasted it.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with that?",
    "answer": "her mom is a great cook."
  },
  {
    "question": "her mom is a great cook.",
    "answer": "so, a little salt and pepper never hurt anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, a little salt and pepper never hurt anything.",
    "answer": "it hurt her feelings."
  },
  {
    "question": "it hurt her feelings.",
    "answer": "oh."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh.",
    "answer": "i apologized to her, but i could tell she was still upset."
  },
  {
    "question": "i apologized to her, but i could tell she was still upset.",
    "answer": "maybe you shouldn't eat there again."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you shouldn't eat there again.",
    "answer": "i'm sure everything will be okay in a day or two."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm sure everything will be okay in a day or two.",
    "answer": "it's your girlfriend's fault. she should have warned you."
  },
  {
    "question": "i eat the same thing every day.",
    "answer": "you're kidding."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're kidding.",
    "answer": "no, i'm serious."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i'm serious.",
    "answer": "doesn't that get old?"
  },
  {
    "question": "doesn't that get old?",
    "answer": "no, because i'm eating food that i like."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, because i'm eating food that i like.",
    "answer": "but the same thing day after day gets old."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the same thing day after day gets old.",
    "answer": "well, i guess if it ever does get old, i'll change to something different."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i guess if it ever does get old, i'll change to something different.",
    "answer": "do you eat fruits and vegetables every day?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you eat fruits and vegetables every day?",
    "answer": "no, i hate vegetables."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i hate vegetables.",
    "answer": "but you eat fruits."
  },
  {
    "question": "but you eat fruits.",
    "answer": "i eat two apples, one banana, and one orange every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i eat two apples, one banana, and one orange every day.",
    "answer": "well, there's nothing wrong with that."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's something wrong with my orange.",
    "answer": "what's wrong?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong?",
    "answer": "it's not orange!"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's not orange!",
    "answer": "your orange isn't orange?"
  },
  {
    "question": "your orange isn't orange?",
    "answer": "no, it's dark pink!"
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it's dark pink!",
    "answer": "are you sure? i never heard of such a thing."
  },
  {
    "question": "are you sure? i never heard of such a thing.",
    "answer": "i just peeled it, and i'm looking at it right now."
  },
  {
    "question": "i just peeled it, and i'm looking at it right now.",
    "answer": "let me see. yes, you're right. your orange is pink."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me see. yes, you're right. your orange is pink.",
    "answer": "who ever heard of such a thing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who ever heard of such a thing?",
    "answer": "oh, look. here's the little sticker that was on it. it's called a pink navel."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, look. here's the little sticker that was on it. it's called a pink navel.",
    "answer": "what is this world coming to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is this world coming to?",
    "answer": "who knows? maybe soon we'll have pink bananas."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love peanuts.",
    "answer": "me, too. i love them roasted and salted."
  },
  {
    "question": "me, too. i love them roasted and salted.",
    "answer": "i love boiled peanuts."
  },
  {
    "question": "i love boiled peanuts.",
    "answer": "boiled? i never heard of that."
  },
  {
    "question": "boiled? i never heard of that.",
    "answer": "just boil raw peanuts in salt water until the shells are soft."
  },
  {
    "question": "just boil raw peanuts in salt water until the shells are soft.",
    "answer": "i'll have to try them sometime."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll have to try them sometime.",
    "answer": "they're best when they're hot."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're best when they're hot.",
    "answer": "my brother is allergic to peanuts."
  },
  {
    "question": "my brother is allergic to peanuts.",
    "answer": "that's not good."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's not good.",
    "answer": "no, it isn't. he almost died when he was little."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, it isn't. he almost died when he was little.",
    "answer": "i guess he has to be very careful about what he eats."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess he has to be very careful about what he eats.",
    "answer": "he has a very strict diet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm gaining weight.",
    "answer": "how much have you gained?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much have you gained?",
    "answer": "three pounds just this month."
  },
  {
    "question": "three pounds just this month.",
    "answer": "do you know why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know why?",
    "answer": "i think it's the ice cream."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think it's the ice cream.",
    "answer": "you started eating ice cream?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you started eating ice cream?",
    "answer": "it was on sale."
  },
  {
    "question": "it was on sale.",
    "answer": "how much did you buy?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much did you buy?",
    "answer": "i filled up my freezer with ice cream."
  },
  {
    "question": "i filled up my freezer with ice cream.",
    "answer": "well, it won't last forever."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, it won't last forever.",
    "answer": "no, i figure i'll finish it all by next week."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i figure i'll finish it all by next week.",
    "answer": "then you can start losing weight, if there isn't another sale."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm stuffed.",
    "answer": "of course you are. you ate everything on the table."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course you are. you ate everything on the table.",
    "answer": "i don't like to eat leftovers."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like to eat leftovers.",
    "answer": "i'm glad to hear there's something you don't like to eat."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm glad to hear there's something you don't like to eat.",
    "answer": "i like my food hot and fresh."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like my food hot and fresh.",
    "answer": "you like to see it disappear."
  },
  {
    "question": "you like to see it disappear.",
    "answer": "i don't like it reheated."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like it reheated.",
    "answer": "well, you'll have hot fresh food tomorrow night."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you'll have hot fresh food tomorrow night.",
    "answer": "i'm so full i'm going to burst."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm so full i'm going to burst.",
    "answer": "you should loosen your belt."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should loosen your belt.",
    "answer": "i already loosened my belt and unbuttoned my pants."
  },
  {
    "question": "i already loosened my belt and unbuttoned my pants.",
    "answer": "well, don't stand up, please."
  },
  {
    "question": "i saw what you did.",
    "answer": "i didn't do anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't do anything.",
    "answer": "oh yes, you did."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh yes, you did.",
    "answer": "what are you talking about?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you talking about?",
    "answer": "you know what i'm talking about."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know what i'm talking about.",
    "answer": "i don't have any idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have any idea.",
    "answer": "you know what you did."
  },
  {
    "question": "you know what you did.",
    "answer": "maybe i know, but how could you know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe i know, but how could you know?",
    "answer": "because i was watching you."
  },
  {
    "question": "because i was watching you.",
    "answer": "okay, i'm sorry i did it."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, i'm sorry i did it.",
    "answer": "don't drink milk out of the carton. use a glass!"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't drink milk out of the carton. use a glass!",
    "answer": "i promise i'll never drink out of the carton again."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like that shirt.",
    "answer": "so do i."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i.",
    "answer": "how much is it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how much is it?",
    "answer": "i don't know. the tag is missing."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. the tag is missing.",
    "answer": "ask the clerk."
  },
  {
    "question": "ask the clerk.",
    "answer": "i will."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will.",
    "answer": "oh, look. here's another shirt just like it."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, look. here's another shirt just like it.",
    "answer": "does it have a price tag?"
  },
  {
    "question": "does it have a price tag?",
    "answer": "yes, it does. it's only $20."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it does. it's only $20.",
    "answer": "that's a great price."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a great price.",
    "answer": "i think i'll buy both of them."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i'll buy both of them.",
    "answer": "you'd better try them on first."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought you a pair of pants.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "i hope they fit."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope they fit.",
    "answer": "i hope you kept the receipt."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hope you kept the receipt.",
    "answer": "you think they won't fit?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you think they won't fit?",
    "answer": "i think i've put on some weight."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i've put on some weight.",
    "answer": "you think?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you think?",
    "answer": "maybe a pound or two."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe a pound or two.",
    "answer": "maybe four or five pounds?"
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe four or five pounds?",
    "answer": "my waist is bigger than it was."
  },
  {
    "question": "my waist is bigger than it was.",
    "answer": "no problem. these pants have an elastic waistband."
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem. these pants have an elastic waistband.",
    "answer": "you are so smart!"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do we need to buy?",
    "answer": "let me look at our list."
  },
  {
    "question": "let me look at our list.",
    "answer": "i know that we need milk."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know that we need milk.",
    "answer": "nonfat."
  },
  {
    "question": "nonfat.",
    "answer": "of course. what else?"
  },
  {
    "question": "of course. what else?",
    "answer": "we need cheese, bread, and ham."
  },
  {
    "question": "we need cheese, bread, and ham.",
    "answer": "what kind of cheese?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what kind of cheese?",
    "answer": "swiss."
  },
  {
    "question": "swiss.",
    "answer": "of course, the cheese with holes in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course, the cheese with holes in it.",
    "answer": "i never used to buy swiss cheese."
  },
  {
    "question": "i never used to buy swiss cheese.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "i didn't want to pay for the holes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need some pants.",
    "answer": "i thought you just bought a pair."
  },
  {
    "question": "i thought you just bought a pair.",
    "answer": "i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "i did.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with them so soon?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with them so soon?",
    "answer": "the pants are fine, but the pocket has a huge hole in it."
  },
  {
    "question": "the pants are fine, but the pocket has a huge hole in it.",
    "answer": "you shouldn't carry your keys and pens in your pocket."
  },
  {
    "question": "you shouldn't carry your keys and pens in your pocket.",
    "answer": "but that's what pockets are for."
  },
  {
    "question": "but that's what pockets are for.",
    "answer": "you should carry them in a purse."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should carry them in a purse.",
    "answer": "i'm a man, and men don't carry purses!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm a man, and men don't carry purses!",
    "answer": "well, you should buy pants with stronger pockets."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, you should buy pants with stronger pockets.",
    "answer": "i would if i could find someone who makes strong pockets."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would if i could find someone who makes strong pockets.",
    "answer": "try a google search online."
  },
  {
    "question": "what are those wipes for?",
    "answer": "you use them to wipe the handle of the shopping cart."
  },
  {
    "question": "you use them to wipe the handle of the shopping cart.",
    "answer": "that's a great idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a great idea.",
    "answer": "yes, all the markets just started offering wipes to shoppers."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, all the markets just started offering wipes to shoppers.",
    "answer": "i'm going to take five wipes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to take five wipes.",
    "answer": "what do you need five of them for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you need five of them for?",
    "answer": "one to wipe the handle, and the others to wipe the produce."
  },
  {
    "question": "one to wipe the handle, and the others to wipe the produce.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with the produce?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with the produce?",
    "answer": "do you think the bananas fell from the sky?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think the bananas fell from the sky?",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "i mean, someone used their dirty hands to pick the bananas, the apples, and the oranges."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mean, someone used their dirty hands to pick the bananas, the apples, and the oranges.",
    "answer": "well, you better save a wipe for the dirty dollar bills you're going to pay with."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you go to the 99 cents store?",
    "answer": "yes, i did."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did.",
    "answer": "what did you buy?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you buy?",
    "answer": "well, i got a lot of good deals, as usual."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i got a lot of good deals, as usual.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "well, a dozen large eggs were only 99 cents."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, a dozen large eggs were only 99 cents.",
    "answer": "that's a good deal."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good deal.",
    "answer": "and a one-pound tub of soft butter was the same price."
  },
  {
    "question": "and a one-pound tub of soft butter was the same price.",
    "answer": "another good deal."
  },
  {
    "question": "another good deal.",
    "answer": "but the best deal was five pounds of potatoes for 99 cents."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the best deal was five pounds of potatoes for 99 cents.",
    "answer": "i don't know how that store makes money."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know how that store makes money.",
    "answer": "neither do i, but they're doing something right."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need a new computer.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with yours?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with yours?",
    "answer": "it's six years old."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's six years old.",
    "answer": "that's pretty old."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's pretty old.",
    "answer": "it still works, but i'm going to give it to a charity."
  },
  {
    "question": "it still works, but i'm going to give it to a charity.",
    "answer": "are you going to buy a desktop or laptop?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you going to buy a desktop or laptop?",
    "answer": "oh, a laptop, of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, a laptop, of course.",
    "answer": "a pc or a mac?"
  },
  {
    "question": "a pc or a mac?",
    "answer": "i haven't decided yet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't decided yet.",
    "answer": "more and more people are using macs."
  },
  {
    "question": "more and more people are using macs.",
    "answer": "but 90 percent of the world uses pcs."
  },
  {
    "question": "but 90 percent of the world uses pcs.",
    "answer": "and that's not going to change anytime soon."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got ripped off.",
    "answer": "what happened?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what happened?",
    "answer": "i had a car problem, so i went online."
  },
  {
    "question": "i had a car problem, so i went online.",
    "answer": "did you find a solution?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you find a solution?",
    "answer": "yes, i did. a site i went to said they would send me the solution."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i did. a site i went to said they would send me the solution.",
    "answer": "so, what's the problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so, what's the problem?",
    "answer": "i sent them $20 using my credit card, but they never sent me the solution."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sent them $20 using my credit card, but they never sent me the solution.",
    "answer": "what are you going to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what are you going to do?",
    "answer": "i sent them an email asking for my money back."
  },
  {
    "question": "i sent them an email asking for my money back.",
    "answer": "have you heard from them?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you heard from them?",
    "answer": "not yet. it's been a week."
  },
  {
    "question": "not yet. it's been a week.",
    "answer": "well, i guess that's a $20 lesson for you."
  },
  {
    "question": "where's the pencil sharpener?",
    "answer": "which one?"
  },
  {
    "question": "which one?",
    "answer": "any one. i need to sharpen this pencil."
  },
  {
    "question": "any one. i need to sharpen this pencil.",
    "answer": "i think there's one on the dining room table."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think there's one on the dining room table.",
    "answer": "i already looked there."
  },
  {
    "question": "i already looked there.",
    "answer": "did you look in the desk drawer?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did you look in the desk drawer?",
    "answer": "yes, i looked there, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i looked there, too.",
    "answer": "don't we have about five sharpeners?"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't we have about five sharpeners?",
    "answer": "yes, but they seem to have legs."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, but they seem to have legs.",
    "answer": "tomorrow i'm going to buy an electric sharpener."
  },
  {
    "question": "tomorrow i'm going to buy an electric sharpener.",
    "answer": "get one with the rubber suction cups on the bottom."
  },
  {
    "question": "get one with the rubber suction cups on the bottom.",
    "answer": "yes. that way it will stay where i put it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm trying to stretch my dollars.",
    "answer": "how are you doing that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how are you doing that?",
    "answer": "i started shopping at the dollar store."
  },
  {
    "question": "i started shopping at the dollar store.",
    "answer": "that saves a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that saves a lot of money.",
    "answer": "i bought three pounds of potatoes for a dollar."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bought three pounds of potatoes for a dollar.",
    "answer": "that's a good deal."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good deal.",
    "answer": "yes, even though some of the potatoes had eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, even though some of the potatoes had eyes.",
    "answer": "just put them in the fridge."
  },
  {
    "question": "just put them in the fridge.",
    "answer": "also, i bought a can of cheap coffee and a bag of good coffee."
  },
  {
    "question": "also, i bought a can of cheap coffee and a bag of good coffee.",
    "answer": "why did you do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did you do that?",
    "answer": "i mixed them together."
  },
  {
    "question": "i mixed them together.",
    "answer": "if the coffee still tastes okay, that's a good idea."
  },
  {
    "question": "i really like this house.",
    "answer": "can we afford it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we afford it?",
    "answer": "they want 20 percent down."
  },
  {
    "question": "they want 20 percent down.",
    "answer": "that's a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a lot of money.",
    "answer": "but the house is so nice."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the house is so nice.",
    "answer": "it's in a great neighborhood."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's in a great neighborhood.",
    "answer": "it's close to the beach."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's close to the beach.",
    "answer": "it's close to the freeways."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's close to the freeways.",
    "answer": "it's got a big yard."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's got a big yard.",
    "answer": "the kids love the house, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "the kids love the house, too.",
    "answer": "if we don't buy it, someone else will."
  },
  {
    "question": "if we don't buy it, someone else will.",
    "answer": "you're right. let's buy it now. we can worry later."
  },
  {
    "question": "we can't afford this house.",
    "answer": "are you sure?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you sure?",
    "answer": "we will be house rich, but cash poor."
  },
  {
    "question": "we will be house rich, but cash poor.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "our monthly payments will be too high."
  },
  {
    "question": "our monthly payments will be too high.",
    "answer": "we won't have any money for other things?"
  },
  {
    "question": "we won't have any money for other things?",
    "answer": "no, we won't have money for gas or food."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, we won't have money for gas or food.",
    "answer": "we'll be eating peanut butter sandwiches?"
  },
  {
    "question": "we'll be eating peanut butter sandwiches?",
    "answer": "without the peanut butter!"
  },
  {
    "question": "without the peanut butter!",
    "answer": "that's no good!"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's no good!",
    "answer": "we have to find a cheaper house."
  },
  {
    "question": "we have to find a cheaper house.",
    "answer": "of course. we can't live without gas or peanut butter."
  },
  {
    "question": "that is a beautiful house.",
    "answer": "i don't like it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't like it.",
    "answer": "what's the matter with it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter with it?",
    "answer": "it's on the corner."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's on the corner.",
    "answer": "so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so?",
    "answer": "that means it gets twice as much traffic."
  },
  {
    "question": "that means it gets twice as much traffic.",
    "answer": "you're right."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're right.",
    "answer": "when you're inside, you will always hear cars stopping and stopping at the intersection."
  },
  {
    "question": "when you're inside, you will always hear cars stopping and stopping at the intersection.",
    "answer": "or you'll hear the collision if someone doesn't stop."
  },
  {
    "question": "or you'll hear the collision if someone doesn't stop.",
    "answer": "or you'll see the collision if they crash into the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "or you'll see the collision if they crash into the house.",
    "answer": "let's find a house that's at the end of a dead end."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's find a house that's at the end of a dead end.",
    "answer": "that's perfect. the less traffic, the better."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate looking for an apartment.",
    "answer": "me, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me, too.",
    "answer": "we have a 2 o'clock appointment to see the one on main street."
  },
  {
    "question": "we have a 2 o'clock appointment to see the one on main street.",
    "answer": "we'd better get ready to go."
  },
  {
    "question": "we'd better get ready to go.",
    "answer": "it's an upstairs unit."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's an upstairs unit.",
    "answer": "that's good, because i don't want to live under people with loud feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's good, because i don't want to live under people with loud feet.",
    "answer": "and it's a corner unit."
  },
  {
    "question": "and it's a corner unit.",
    "answer": "that's great. we won't have neighbors on both sides of us."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's great. we won't have neighbors on both sides of us.",
    "answer": "no pets are allowed."
  },
  {
    "question": "no pets are allowed.",
    "answer": "perfect. we don't have to listen to barking dogs."
  },
  {
    "question": "perfect. we don't have to listen to barking dogs.",
    "answer": "and there are only six units in the whole building."
  },
  {
    "question": "and there are only six units in the whole building.",
    "answer": "where's the checkbook? i'm ready to rent it without even seeing it."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you call the manager?",
    "answer": "yes. he said he'd come over tomorrow."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. he said he'd come over tomorrow.",
    "answer": "did he say what time?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he say what time?",
    "answer": "yes. he said he'd be here at 9 o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. he said he'd be here at 9 o'clock.",
    "answer": "did he understand what the problem is?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he understand what the problem is?",
    "answer": "yes. i told him our doorbell doesn't work."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i told him our doorbell doesn't work.",
    "answer": "it shouldn't take him long to fix it."
  },
  {
    "question": "it shouldn't take him long to fix it.",
    "answer": "i don't even know why we need to fix it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't even know why we need to fix it.",
    "answer": "in case we have visitors."
  },
  {
    "question": "in case we have visitors.",
    "answer": "but they can just knock on the door."
  },
  {
    "question": "but they can just knock on the door.",
    "answer": "actually, i want him to look at our carpet, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "actually, i want him to look at our carpet, too.",
    "answer": "yes, it would be nice if he'd give us a new carpet."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you like this house?",
    "answer": "yes, it's beautiful."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's beautiful.",
    "answer": "it's perfect for us and the kids."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's perfect for us and the kids.",
    "answer": "three bedrooms, three bathrooms, and a big back yard."
  },
  {
    "question": "three bedrooms, three bathrooms, and a big back yard.",
    "answer": "and we can afford it!"
  },
  {
    "question": "and we can afford it!",
    "answer": "so are we going to buy it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so are we going to buy it?",
    "answer": "i'm afraid not."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm afraid not.",
    "answer": "it's too far from your job, isn't it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "it's too far from your job, isn't it?",
    "answer": "i can't spend four hours on the road every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't spend four hours on the road every day.",
    "answer": "by the time you get home, you'll be too tired to even eat."
  },
  {
    "question": "by the time you get home, you'll be too tired to even eat.",
    "answer": "i won't be able to play with the kids."
  },
  {
    "question": "i won't be able to play with the kids.",
    "answer": "no, we have to find something closer to your job."
  },
  {
    "question": "boy, it's chilly outside, isn't it?",
    "answer": "it sure is."
  },
  {
    "question": "it sure is.",
    "answer": "in fact, it's chilly in the apartment, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "in fact, it's chilly in the apartment, too.",
    "answer": "let's turn on the heat."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's turn on the heat.",
    "answer": "i'll check to make sure that all the windows are shut."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll check to make sure that all the windows are shut.",
    "answer": "it should be warmer in a few minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "it should be warmer in a few minutes.",
    "answer": "it's so nice to have a heated apartment."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's so nice to have a heated apartment.",
    "answer": "how did they survive in the old days?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did they survive in the old days?",
    "answer": "they had fireplaces."
  },
  {
    "question": "they had fireplaces.",
    "answer": "someone had to chop the wood."
  },
  {
    "question": "someone had to chop the wood.",
    "answer": "and carry it into the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "and carry it into the house.",
    "answer": "all we have to do is flip a switch."
  },
  {
    "question": "this is a nice neighborhood.",
    "answer": "the streets are clean and quiet."
  },
  {
    "question": "the streets are clean and quiet.",
    "answer": "the neighbors don't party on the weekends."
  },
  {
    "question": "the neighbors don't party on the weekends.",
    "answer": "people take care of their lawns."
  },
  {
    "question": "people take care of their lawns.",
    "answer": "no rusty old cars are sitting in the front yards."
  },
  {
    "question": "no rusty old cars are sitting in the front yards.",
    "answer": "we never have to call the police about anything."
  },
  {
    "question": "we never have to call the police about anything.",
    "answer": "our kids are completely safe."
  },
  {
    "question": "our kids are completely safe.",
    "answer": "so why are we selling our house?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so why are we selling our house?",
    "answer": "they're building a 3-story apartment building on the corner."
  },
  {
    "question": "they're building a 3-story apartment building on the corner.",
    "answer": "so we've got to sell before property values go down?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so we've got to sell before property values go down?",
    "answer": "yes. i still can't believe our city council allowed this building."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i still can't believe our city council allowed this building.",
    "answer": "they're probably getting something under the table."
  },
  {
    "question": "that was a huge fire in santa barbara.",
    "answer": "yes, it was."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it was.",
    "answer": "they said about 30 houses burned to the ground."
  },
  {
    "question": "they said about 30 houses burned to the ground.",
    "answer": "and they were expensive houses."
  },
  {
    "question": "and they were expensive houses.",
    "answer": "i feel so sorry for those people."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel so sorry for those people.",
    "answer": "why feel sorry for rich people?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why feel sorry for rich people?",
    "answer": "i feel sorry for anyone who loses their home."
  },
  {
    "question": "i feel sorry for anyone who loses their home.",
    "answer": "so do i, but not if they're rich."
  },
  {
    "question": "so do i, but not if they're rich.",
    "answer": "what does that have to do with it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what does that have to do with it?",
    "answer": "rich people think they're better than us."
  },
  {
    "question": "rich people think they're better than us.",
    "answer": "how many rich people do you know?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many rich people do you know?",
    "answer": "none."
  },
  {
    "question": "bears are invading our neighborhoods.",
    "answer": "of course they are. they're starving to death."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course they are. they're starving to death.",
    "answer": "they should stay in the woods where they belong."
  },
  {
    "question": "they should stay in the woods where they belong.",
    "answer": "there's no food in the woods."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's no food in the woods.",
    "answer": "can't they eat grass?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can't they eat grass?",
    "answer": "do you think a bear is a cow?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you think a bear is a cow?",
    "answer": "well, i've seen them eating berries."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, i've seen them eating berries.",
    "answer": "berries aren't in season all year round."
  },
  {
    "question": "berries aren't in season all year round.",
    "answer": "it's too dangerous for kids and pets."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's too dangerous for kids and pets.",
    "answer": "people need to cover their trash cans."
  },
  {
    "question": "people need to cover their trash cans.",
    "answer": "the police need to shoot all the bears."
  },
  {
    "question": "the police need to shoot all the bears.",
    "answer": "you don't solve a problem by shooting it."
  },
  {
    "question": "who did you vote for?",
    "answer": "i voted for obama."
  },
  {
    "question": "i voted for obama.",
    "answer": "me too."
  },
  {
    "question": "me too.",
    "answer": "he will be a great president."
  },
  {
    "question": "he will be a great president.",
    "answer": "everyone likes him."
  },
  {
    "question": "everyone likes him.",
    "answer": "he's a good speaker."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's a good speaker.",
    "answer": "and he's really smart."
  },
  {
    "question": "and he's really smart.",
    "answer": "he will solve our problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "he will solve our problems.",
    "answer": "he will end the war."
  },
  {
    "question": "he will end the war.",
    "answer": "the next four years will be good years."
  },
  {
    "question": "the next four years will be good years.",
    "answer": "i'll vote for him next time, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll vote for him next time, too.",
    "answer": "i think everyone will."
  },
  {
    "question": "the election is next week.",
    "answer": "who are you voting for?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who are you voting for?",
    "answer": "i'm not voting for the mayor."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm not voting for the mayor.",
    "answer": "why not?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why not?",
    "answer": "he made promises that he didn't keep."
  },
  {
    "question": "he made promises that he didn't keep.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "he promised to hire 1,000 more police officers."
  },
  {
    "question": "he promised to hire 1,000 more police officers.",
    "answer": "how many did he hire?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how many did he hire?",
    "answer": "one hundred!"
  },
  {
    "question": "one hundred!",
    "answer": "maybe he had a good reason."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe he had a good reason.",
    "answer": "maybe he's just a liar."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe he's just a liar.",
    "answer": "maybe i'll vote for someone else, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe he won the election.",
    "answer": "only 15 percent of the voters turned out."
  },
  {
    "question": "only 15 percent of the voters turned out.",
    "answer": "that is a joke."
  },
  {
    "question": "that is a joke.",
    "answer": "voting is so important, but people don't bother."
  },
  {
    "question": "voting is so important, but people don't bother.",
    "answer": "many people think their vote doesn't matter."
  },
  {
    "question": "many people think their vote doesn't matter.",
    "answer": "the mayor won by only 2,000 votes."
  },
  {
    "question": "the mayor won by only 2,000 votes.",
    "answer": "we're stuck with him for four more years."
  },
  {
    "question": "we're stuck with him for four more years.",
    "answer": "voting is so easy. you can even mail your ballot in."
  },
  {
    "question": "voting is so easy. you can even mail your ballot in.",
    "answer": "all you have to do is vote and put a stamp on it."
  },
  {
    "question": "all you have to do is vote and put a stamp on it.",
    "answer": "how easy is that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how easy is that?",
    "answer": "i guess people just don't care."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess people just don't care.",
    "answer": "they'll care when they see their taxes go up."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, we have a new president.",
    "answer": "but we have the same old problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "but we have the same old problems.",
    "answer": "well, he's made a few changes."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, he's made a few changes.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "i think he closed the bowling alley in the white house."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think he closed the bowling alley in the white house.",
    "answer": "oh, yeah. he's changing it to a basketball court."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yeah. he's changing it to a basketball court.",
    "answer": "who's paying for that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who's paying for that?",
    "answer": "i think we are!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think we are!",
    "answer": "well, that's okay, as long as it helps him relax and think more clearly."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, that's okay, as long as it helps him relax and think more clearly.",
    "answer": "yes, we need a relaxed president who thinks clearly."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, we need a relaxed president who thinks clearly.",
    "answer": "do any other world leaders have a basketball court?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do any other world leaders have a basketball court?",
    "answer": "they will. you know america always leads the way."
  },
  {
    "question": "people say that everybody loves obama.",
    "answer": "well, more than 50 million people voted for mccain."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, more than 50 million people voted for mccain.",
    "answer": "that's 50 million people who don't love obama."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's 50 million people who don't love obama.",
    "answer": "obama's got four years to make everyone happy."
  },
  {
    "question": "obama's got four years to make everyone happy.",
    "answer": "he's never going to make everyone happy."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's never going to make everyone happy.",
    "answer": "can you imagine being president?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can you imagine being president?",
    "answer": "everyone wants you to solve their problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "everyone wants you to solve their problems.",
    "answer": "i have enough stress from trying to solve my own problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have enough stress from trying to solve my own problems.",
    "answer": "you and everybody else."
  },
  {
    "question": "you and everybody else.",
    "answer": "i would never want to be president."
  },
  {
    "question": "i would never want to be president.",
    "answer": "but think about all the power you'd have."
  },
  {
    "question": "but think about all the power you'd have.",
    "answer": "i prefer my quiet little life to all the power in the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you read this article?",
    "answer": "what article?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what article?",
    "answer": "it says the mayor spends only 11 percent of his time on city duties."
  },
  {
    "question": "it says the mayor spends only 11 percent of his time on city duties.",
    "answer": "only 11 percent?"
  },
  {
    "question": "only 11 percent?",
    "answer": "about 50 percent of the time he's traveling."
  },
  {
    "question": "about 50 percent of the time he's traveling.",
    "answer": "where does he travel to?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where does he travel to?",
    "answer": "oh, all over the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, all over the world.",
    "answer": "but he's supposed to be making our city a better place."
  },
  {
    "question": "but he's supposed to be making our city a better place.",
    "answer": "he's visiting other cities to get ideas."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's visiting other cities to get ideas.",
    "answer": "can't he just go online?"
  },
  {
    "question": "can't he just go online?",
    "answer": "the rest of the time he's raising money for his reelection."
  },
  {
    "question": "the rest of the time he's raising money for his reelection.",
    "answer": "well, he'll never get reelected once this news gets out."
  },
  {
    "question": "who did you vote for for president?",
    "answer": "i voted for ralph nader."
  },
  {
    "question": "i voted for ralph nader.",
    "answer": "who in the world is ralph nader?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who in the world is ralph nader?",
    "answer": "he's the best man for president."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's the best man for president.",
    "answer": "why's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why's that?",
    "answer": "he hates corporations."
  },
  {
    "question": "he hates corporations.",
    "answer": "well, most corporations do think only about money."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, most corporations do think only about money.",
    "answer": "he hates democrats and republicans."
  },
  {
    "question": "he hates democrats and republicans.",
    "answer": "well, they do put their party before their country."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, they do put their party before their country.",
    "answer": "he's the only candidate that i trust."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's the only candidate that i trust.",
    "answer": "but he didn't have a chance. nobody voted for him!"
  },
  {
    "question": "but he didn't have a chance. nobody voted for him!",
    "answer": "sooner or later, voters will wake up."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know why i bother to vote.",
    "answer": "why's that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why's that?",
    "answer": "what good does it do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what good does it do?",
    "answer": "you get to put someone in power that you like."
  },
  {
    "question": "you get to put someone in power that you like.",
    "answer": "only if my candidate wins."
  },
  {
    "question": "only if my candidate wins.",
    "answer": "well, he can't win unless you and others vote for him."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, he can't win unless you and others vote for him.",
    "answer": "but even if my candidate wins, he'll break his promises."
  },
  {
    "question": "but even if my candidate wins, he'll break his promises.",
    "answer": "that's true. they promise anything just so they get elected."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's true. they promise anything just so they get elected.",
    "answer": "and when elected, they go their own way."
  },
  {
    "question": "and when elected, they go their own way.",
    "answer": "they forget who put them in power."
  },
  {
    "question": "they forget who put them in power.",
    "answer": "they forget where they came from."
  },
  {
    "question": "they forget where they came from.",
    "answer": "maybe you should run for office."
  },
  {
    "question": "that election for u.s. senator stunk.",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "there were more votes than voters!"
  },
  {
    "question": "there were more votes than voters!",
    "answer": "but that's impossible."
  },
  {
    "question": "but that's impossible.",
    "answer": "officials said that it's possible."
  },
  {
    "question": "officials said that it's possible.",
    "answer": "did they explain how it's possible?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did they explain how it's possible?",
    "answer": "no. they said there are some things you can't explain."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. they said there are some things you can't explain.",
    "answer": "so are they going to hold another election?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so are they going to hold another election?",
    "answer": "no. that will cost too much money."
  },
  {
    "question": "no. that will cost too much money.",
    "answer": "so it's better to save money than to have an honest election?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so it's better to save money than to have an honest election?",
    "answer": "well, the democratic party says it was an honest election."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, the democratic party says it was an honest election.",
    "answer": "of course they say thatÂ—their man won!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i see that former president bush is at a conference.",
    "answer": "yes. he's telling jokes about his eight years as president."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. he's telling jokes about his eight years as president.",
    "answer": "yes, those eight years were a lot of fun for everyone."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, those eight years were a lot of fun for everyone.",
    "answer": "only 4,000 american soldiers were killed overseas."
  },
  {
    "question": "only 4,000 american soldiers were killed overseas.",
    "answer": "not to mention 40,000 wounded soldiers."
  },
  {
    "question": "not to mention 40,000 wounded soldiers.",
    "answer": "but bush visited some of them in the hospital once."
  },
  {
    "question": "but bush visited some of them in the hospital once.",
    "answer": "that's nice that he found the time to make a visit."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's nice that he found the time to make a visit.",
    "answer": "he spoke to them and made them feel better."
  },
  {
    "question": "he spoke to them and made them feel better.",
    "answer": "did he speak to every family that lost a soldier?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did he speak to every family that lost a soldier?",
    "answer": "no, he didn't have time to do that."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, he didn't have time to do that.",
    "answer": "well, he's got plenty of time now!"
  },
  {
    "question": "well, he's got plenty of time now!",
    "answer": "no, he's too busy writing a book about how hard it was to be president."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you get your official sample ballot?",
    "answer": "yes, with the voter instructions."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, with the voter instructions.",
    "answer": "how are you going to vote?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how are you going to vote?",
    "answer": "same as ever, by mail. all it costs me is a 42-cent stamp."
  },
  {
    "question": "same as ever, by mail. all it costs me is a 42-cent stamp.",
    "answer": "i meant, are you going to vote for or against the new taxes?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i meant, are you going to vote for or against the new taxes?",
    "answer": "against all of them, of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "against all of them, of course.",
    "answer": "but we need new taxes to pay for highways, schools, and prisons."
  },
  {
    "question": "but we need new taxes to pay for highways, schools, and prisons.",
    "answer": "we've already voted for new taxes to pay for all that stuff!"
  },
  {
    "question": "we've already voted for new taxes to pay for all that stuff!",
    "answer": "that's true. where did that money go?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's true. where did that money go?",
    "answer": "our legislators spent it on first-class travel all over the world."
  },
  {
    "question": "our legislators spent it on first-class travel all over the world.",
    "answer": "they are having a good time with our money."
  },
  {
    "question": "they are having a good time with our money.",
    "answer": "so when are we going to stop giving them more?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you decided how you are going to vote?",
    "answer": "do you mean on measures 1, 2, and 3?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you mean on measures 1, 2, and 3?",
    "answer": "yes. the ones that will improve our schools, roads, and hospitals."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. the ones that will improve our schools, roads, and hospitals.",
    "answer": "you mean the measures that will raise our taxes."
  },
  {
    "question": "you mean the measures that will raise our taxes.",
    "answer": "but the tv ads say that our taxes will not increase."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the tv ads say that our taxes will not increase.",
    "answer": "do you believe the tv ads?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you believe the tv ads?",
    "answer": "i like the one where the fireman tells us why we should vote yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i like the one where the fireman tells us why we should vote yes.",
    "answer": "don't believe him! whatever the tv ads tell you, the opposite is true."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't believe him! whatever the tv ads tell you, the opposite is true.",
    "answer": "but the title of measure 1 is \"better schools at no cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the title of measure 1 is \"better schools at no cost.",
    "answer": "the title should be \"better schools at huge cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "the title should be \"better schools at huge cost.",
    "answer": "i can't believe that they would lie to us."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe that they would lie to us.",
    "answer": "of course they lieÂ—that's what politicians do!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i have a stomachache.",
    "answer": "is it something you ate?"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it something you ate?",
    "answer": "maybe. i'm not sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe. i'm not sure.",
    "answer": "what did you have for breakfast?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you have for breakfast?",
    "answer": "the usual, cereal with milk and a banana."
  },
  {
    "question": "the usual, cereal with milk and a banana.",
    "answer": "maybe the milk was bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe the milk was bad.",
    "answer": "it didn't smell bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "it didn't smell bad.",
    "answer": "maybe the banana was bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe the banana was bad.",
    "answer": "no, the banana was delicious."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, the banana was delicious.",
    "answer": "maybe you just need to go to the bathroom."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe you just need to go to the bathroom.",
    "answer": "no, that's not the problem."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, that's not the problem.",
    "answer": "maybe it will go away in a little while."
  },
  {
    "question": "what's this stain?",
    "answer": "i don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know.",
    "answer": "it looks like blood."
  },
  {
    "question": "it looks like blood.",
    "answer": "i think my nose was bleeding."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think my nose was bleeding.",
    "answer": "you should wet your shirt immediately."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should wet your shirt immediately.",
    "answer": "why?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why?",
    "answer": "because that gets the blood out of the shirt."
  },
  {
    "question": "because that gets the blood out of the shirt.",
    "answer": "what's a little blood?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's a little blood?",
    "answer": "your white shirt is ruined."
  },
  {
    "question": "your white shirt is ruined.",
    "answer": "so, i'll just buy another one."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, i'll just buy another one.",
    "answer": "you can wear this one around the house."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can wear this one around the house.",
    "answer": "next time i'll soak it immediately."
  },
  {
    "question": "my fingers hurt.",
    "answer": "why do they hurt?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do they hurt?",
    "answer": "i type too much."
  },
  {
    "question": "i type too much.",
    "answer": "you should take a break."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should take a break.",
    "answer": "i need to type to make money."
  },
  {
    "question": "i need to type to make money.",
    "answer": "but typing is causing you pain."
  },
  {
    "question": "but typing is causing you pain.",
    "answer": "maybe i should see a doctor."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe i should see a doctor.",
    "answer": "doctors are too expensive."
  },
  {
    "question": "doctors are too expensive.",
    "answer": "he might tell me to rest for a while."
  },
  {
    "question": "he might tell me to rest for a while.",
    "answer": "he might want to cut you open."
  },
  {
    "question": "he might want to cut you open.",
    "answer": "he might say i'm okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "he might say i'm okay.",
    "answer": "he might say you have bone cancer."
  },
  {
    "question": "what did the doctor say?",
    "answer": "he thinks i have too much stress."
  },
  {
    "question": "he thinks i have too much stress.",
    "answer": "stress causes your stomachaches?"
  },
  {
    "question": "stress causes your stomachaches?",
    "answer": "stress causes different problems with different people."
  },
  {
    "question": "stress causes different problems with different people.",
    "answer": "so what did he tell you to do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so what did he tell you to do?",
    "answer": "he said i need to think positive."
  },
  {
    "question": "he said i need to think positive.",
    "answer": "he didn't give you any medication?"
  },
  {
    "question": "he didn't give you any medication?",
    "answer": "i hate medication. it makes me feel different."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate medication. it makes me feel different.",
    "answer": "so how do you think positive?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so how do you think positive?",
    "answer": "i think about nice things."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think about nice things.",
    "answer": "like what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "like what?",
    "answer": "like a day at the beach, with my toes in the sand."
  },
  {
    "question": "i cut my finger.",
    "answer": "how did you do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did you do that?",
    "answer": "it's a paper cut."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's a paper cut.",
    "answer": "paper can be dangerous."
  },
  {
    "question": "paper can be dangerous.",
    "answer": "it hurts, too."
  },
  {
    "question": "it hurts, too.",
    "answer": "paper cuts can hurt a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "paper cuts can hurt a lot.",
    "answer": "where are the band-aids?"
  },
  {
    "question": "where are the band-aids?",
    "answer": "i think they're in the medicine cabinet."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think they're in the medicine cabinet.",
    "answer": "it's on the tip of my finger."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's on the tip of my finger.",
    "answer": "a band-aid might not work."
  },
  {
    "question": "a band-aid might not work.",
    "answer": "i must not use this finger until the cut heals."
  },
  {
    "question": "i must not use this finger until the cut heals.",
    "answer": "it might take a day or two to heal."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you smell that?",
    "answer": "oh, yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, yes.",
    "answer": "i can't stand cigarette smoke."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't stand cigarette smoke.",
    "answer": "it smells so bad."
  },
  {
    "question": "it smells so bad.",
    "answer": "one cigarette stinks up the whole sidewalk."
  },
  {
    "question": "one cigarette stinks up the whole sidewalk.",
    "answer": "smokers think they are so cool."
  },
  {
    "question": "smokers think they are so cool.",
    "answer": "they are so weak."
  },
  {
    "question": "they are so weak.",
    "answer": "a little cigarette controls them."
  },
  {
    "question": "a little cigarette controls them.",
    "answer": "they look so stupid taking a puff."
  },
  {
    "question": "they look so stupid taking a puff.",
    "answer": "and then they blow smoke out of their mouth."
  },
  {
    "question": "and then they blow smoke out of their mouth.",
    "answer": "they think it's cool."
  },
  {
    "question": "they think it's cool.",
    "answer": "cigarettes stink."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you have a cold?",
    "answer": "yes, i do."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, i do.",
    "answer": "how did you get it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how did you get it?",
    "answer": "my sister had a cold. she gave it to me."
  },
  {
    "question": "my sister had a cold. she gave it to me.",
    "answer": "have you taken anything for your cold?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you taken anything for your cold?",
    "answer": "no, i just blow my nose a lot."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i just blow my nose a lot.",
    "answer": "your nose is stopped up?"
  },
  {
    "question": "your nose is stopped up?",
    "answer": "yes. i have to breathe through my mouth."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. i have to breathe through my mouth.",
    "answer": "have you tried nose drops?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you tried nose drops?",
    "answer": "no, i don't like nose drops."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i don't like nose drops.",
    "answer": "they work great."
  },
  {
    "question": "they work great.",
    "answer": "i don't care. i don't like to put drops in my nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "would you put suntan lotion on my back, please?",
    "answer": "sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "sure.",
    "answer": "thank you."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you.",
    "answer": "you shouldn't lie in the sun for too long."
  },
  {
    "question": "you shouldn't lie in the sun for too long.",
    "answer": "i want to get a tan. i don't want to look so pale."
  },
  {
    "question": "i want to get a tan. i don't want to look so pale.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with looking pale?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with looking pale?",
    "answer": "people think you might be sick."
  },
  {
    "question": "people think you might be sick.",
    "answer": "who thinks that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who thinks that?",
    "answer": "i don't know."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know.",
    "answer": "it's better to be pale than to have skin cancer."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's better to be pale than to have skin cancer.",
    "answer": "i know that."
  },
  {
    "question": "i know that.",
    "answer": "so why are you arguing with me? don't lie in the sun too long!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't quit smoking.",
    "answer": "of course you can."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course you can.",
    "answer": "i don't have enough will power."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't have enough will power.",
    "answer": "of course you do."
  },
  {
    "question": "of course you do.",
    "answer": "i wish i had never started."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wish i had never started.",
    "answer": "so does every smoker."
  },
  {
    "question": "so does every smoker.",
    "answer": "i've tried to quit so many times."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've tried to quit so many times.",
    "answer": "so has everyone else."
  },
  {
    "question": "so has everyone else.",
    "answer": "nothing seems to work."
  },
  {
    "question": "nothing seems to work.",
    "answer": "all it takes is will power, and you have it."
  },
  {
    "question": "all it takes is will power, and you have it.",
    "answer": "then why can't i quit?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why can't i quit?",
    "answer": "you have to believe in yourself."
  },
  {
    "question": "my back is killing me.",
    "answer": "what did you do?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did you do?",
    "answer": "i got out of my car."
  },
  {
    "question": "i got out of my car.",
    "answer": "that's it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's it?",
    "answer": "i injured my back one time just by sneezing."
  },
  {
    "question": "i injured my back one time just by sneezing.",
    "answer": "you should see a doctor."
  },
  {
    "question": "you should see a doctor.",
    "answer": "my doctor said i need surgery."
  },
  {
    "question": "my doctor said i need surgery.",
    "answer": "so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so?",
    "answer": "so, forget it."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, forget it.",
    "answer": "you don't have the money?"
  },
  {
    "question": "you don't have the money?",
    "answer": "i have no insurance."
  },
  {
    "question": "i have no insurance.",
    "answer": "maybe a back rub would help."
  },
  {
    "question": "my brother smokes three packs a day.",
    "answer": "three packs of what?"
  },
  {
    "question": "three packs of what?",
    "answer": "cigarettes, of course."
  },
  {
    "question": "cigarettes, of course.",
    "answer": "how can he do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how can he do that?",
    "answer": "when he is almost finished with one cigarette, he uses it to light another."
  },
  {
    "question": "when he is almost finished with one cigarette, he uses it to light another.",
    "answer": "he's a chain smoker."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's a chain smoker.",
    "answer": "he's been a chain smoker for 30 years."
  },
  {
    "question": "he's been a chain smoker for 30 years.",
    "answer": "that's unbelievable. can he still breathe?"
  },
  {
    "question": "that's unbelievable. can he still breathe?",
    "answer": "he can, but the people around him can't."
  },
  {
    "question": "he can, but the people around him can't.",
    "answer": "how can he still be alive?"
  },
  {
    "question": "how can he still be alive?",
    "answer": "his doctor says his heart and lungs are strong and healthy."
  },
  {
    "question": "his doctor says his heart and lungs are strong and healthy.",
    "answer": "maybe i should start smoking."
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate brushing my teeth.",
    "answer": "it's such a chore."
  },
  {
    "question": "it's such a chore.",
    "answer": "brush, brush. spit, spit."
  },
  {
    "question": "brush, brush. spit, spit.",
    "answer": "what did they do in the old days?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what did they do in the old days?",
    "answer": "they brushed with their fingers."
  },
  {
    "question": "they brushed with their fingers.",
    "answer": "they also ate with their fingers!"
  },
  {
    "question": "they also ate with their fingers!",
    "answer": "why do they call it the good old days?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why do they call it the good old days?",
    "answer": "maybe because they didn't have to brush and floss."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe because they didn't have to brush and floss.",
    "answer": "who invented flossing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "who invented flossing?",
    "answer": "a dentist, i'm sure."
  },
  {
    "question": "a dentist, i'm sure.",
    "answer": "i hate flossing more than brushing!"
  },
  {
    "question": "i hate flossing more than brushing!",
    "answer": "i can't wait till all my teeth fall out."
  },
  {
    "question": "let's stop for a while. i need a break and some water.",
    "answer": "this trail is hard to climb."
  },
  {
    "question": "this trail is hard to climb.",
    "answer": "especially on a hot day like this."
  },
  {
    "question": "especially on a hot day like this.",
    "answer": "i can't believe we haven't seen any animals."
  },
  {
    "question": "i can't believe we haven't seen any animals.",
    "answer": "thank goodness! i don't want to see any wild animals."
  },
  {
    "question": "thank goodness! i don't want to see any wild animals.",
    "answer": "all we've seen so far is a couple of lizards."
  },
  {
    "question": "all we've seen so far is a couple of lizards.",
    "answer": "we're hiking to lose weight, not to see goats and bears."
  },
  {
    "question": "we're hiking to lose weight, not to see goats and bears.",
    "answer": "i bet i've lost a couple of pounds already."
  },
  {
    "question": "i bet i've lost a couple of pounds already.",
    "answer": "all you've lost is some sweat."
  },
  {
    "question": "all you've lost is some sweat.",
    "answer": "i haven't even lost one pound of fat?"
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven't even lost one pound of fat?",
    "answer": "if you want to lose fat, you've got to do this hike every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "if you want to lose fat, you've got to do this hike every day.",
    "answer": "okay, but let's hike in town. at least there are cats and dogs to see."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh no, another pimple on my face.",
    "answer": "pimples suck."
  },
  {
    "question": "pimples suck.",
    "answer": "it seems like i get a new pimple almost every day."
  },
  {
    "question": "it seems like i get a new pimple almost every day.",
    "answer": "maybe it's something in your diet."
  },
  {
    "question": "maybe it's something in your diet.",
    "answer": "no, i eat the same things day after day."
  },
  {
    "question": "no, i eat the same things day after day.",
    "answer": "then maybe it's in your genes."
  },
  {
    "question": "then maybe it's in your genes.",
    "answer": "you might be right."
  },
  {
    "question": "you might be right.",
    "answer": "do pimples run in your family?"
  },
  {
    "question": "do pimples run in your family?",
    "answer": "not that i've noticed."
  },
  {
    "question": "not that i've noticed.",
    "answer": "well, maybe it's from the pollution in the air."
  },
  {
    "question": "well, maybe it's from the pollution in the air.",
    "answer": "whatever the cause, i hate seeing them on my face."
  },
  {
    "question": "whatever the cause, i hate seeing them on my face.",
    "answer": "well, on the bright side, they're fun to pop."
  },
  {
    "question": "do you believe everything you hear?",
    "answer": "i don't believe anything i don't see with my own eyes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't believe anything i don't see with my own eyes.",
    "answer": "you can't believe what you hear on tv or radio."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can't believe what you hear on tv or radio.",
    "answer": "you can't believe what you read in the newspapers."
  },
  {
    "question": "you can't believe what you read in the newspapers.",
    "answer": "everyone tells you a different story about the same thing."
  },
  {
    "question": "everyone tells you a different story about the same thing.",
    "answer": "three different people will give you three different stories."
  },
  {
    "question": "three different people will give you three different stories.",
    "answer": "and the government will give you a fourth story."
  },
  {
    "question": "and the government will give you a fourth story.",
    "answer": "yes, like the government says not to worry about the swine flu."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, like the government says not to worry about the swine flu.",
    "answer": "but the swine flu just killed 20 people in mexico."
  },
  {
    "question": "but the swine flu just killed 20 people in mexico.",
    "answer": "the government says we have nothing to worry about."
  },
  {
    "question": "the government says we have nothing to worry about.",
    "answer": "then why are some schools telling the kids to stay home?"
  },
  {
    "question": "then why are some schools telling the kids to stay home?",
    "answer": "the government says to wash our hands frequently, and we'll all be okay."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't pick your nose.",
    "answer": "i wasn't picking my nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "i wasn't picking my nose.",
    "answer": "what were you doing?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what were you doing?",
    "answer": "i was scratching my nose."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was scratching my nose.",
    "answer": "i think i know the difference between picking and scratching."
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i know the difference between picking and scratching.",
    "answer": "okay, mom, maybe i was picking it a little bit."
  },
  {
    "question": "okay, mom, maybe i was picking it a little bit.",
    "answer": "use a tissue next time."
  },
  {
    "question": "use a tissue next time.",
    "answer": "i didn't have a tissue."
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn't have a tissue.",
    "answer": "then wait till you find a tissue."
  },
  {
    "question": "then wait till you find a tissue.",
    "answer": "i couldn't wait. it was an emergency."
  },
  {
    "question": "i couldn't wait. it was an emergency.",
    "answer": "oh, really? maybe you should have called 911."
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, really? maybe you should have called 911.",
    "answer": "it wasn't that kind of emergency."
  },
  {
    "question": "our tv remote is filthy.",
    "answer": "yes, it's covered with crud."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, it's covered with crud.",
    "answer": "i'm going to clean it."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'm going to clean it.",
    "answer": "don't use water on it!"
  },
  {
    "question": "don't use water on it!",
    "answer": "i'll use a damp cloth."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll use a damp cloth.",
    "answer": "don't let water get into any of the cracks."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't let water get into any of the cracks.",
    "answer": "i'll squeeze the cloth so it's almost dry."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll squeeze the cloth so it's almost dry.",
    "answer": "don't rub the numbers off the remote."
  },
  {
    "question": "don't rub the numbers off the remote.",
    "answer": "i will rub gently but firmly."
  },
  {
    "question": "i will rub gently but firmly.",
    "answer": "do it quickly, please, so i can change channels during commercials."
  },
  {
    "question": "do it quickly, please, so i can change channels during commercials.",
    "answer": "i'll give it back to you in a couple of minutes."
  },
  {
    "question": "i'll give it back to you in a couple of minutes.",
    "answer": "maybe we should put it in a plastic bag to keep it clean."
  },
  {
    "question": "my ear is killing me.",
    "answer": "what's the matter?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's the matter?",
    "answer": "i was on a plane."
  },
  {
    "question": "i was on a plane.",
    "answer": "so?"
  },
  {
    "question": "so?",
    "answer": "so, every time the plane goes up, my ear starts to hurt."
  },
  {
    "question": "so, every time the plane goes up, my ear starts to hurt.",
    "answer": "that's no good."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's no good.",
    "answer": "sometimes the pain goes away, and sometimes it doesn't."
  },
  {
    "question": "sometimes the pain goes away, and sometimes it doesn't.",
    "answer": "have you seen a doctor?"
  },
  {
    "question": "have you seen a doctor?",
    "answer": "i've been to two doctors."
  },
  {
    "question": "i've been to two doctors.",
    "answer": "and they couldn't fix your problem?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and they couldn't fix your problem?",
    "answer": "they both said i have to live with it."
  },
  {
    "question": "they both said i have to live with it.",
    "answer": "or you can stay off planes."
  },
  {
    "question": "did you see the woman with the new face?",
    "answer": "did she get a nice job?"
  },
  {
    "question": "did she get a nice job?",
    "answer": "she got an \"everything\" job!"
  },
  {
    "question": "she got an \"everything\" job!",
    "answer": "what do you mean?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you mean?",
    "answer": "a team of doctors gave her a whole new face."
  },
  {
    "question": "a team of doctors gave her a whole new face.",
    "answer": "why did they do that?"
  },
  {
    "question": "why did they do that?",
    "answer": "a mad dog bit most of her face off."
  },
  {
    "question": "a mad dog bit most of her face off.",
    "answer": "oh, that's terrible. what does she look like now?"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh, that's terrible. what does she look like now?",
    "answer": "her face is really fat, but they say the swelling will go down."
  },
  {
    "question": "her face is really fat, but they say the swelling will go down.",
    "answer": "and then will she look normal again?"
  },
  {
    "question": "and then will she look normal again?",
    "answer": "i guess so."
  },
  {
    "question": "i guess so.",
    "answer": "god bless modern medicine."
  },
  {
    "question": "there's something wrong with my right hand.",
    "answer": "what's wrong with it?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what's wrong with it?",
    "answer": "it aches most of the time."
  },
  {
    "question": "it aches most of the time.",
    "answer": "what do you think it is?"
  },
  {
    "question": "what do you think it is?",
    "answer": "i don't know. i think it's old age."
  },
  {
    "question": "i don't know. i think it's old age.",
    "answer": "if it's old age, why don't both of your hands hurt?"
  },
  {
    "question": "if it's old age, why don't both of your hands hurt?",
    "answer": "that's a good question. maybe it's not old age."
  },
  {
    "question": "that's a good question. maybe it's not old age.",
    "answer": "are you right-handed?"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you right-handed?",
    "answer": "yes. all my life."
  },
  {
    "question": "yes. all my life.",
    "answer": "you're wearing out your right hand. stop using it so much."
  },
  {
    "question": "you're wearing out your right hand. stop using it so much.",
    "answer": "but i do all my writing with my right hand."
  },
  {
    "question": "but i do all my writing with my right hand.",
    "answer": "start typing instead. that way your left hand will do half the work."
  }
]